<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Celebs on Brainsation</title>
    <link>http://st.brainsation.com/tags/celebs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Celebs on Brainsation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 05:56:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://st.brainsation.com/tags/celebs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Meghan Markle Makes Royal Faux Pas In Awkward Moment With Queen Elizabeth</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/meghan-markle-makes-royal-faux-pas-in-awkward-moment-with-queen-elizabeth/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 05:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/meghan-markle-makes-royal-faux-pas-in-awkward-moment-with-queen-elizabeth/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Of course, she&amp;rsquo;s a novice when it comes to protocol,&amp;rdquo; said a Buckingham Palace insider. &amp;ldquo;She&amp;rsquo;s having to learn all this as she goes. The Duchess of Cambridge was a natural, however, Meghan Markle seems rather dense by comparison.&amp;rdquo; Meghan Markle had her first joint appearance with Queen Elizabeth on Thursday, but unfortunately for her, she didn&amp;rsquo;t impress anyone with her understanding of royal protocol.

Image Credit &amp;ldquo;She looked like a fool,&amp;rdquo; said Ashley Winslow, a reporter for the BBC who was present for incident.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kate Middleton Refuses To Make Same Mistake With Prince Louis That She Did With Charlotte -- She’s Not Backing Down…</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/kate-middleton-refuses-to-make-same-mistake-with-prince-louis-that-she-did-with-charlotte-shes-not-backing-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 05:30:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/kate-middleton-refuses-to-make-same-mistake-with-prince-louis-that-she-did-with-charlotte-shes-not-backing-down/</guid>
      <description>On April 23rd of this year, Prince William and his wife Kate Middleton happily welcomed their third child, Prince Louis, into this world. Several hours after his birth, Louis was presented to the public when the Duke and Duchess of Cambridge stepped out of the Lindo Wing and allowed the press to photograph the newborn as he slept. Afterwards, Kate returned to her home at Kensington Palace with Louis to rest and recover.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why This NFL Superstar&#39;s Secret Life Attracted The FBI&#39;s Attention</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/why-this-nfl-superstars-secret-life-attracted-fbi-spm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2018 03:34:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/why-this-nfl-superstars-secret-life-attracted-fbi-spm/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever worked so hard in your life that you wanted to let loose and have a bit of dangerous fun? Most of us have and it was no different for this football superstar. He thrived on competition, the thrill and excitement, that it brings to the table when he knocks someone out to run across the field and get that touchdown. The thrill has driven him to be the superstar that he is today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>These Celebrities Fought Hard Against Drugs And Addiction, But Eventually Lost Everything</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/these-celebrities-fought-hard-against-drugs-and-addiction-but-eventually-lost-everything/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 18:47:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/these-celebrities-fought-hard-against-drugs-and-addiction-but-eventually-lost-everything/</guid>
      <description>NYDailyNews Our obsession with celebrities is a phenomenon as old as the moving picture. For some reason, a switch flips in our brains when we see someone on a screen that makes us want to know everything possible about that person and what they&amp;rsquo;re doing every single day. But the pressure of constantly being in the public eye can have an adverse effect on celebrities, most of whom are just regular people trying to live normal lives when they&amp;rsquo;re off-set.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>These Female Olympians Have Our Hearts Racing, And You&#39;re About To See Why</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/female-olympians/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 07:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/female-olympians/</guid>
      <description>With the 2018 Olympics upon us, you might find yourself flipping through photos of hot female athletes &amp;ndash; so, we&amp;rsquo;ve saved you some trouble. While all athletes are in shape (it&amp;rsquo;s kind of a requirement of the job) some of them are just downright sexy. For many of them, time off from training means there&amp;rsquo;s plenty of time to model, and plenty of these ladies do just that. You may recognize a number of these sexy athletes from their various ads and photoshoots in which they aren&amp;rsquo;t at all shy about showing off their incredible bodies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Celebrities You Had No Idea Are Atheist</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-celebrities-you-had-no-idea-are-atheist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 22:47:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-celebrities-you-had-no-idea-are-atheist/</guid>
      <description>qpolitical Hollywood stars mesmerize everyday people with their larger than life portrayals of historical and dramatic figures. Some celebrities convince us, when playing people like Ghandi, Moses or Jesus Christ, that they have a devoutly spiritual soul. That’s is certainly a testament to their great acting skills and abilities to create on-screen passion. But, at the end of the day, we generally do not know these stars of the silver screen personally.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Celebrities With Good For Nothing Kids</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-celebrities-with-good-for-nothing-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 20:48:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-celebrities-with-good-for-nothing-kids/</guid>
      <description>teriobrien Like the saying goes, the apple doesn’t fall far from the tree. This definitely holds true for children of famous celebrities. These tots often inherit their parents’ superstar good looks and talents. However, the work ethic and personal skills that helped launch their parents to the top of their fields is often completely lacking in the more privileged progeny. Hidden by the shade of their parent’s fame, their problems usually don’t catch the public eye until they’ve gone completely off the deep end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Celebs You Didn&#39;t Realize Were Transgender</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-celebs-you-didnt-realize-were-transgender/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 21:27:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-celebs-you-didnt-realize-were-transgender/</guid>
      <description>Transgender people are making themselves known more and more. Transgender people have always been courageous; however, many are now also becoming famous for what they are doing and how they are doing it. Younger people are no longer accepting arbitrarily-imposed definitions of gender identity or sexual orientation. In general, they are much more fluid about these things. They realize that these personal feelings are truly up to each individual. Diversity is amazing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful Wives of Celebrities: Then and Now</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/beautiful-wives-of-celebrities/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 19:41:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/beautiful-wives-of-celebrities/</guid>
      <description>“Behind every great man, there’s a great woman.” Celebrities are no exception. Throughout history, the public has followed the love lives of celebs, from dating to marriage to children. However, here are the wives, and ex-wives, you may not remember.
Robert Redford – Lola Van Wagenen Robert Redford and Lola Van Wagenen met, in 1957, and were secretly married, in Las Vegas, in 1958. However, they had a public ceremony a few months later, in Provo, Utah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Unapologetic Life Of Howard Stern</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-unapologetic-life-of-howard-stern/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2017 22:42:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-unapologetic-life-of-howard-stern/</guid>
      <description>Cloudfont Some claim that Howard Stern was chased out of terrestrial radio by the fists and screams of moralists. Others say that he left by his own steam, settling in at a quieter and better-paying gig on satellite radio, where the moralists could find no, even slightly absurd, argument to ban him. From whichever perspective you see him through his eighties metal-hair, which for some creepy reason he looks good with the metal-kid curly locks in 2017, you have to agree he has never apologized for anything he&amp;rsquo;s said or done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Insane Celebrity Mansions You Wish You Lived In</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-insane-celebrity-mansions-you-wish-you-lived-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 20:53:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-insane-celebrity-mansions-you-wish-you-lived-in/</guid>
      <description>SunSentinel We all dream of living in sprawling, luxurious, marble finished mansions. This will remain a dream for many of us but for most superstars; it is a reality. Most celebrities make a lot of money from their careers, and they also love to flaunt their fortunes. Considering the amount of money they make every year, it should not come as a surprise that they live in luxurious mega mansions in some of the most beautiful and exclusive neighborhoods on earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Most Stunning Wives and Girlfriends of NBA Stars</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-most-stunning-wives-and-girlfriends-of-nba-stars/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2017 18:55:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-most-stunning-wives-and-girlfriends-of-nba-stars/</guid>
      <description>Over the past several years the NBA has turned into quite possibly the biggest sport in america, with more stars in the league than any other. With all of this new star-power, the pretty, and not so pretty, women are sure to not be far behind. We are here to keep you up to date with all of the off-court drama, and bring you the hottest (and strangest) wives and girlfriends of the NBA superstars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Most Expensive &amp; Shocking Celebrity Plastic Surgeries</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/most-expensive-shocking-celebrity-plastic-surgeries/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 22:20:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/most-expensive-shocking-celebrity-plastic-surgeries/</guid>
      <description>Donatella Versace – $25,000 She is synonymous with her last name in the fashion industry. As she has aged she has tried to keep herself young. $25k, might seem like alot, but compared to the other names on this list, it is actually quite cheap. We&amp;rsquo;re thinking she wishes she had shelled out more money, because she looks sort of inhuman at this point!

Pinterest
Lil’ Kim – $19,625 With the passing of time comes a change for the better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kardashians: The Unknown Early Years</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/kardashians-early-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 20:21:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/kardashians-early-years/</guid>
      <description>Even if you are not a fan, it is hard to look away from the rumors and gossip that follow the wealthy family. And safe to say there are many of them. From Kim’s bold magazine cover to Khloe’s real biological father, even if you don’t watch the show you most likely are aware of all the drama, since it is plastered all over our television sets, smartphones, tablets and computers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful Hollywood Celebs: Then and Now</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/where-are-these-beautiful-celebrities-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 23:26:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/where-are-these-beautiful-celebrities-today/</guid>
      <description>We all remember these vixens from the 80&amp;rsquo;s and 90&amp;rsquo;s. They were beautiful celebrities starring in our favorite movies and TV shows. Over the years they have fallen out of the spotlight. But we are here to track them down for you and show how they have aged over the years. Some for better, some for tragically worse.

Kelly McGillis We fell in love with her in the 80&amp;rsquo;s as Maverick&amp;rsquo;s brainy beau, Charlie Blackwood, in &amp;lsquo;Top Gun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Most Shocking Wives and Girlfriends of NBA Stars</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-23-hottest-wags-in-the-nba/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 20:05:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-23-hottest-wags-in-the-nba/</guid>
      <description>Over the past several years the NBA has turned into quite possibly the biggest sport in america, with more stars in the league than any other. With all of this new star-power, the pretty, and not so pretty, women are sure to not be far behind. We are here to keep you up to date with all of the off-court drama, and bring you the hottest (and strangest) wives and girlfriends of the NBA superstars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 20 Celebs You Didn&#39;t Know Were Gay</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/top-20-celebs-you-didnt-know-were-gay/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 18:31:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/top-20-celebs-you-didnt-know-were-gay/</guid>
      <description>Many movie stars and artists are in gay relationships. Even though they try to keep their private life away from the public domain, they are eventually exposed. However, there are those who embrace who they are by admitting to the world that they are gay. Below is a list of 20 celebrities who you didn&amp;rsquo;t know were gay.
1. Tom Daley 
DailyStar Tom used a homemade video to break his silence regarding his relationship status.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Lame To Fame: Amazing Celebrity Transformations That&#39;ll Make You Double-Take!</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/from-lame-to-fame-amazing-celebrity-transformations-thatll-make-you-double-take/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 18:47:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/from-lame-to-fame-amazing-celebrity-transformations-thatll-make-you-double-take/</guid>
      <description>Stars grow up just like regular people. Plus, with the added pressure from fans and critics, it makes sense that celebrities would want to change a few things every now and again. From weight loss to total make overs, these 30 stars have had the biggest transformations of our time.

BET
Jonah Hill - 2016 
InTouch
Jonah Hill has become rather well known for his rapid weight fluctuations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Actors You didn&#39;t Realize Passed Away in 2017</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-actors-you-didnt-realize-passed-away-in-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 19:07:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-actors-you-didnt-realize-passed-away-in-2017/</guid>
      <description>Reddit Life is short, so they say. Any moment someone can die and when death strikes all we can do is mourn the departed soul and wish that it rest s in eternal peace. Unfortunately, death isn&amp;rsquo;t selective about who should go and who should remain on earth. Over the past few years, we have lost some of the greatest men and women who brought us unforgettable memories. 2017 hasn&amp;rsquo;t been any different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Celebrity Children All Grown Up</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/10-celebrity-children-all-grown-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 23:23:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/10-celebrity-children-all-grown-up/</guid>
      <description>Celebrities’ lives are splashed across a myriad of media outlets every day, all day. The reality is reporting on celebrities is really big business.
The children of these gifted, renowned individuals, however, are often purposefully hidden from the public for obvious reasons. What is quite fascinating is that celebrity offspring are frequently even more impressive than their parents. A large percentage of these celebrity children try to follow their parents’ professional career paths.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What The Cast Of Game Of Thrones Were Like Before They Got Famous</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/what-the-cast-of-game-of-thrones-were-like-before-they-got-famous/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 00:05:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/what-the-cast-of-game-of-thrones-were-like-before-they-got-famous/</guid>
      <description>Game of Thrones is undoubtedly one of the most popular shows to have ever graced the small screen. With its vast world and intriguing characters, this monster HBO original from writer George R.R. Martin premiered to great acclaim and a healthy fan craze. Part of the success is the cast, who are made up of some well-known names and newcomers alike.
TheSuperficial
Here is a look at what some of the brilliant cast was up to before they entered the world of Westeros.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>These 30 Celebrities Dodged Their Taxes And Ran From The IRS</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/these-30-celebrities-dodged-taxes-ran-from-the-irs-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2017 20:43:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/these-30-celebrities-dodged-taxes-ran-from-the-irs-2/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Money is a problem until you&amp;rsquo;ve got some.&amp;rdquo; This adage is true for some, but not for these riches-to-rags celebrities. Whether it be gambling, bad investing, or poor spending, these people have all had to evade the taxman at least once in their lives. From boxers to actors to presidents of the United States, here are 30 celebrities who fled the IRS.
Flickr
Pamela Anderson Flickr
Known as a bona fide sex symbol in the 1990s, Pamela Anderson has had a rough going of things as of late.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Celebrities Who Went Broke and Have To Work Normal Jobs</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/these-30-celebrities-dodged-their-taxes-and-ran-from-the-irs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2017 20:12:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/these-30-celebrities-dodged-their-taxes-and-ran-from-the-irs/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Money is a problem until you&amp;rsquo;ve got some.&amp;rdquo; This adage is true for some, but not for these riches-to-rags celebrities. Whether it be gambling, bad investing, or poor spending, these people have all had to evade the taxman at least once in their lives. From boxers to actors to presidents of the United States, here are 30 celebrities who lost it all.
Pinterest
Vanilla Ice Sells Real Estate MasterChollo</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Shocking Net Worth Of These Celebs Will Completely Boggle Your Mind</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/shocking-net-worths/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 17:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/shocking-net-worths/</guid>
      <description>Reddit Life is short, so they say. Any moment someone can die and when death strikes all we can do is mourn the departed soul and wish that it rest s in eternal peace. Unfortunately, death isn&amp;rsquo;t selective about who should go and who should remain on earth. Over the past few years, we have lost some of the greatest men and women who brought us unforgettable memories. 2017 hasn&amp;rsquo;t been any different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Much Does Dr. Oz Make? Net Worths Of Famous TV Doctors</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/tv-doctors-net-worth/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 20:59:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/tv-doctors-net-worth/</guid>
      <description>It takes a lot of hard work and training to become a doctor. But to become a doctor with your own television show? Now that&amp;rsquo;s tough. Thankfully, our favorite medical media personalities seem to earn back what they put into their programs (and then some)! Ever wondered what Dr. Phil earns in a year, or the net worth of hunky former Bachelor contestant Travis Stork? We&amp;rsquo;ve got the dirt!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ridiculous Celebrity Impulse Buys That Will Blow Your Socks Off</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/ridiculous-celebrity-impulse-buys/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 02:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/ridiculous-celebrity-impulse-buys/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve all impulsively bought that pack of gum while waiting in line at the supermarket. But imagine if you had millions of dollars burning in your pocket. What would you spend it on? If celebrities are any example, it&amp;rsquo;d probably be something pretty ridiculous. From pet cobras to blinged-out bathtubs, here are some of the most extravagant celebrity impulse buys on record.
And One $1,700 Plane Ticket For My Hat, Please Wikipedia</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Famous Celebs Who Are Frugal And Clip Coupons Just Like You</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/famous-celebs-frugal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/famous-celebs-frugal/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s no shame in pinching a few pennies, even if you are able to live rather lavishly. Lifestyles of the rich and the famous may make it seem like money isn&amp;rsquo;t an option, but some celebrities still prefer to spend frugally. These celebs actually use coupons to save some hard-earned cash, and you will be shocked by some of the stars that prefer to get a good deal!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>