<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Science on Brainsation</title>
    <link>http://st.brainsation.com/tags/science/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Science on Brainsation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 19:41:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://st.brainsation.com/tags/science/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Kilauea Prompts Red Air Alert in Hawaii - This is NOT Good</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/kilauea-prompts-red-air-alert-in-hawaii-this-is-not-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 19:41:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/kilauea-prompts-red-air-alert-in-hawaii-this-is-not-good/</guid>
      <description>Hawaii, ‘The Big Island’, is experiencing the unfolding of a hellish tragedy. Mt. Kilauea began erupting on May 3 and since then the southeastern area of the island has been ripped asunder by 21 fissures scarring the jungle paradise, while tremors continue to leave residents feeling the ground beneath their feet is far from stable. Seismologists are now warning that the Kilauea volcano may be getting ready for a major eruption, reports CNN.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guess Whose Beds are Cleaner Than Humans&#39;?</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/guess-whose-beds-are-cleaner-than-humans/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 18:24:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/guess-whose-beds-are-cleaner-than-humans/</guid>
      <description>It could be termed ‘The Rise of the Bedroom of the Apes’. Researchers from North Carolina State University have found that the beds of chimpanzees are cleaner than those of humans, reports The Telegraph.
Pexels The study was born out of a curiosity over the cleanliness of human beds compared to our closest genetic relatives. &amp;ldquo;We know that human homes are effectively their own ecosystems, and human beds often contain a subset of the taxa - or types - of organisms found in the home,” said Megan Thoemmes, who led the research in Tanzania.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multiverse Dark Matter Findings Have Scientists Looking for New Law of Physics</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/multiverse-dark-matter-findings-have-scientists-looking-for-new-law-of-physics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 16:53:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/multiverse-dark-matter-findings-have-scientists-looking-for-new-law-of-physics/</guid>
      <description>The precise setting of the variables that went in to making our universe the way it is are beyond belief. Just a smidgen change here and there and the constitution of the cosmos could change and possibly make life extinct.
Pixnio Take that fragility of this cosmic stasis and try to replicate it in a parallel universe the balance becomes even harder to achieve. Thanks to a pair of research papers that have been published in the &amp;lsquo;Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society&amp;rsquo;, it appears that one variable could be increased on hundreds of magnitudes in a parallell universe and it would not deter the formation of life-giving planets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Explore Body Changes of Schizophrenic Patients</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/researchers-explore-body-changes-of-schizophrenic-patients/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 16:45:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/researchers-explore-body-changes-of-schizophrenic-patients/</guid>
      <description>Amalgamated from the Greek words skhizein and phren, Swiss psychiatrist Eugen Bleuler introduced the word schizophrenie into the psychological lexicon in 1910. The word meant ‘a splitting of the mind’ and was seen as an apt term to describe the deteriorating mental health of those suffering from the diagnosed disease.
Healthncare.info That diagnostic consensus has been the accepted one for decades, but now Toby Pillinger, a Doctor and Clinical Researcher at King&amp;rsquo;s College in London, and a team of colleagues has completed a study that alleges that there are correlations between the disease and physical changes in the body.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scientists: Our Universe is Like... Raisin Bread?</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientists-our-universe-is-like-raisin-bread/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 14:56:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientists-our-universe-is-like-raisin-bread/</guid>
      <description>We have all heard the expression, ‘He/She thinks they are the center of the universe.’ Western Civilization’s infatuation with the cosmos began with the belief that our collective terra firma was the focal point of a geocentric solar system.
MaxPixel It seems a part of human nature to view ourselves at the center of universal existence but are we the center of the cosmos? Is there even a true center? Live Science reports that, based on the majority consensus of astrophysicists, there is no actual center of the universe because our cosmic reality is ever-expanding, pushing all celestial bodies further apart as it grows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>After Biohacker&#39;s Sudden Death, Followers are Wondering, &#34;What&#39;s Next?&#34;</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/after-biohackers-sudden-death-followers-are-wondering-whats-next/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 21:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/after-biohackers-sudden-death-followers-are-wondering-whats-next/</guid>
      <description>Law enforcement officials were called to a spa in Washington, D.C. on May 6. Once they arrived on scene they discovered the body of 28-year-old Ascendance Biomedical founder Aaron Traywick in a flotation therapy tank, reports Independent. Traywick gained recent notoriety when he injected himself with an untested herpes drug while in front of an audience. Traywick and his company advocated for biohacking, a broad term applied to methods of treating disease or overall health without the aid of pharmaceutical products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NASA Just Took 3D Printing to Whole New Level with Rocket Engine</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/nasa-just-took-3d-printing-to-whole-new-level-with-rocket-engine/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 19:57:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/nasa-just-took-3d-printing-to-whole-new-level-with-rocket-engine/</guid>
      <description>When 3D printing first appeared on the scene it was said by many scientists and economists that the process would spur a resurgence in ‘cottage industry’ entrepreneurship. While that prophecy has for the most part proven to be true, 3D printing has also been used by the ‘big boys’ to improve their operations. Take NASA for example. Popular Mechanics (PM) writes that the nation’s space agency has used a 3D printer to successfully produce a combustion chamber for a rocket engine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tired of Sitting in Traffic? Elon Musk Has a Solution &amp; It&#39;s a Beauty</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/tired-of-sitting-in-traffic-elon-musk-has-a-solution-its-a-beauty/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 19:35:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/tired-of-sitting-in-traffic-elon-musk-has-a-solution-its-a-beauty/</guid>
      <description>Frustrated by his daily commute, Tesla and Space-X CEO Elon Musk once vowed that he would dig a tunnel beneath Los Angeles and bypass the bumper-to-bumper traffic.
Traffic is driving me nuts. Am going to build a tunnel boring machine and just start digging...
&amp;mdash; Elon Musk (@elonmusk) December 17, 2016  Now, Musk is just months away from offering commuters the first maiden voyage of his subterranean shuttle system, writes the Los Angeles Times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Houston Company Creates Underwater &#34;Transformer&#34; - With a Submarine Instead of a Car</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/houston-company-creates-underwater-transformer-with-a-submarine-instead-of-a-car/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 17:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/houston-company-creates-underwater-transformer-with-a-submarine-instead-of-a-car/</guid>
      <description>A partnership between the U.S. Department of Defense and members of corporate oil is looking to make Mattel’s ‘Transformers’ a reality.
SubSeaWorldNews According to Live Science, DOD contractor Houston Mechatronics is a company founded by a former NASA robot engineer who is looking to design the first ever transforming submersible robot that will have both civilian and military applications.
SubSeaWorldNews On May 1, Houston Mechatronics announced that it had completed the hardest part of what will be called ‘Aquanaut’, a unmanned underwater vehicle (UUV) and remotely operated vehicle (ROV) weighing just over 2,000 lbs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand Farmer Wakes Up to 200 Yd Wide Sink Hole</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/new-zealand-farmer-wakes-up-to-200-yd-wide-sink-hole/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 23:54:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/new-zealand-farmer-wakes-up-to-200-yd-wide-sink-hole/</guid>
      <description>The Earth appears to be going through some growing pains. In the news recently was the report of the massive fissure that appeared overnight in Kenya on March 18 and has been labeled the &amp;lsquo;Grand Kenyan&amp;rsquo;. At more than fifty feet deep and 65 feet wide, the fissure rungs for hundreds of yards and scientists believe it is a sign that the Dark Continent is succumbing to tectonic forces that are ripping the eastern half of the land mass apart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scientists in Lab Gain New Insight into How HIV Virus Works</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientists-in-lab-gain-new-insight-into-how-hiv-virus-works/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 23:42:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientists-in-lab-gain-new-insight-into-how-hiv-virus-works/</guid>
      <description>It looks like something out of a sci-fi horror movie. A glowing green alien life form closes in on its prey and shoots out green blasts of energy at its victim. The alien closes in and infects his adversary with a virus that he/she will spread to others. The incident detailed above occurred and was recorded by pathologists at the Institut Cochin in Paris who were studying the actual method and playing out of an HIV viral cell attacking a healthy cell in the human body.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experts Reveal What&#39;s Next for Kilauea - And It&#39;s NOT Good</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/experts-reveal-whats-next-for-kilauea-and-its-not-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 22:06:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/experts-reveal-whats-next-for-kilauea-and-its-not-good/</guid>
      <description>A series of unfolding events in and around Hawaii’s Kilauea volcano has the potential to rain trouble down on the immediate area… literally. Before it started leaking lava last week, the lava lake in the crater atop Kilauea had ballooned like a Jiffy Pop bag due to the tremendous pressure from an expanding pool of magma and accompanying volcanic gas.
Wiki Commons Earthquakes triggered the “popping” of this balloon, sending lava slowly cascading down the east side of the mountain and causing numerous pockets of vapor to shoot out of the ground.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Woman&#39;s Runny Nose Turns Out to Be Something Much More Serious</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/womans-runny-nose-turns-out-to-be-something-much-more-serious/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 18:57:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/womans-runny-nose-turns-out-to-be-something-much-more-serious/</guid>
      <description>Kendra Jackson of Omaha, Nebraska counted herself lucky in 2013 when she walked away from a car accident with a minor head injury resulting from her head hitting the dashboard of the car she was in. The bruising slowly went away. The pain receded as well&amp;hellip;at least temporarily.
Week Facts Years after her accident Jackson began to be plagued with debilitating headaches, dizziness, sleeplessness and a constant runny nose. Her primary care physician diagnosed her symptoms as results of severe allergies that were causing sinus infections.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scientist: $180 Kit Can Help Criminals Avoid Prosecution</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientist-180-kit-can-help-criminals-avoid-prosecution/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 18:21:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientist-180-kit-can-help-criminals-avoid-prosecution/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been over a century since the police started using fingerprint evidence to solve crimes. As a work around, criminals simply started wearing gloves or wiping down whatever they touched at a crime scene. DNA is much more pervasive. A hair at a crime scene or dead skin under a victim&amp;rsquo;s fingernails could be matched to a criminal with DNA analysis, and there was nothing the bad guys could do about it, until now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chile&#39;s Getting a New Telescope -- And It&#39;s a Monster</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/chiles-getting-a-new-telescope-and-its-a-monster/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 19:01:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/chiles-getting-a-new-telescope-and-its-a-monster/</guid>
      <description>The mountains of Chile are home to some of the most advanced astronomical equipment in the world today, and it looks like they&amp;rsquo;re about to get a new addition. Work has begun on the erection of what promises to be the world&amp;rsquo;s largest optical reflecting telescope in the world. Perched atop the nearly 10,000 foot high Cerro Armazones in Chile, the Extremely Large Telescope (ELT) is the brainchild of the European Southern Observatory and is expected to be up and running in 2024.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Create First Synthetic Embryos in Lab - Here&#39;s What it Means for Humans</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientists-create-first-synthetic-embryos-in-lab-heres-what-it-means-for-humans/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 13:17:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientists-create-first-synthetic-embryos-in-lab-heres-what-it-means-for-humans/</guid>
      <description>It is possible that in the near future infertile women will have access to proto-embryos that will go on to develop into viable human offspring.
IFLScience.com IFL Science writes that scientists from Maastricht University and the Hubrecht Institute in the Netherlands have successfully used the stem cells of mice to initiate the process of pregnancy in a mouse womb. Using bundles of the stem cells, the researchers created an embryo in a dish and when placed in a womb, it triggered a biochemical reaction that began to prepare the womb for pregnancy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Criminal Gangs Use High Tech to Fight the FBI</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/criminal-gangs-use-high-tech-to-fight-the-fbi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 02:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/criminal-gangs-use-high-tech-to-fight-the-fbi/</guid>
      <description>Last winter at an undisclosed town in the United States, officials with the Federal Bureau of Investigation&amp;rsquo;s hostage rescue unit moved in to begin an extraction operation. Agents fanned out around the scene, some in obvious positions while others sat or lay concealed in other spots.
Digital Addicts Blog Not long after arriving on scene and staging personnel, the FBI team was harassed by a swarm of drones that made &amp;ldquo;high-speed, low passes at agents in the observation post&amp;rdquo; in an attempt to flush them out and prevent the Bureau from having eyes on the scene.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is This Planet the Closest Thing to an Earthlike Planet?  Scientists Think It Is</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/is-this-planet-the-closest-thing-to-an-earthlike-planet-scientists-think-it-is/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 23:42:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/is-this-planet-the-closest-thing-to-an-earthlike-planet-scientists-think-it-is/</guid>
      <description>Astronomers and other scientists focused on finding a habitable &amp;lsquo;earth-like&amp;rsquo; exoplanet in the cosmos have many requirements that have to be met before they seriously zero in on a candidate. One of these requirements is that the planet have a sizable iron core that would lend itself to the creation and maintenance of a magnetosphere.
NASA In February of 2017, European astronomers went public with the news that they had discovered a seven-planet orbiting the nearby star TRAPPIST-1, a celestial object located 39.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sir Richard Branson&#39;s Bringing the Space Age to the Desert in Dubai</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/sir-richard-bransons-bringing-the-space-age-to-the-desert-in-dubai/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 23:13:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/sir-richard-bransons-bringing-the-space-age-to-the-desert-in-dubai/</guid>
      <description>The future of overland cargo shipment and human travel is taking shape in the deserts of Dubai.
The Daily Mail writes that billionaire entrepreneur Richard Branson, founder and CEO of Virgin, is getting behind the development of what is called hyperloop technology.
Daily Mail Hyperloop uses a pod and tube system in which the pods are levitated and accelerated through the tubal system through electromagnetism, reaching speeds of up to 760mph.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NASA Bringing Back Supersonic Air Travel - With No Sonic Boom</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/nasa-bringing-back-supersonic-air-travel-with-no-sonic-boom/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 22:02:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/nasa-bringing-back-supersonic-air-travel-with-no-sonic-boom/</guid>
      <description>Supersonic commercial flights have been hiatus since 2003, after the British-French Concorde went belly up to due to expensive operations and prohibitive passenger fares. While aeronautic enthusiasts mourned the end of such flights, those living in the path of the incoming and outgoing airplanes felt relief that the loud, bone rattling sonic booms of the Concorde would no longer be heard.
Wikimedia Commons If NASA has its way, though, supersonic flights will make a comeback soon, but will do so much more quietly, reports Fox News.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Study Love Lives of Senior Citizens - Here are the Results</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/researchers-study-love-lives-of-senior-citizens-here-are-the-results/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 21:46:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/researchers-study-love-lives-of-senior-citizens-here-are-the-results/</guid>
      <description>Can the golden years in life still be a time of sexual desire and intimacy? This is the question asked by scientists out of Michigan. According to a report from the University of Michigan referenced by The Guardian, there is a sizeable chunk of seniors that are still sexually active and a much larger cadre of elders who say that sex is important in all stages of life.
Pixabay The Michigan research found that 40% of those surveyed between the ages of 65 and 80 were sexually active.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Quantum Anomaly Changes What We Know About Reality</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/a-quantum-anomaly-changes-what-we-know-about-reality/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 19:33:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/a-quantum-anomaly-changes-what-we-know-about-reality/</guid>
      <description>There are some in the scientific community who believe that we are on the cusp of a fundamental shift in the perceived reality, or paradigm, experienced by humanity, or at least those populations exposed to current scientific breakthroughs.
Pixabay Scientific American reports that as researchers delve deeper into quantum mechanics, unlocking the mysteries it holds, there is a growing cognitive shift in how ‘reality’ is perceived. The shift, if it occurs, will involve humanity’s departure from the non-contextuality of our sensory observations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Look to Medieval Period for Proof of Planet 9</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/researchers-look-to-medieval-period-for-proof-of-planet-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 19:17:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/researchers-look-to-medieval-period-for-proof-of-planet-9/</guid>
      <description>There are some astronomers who have theorized that in the depths of our solar system, far beyond the orbit of Neptune, there is a large cold planet that has evaded discovery by modern researchers. ‘Planet Nine’, as it has been dubbed, may have been knowingly or unknowingly revealed by our medieval ancestors.
NASA Fox News writes that two researchers from Queen&amp;rsquo;s University Belfast in Northern Ireland are searching through old scrolls and tapestries from the Medieval era, like the famous Bayeux Tapestry that showed the 1066 AD appearance of Haley’s Comet, looking for clues about Planet Nine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NY Airport Robot Accused of Sexual Harrassment</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/ny-airport-robot-accused-of-sexual-harrassment/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 13:37:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/ny-airport-robot-accused-of-sexual-harrassment/</guid>
      <description>NY Post[/caption] New York’s LaGuardia Airport, like most major airline hubs, have their entrances swarmed by taxis looking to scoop up passengers before their competitors. The cutthroat business has resulted in the cabs ignoring parking protocols and idling areas. To combat this, LaGuardia has used security officers on foot to shoo away the cabbies, but that ended three months ago when the airport deployed the Knightscope K5 robot. It was hoped that the robot would be able to cover more ground in a more effective manner than its human predecessor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here are the Warning Signs Super Volcanos Give Before They Blow</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/here-are-the-warning-signs-super-volcanos-give-before-they-blow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 16:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/here-are-the-warning-signs-super-volcanos-give-before-they-blow/</guid>
      <description>Rumblings, geyser eruptions and growing magma chambers at Yellowstone National Park in Wyoming have been unnerving citizens in and around the area lately, causing many to wonder if the super volcano underneath the park is about to erupt.
MaxPixel.net[/caption] A new study just release by academics from Illinois should help allay those fears. A paper authored by geologist Patricia Gregg and PhD student, Haley Cabaniss, both of the University of Illinois, is claiming that any imminent large-scale eruption would be proceeded by hundreds if not thousands of years of increased tectonic activity, a growing magma chamber and geological ‘uplift’ measured in meters and not inches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Details Behind NASA&#39;s Latest Mission to Mars</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-details-behind-nasas-latest-mission-to-mars/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 14:43:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-details-behind-nasas-latest-mission-to-mars/</guid>
      <description>NASA - Jet Propulsion Laboratory[/caption] For all of its desolate alien façade, Mars has enough similarities to Earth to continually intrigue scientists. On May 5, NASA’s Jet Propulsion Laboratory will be launching another probe to the Red Planet but this one will not have the superficial focus of prior Mars Rovers, reports Science News. Skin Deep
Astronomists and scientists look upon Mars as the closest planetary copy of Earth that is within the ‘easy’ grasp of exploratory satellites and probes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious Eye in Appears in Sky Over the Netherlands</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/mysterious-eye-in-appears-in-sky-over-the-netherlands/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 21:44:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/mysterious-eye-in-appears-in-sky-over-the-netherlands/</guid>
      <description>The sky above the Netherlands on April 22 was the typical cloudy setting that natives are used to around this time of year. One thing that was not typical was an unusual cloud formation that had people offering various interpretations of what was being seen. One Eye Open The UK’s Express reports that on the aforementioned date a “monstrous eye in the sky” made from clouds appeared in the heavens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things Continue to Heat Up Under Yellowstone National Park</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/things-continue-to-heat-up-under-yellowstone-national-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 20:03:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/things-continue-to-heat-up-under-yellowstone-national-park/</guid>
      <description>The signs that something is brewing beneath the earth at Wyoming’s Yellowstone National Park are increasing. Seismic events have been increasingly common, scientists have discovered that a magma bloom under the soil is larger than expected and much closer to the surface than previously thought and the venting of sulfur dioxide have been more and more common and lethal for indigenous fauna in the area. The Independent now reports that another sign has popped up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breakthrough Brain Technology Could Restore Sight to the Blind</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/breakthrough-brain-technology-could-restore-sight-to-the-blind/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 19:56:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/breakthrough-brain-technology-could-restore-sight-to-the-blind/</guid>
      <description>It seems that every single day scientists make a breakthrough that seems impossible. For people who have to deal with the loss of a sense, such as sight, hearing, or touch, this recent breakthrough may prove to be especially exciting.
Brain in Human[/caption] The Independent reports that neurologists have made a tremendous advance in undoing the loss of senses in some people. Using what has become referred to as a ‘holographic brain modulator’, scientists have crafted for themselves the ability to target sensory receptors in the body with encoded hologram stimuli that reportedly mimics that of real external forces like light and the contact of objects on someone’s skin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent US Solar Eclipse Set Off Atmospheric Wave Measured Around the Globe</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/recent-us-solar-eclipse-set-off-atmospheric-wave-measured-around-the-globe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 19:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/recent-us-solar-eclipse-set-off-atmospheric-wave-measured-around-the-globe/</guid>
      <description>Flickr[/caption] Did you see the bug total solar eclipse last August? Did you feel it? If not, don’t fret, because while the eclipse did indeed case a palpable sensation, it did so at around 180 miles above the Earth’s surface. On August 21, 2017 many Americans and Canadians lifted their protected eyes to the heavens to take in a rare total solar eclipse. For an average of two minutes, midday turned a bit darker in spots and downright nighttime in others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harvard Scientists Hope This Extinct Animal Can Make a &#39;Mammoth&#39; Comeback</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/harvard-scientists-hope-this-extinct-animal-can-make-a-mammoth-comeback/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 18:13:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/harvard-scientists-hope-this-extinct-animal-can-make-a-mammoth-comeback/</guid>
      <description>Wikimedia Commons[/caption] The Flintstones&amp;rsquo; dishwasher is one step closer to being resurrected. Move over Maytag! Make way for the Woolly Mammoth! C/Net reports now that scientists have successfully duplicated 44 mammoth genes, they are now hoping to grow a mammoth-hybrid in an artificial womb. The large hairy elephant walked the earth as early as 2.5 million years ago before going extinct around 3rd millennium B.C. A team of researchers at Harvard University, headed up by well-known geneticist Professor George Church, participated in the Fourth International Vatican Conference in Vatican City on April 27.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Common Virus Linked to 7 Autoimmune Diseases</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/common-virus-linked-to-7-autoimmune-diseases/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 16:42:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/common-virus-linked-to-7-autoimmune-diseases/</guid>
      <description>Cells with Epstein Barr Virus | Wikimedia Commons[/caption] In a stunning bit of news, the Cincinnati Children’s Hospital has announced that a team of its researchers have concluded that the injection at least some forms of viral DNA into the human lymphatic system may be causing the onset of seven debilitating diseases. IFLScience writes that a study of patients who received shots of the Epstein-Barr Virus (EBV) as part of a vaccination process against mononucleosis (mono) had increased chances of developing autoimmune diseases such as lupus, multiple sclerosis, rheumatoid arthritis, juvenile idiopathic arthritis, inflammatory bowel disease, celiac disease, and type 1 diabetes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crime Researcher Releases Shocking Fact About Number of Serial Killers in US</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/crime-researcher-releases-shocking-fact-about-number-of-serial-killers-in-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 16:01:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/crime-researcher-releases-shocking-fact-about-number-of-serial-killers-in-us/</guid>
      <description>Vox[/caption] “The taste of death that lives within He loves it when he Tastes their final breath Stalking gives him pleasure Killing is the final act He takes no pity With his lust for death.” &amp;mdash;-’Psycho Man’, Ozzy Osbourne The recent arrest of the notorious Golden State Killer, a man now identified as 72-year-old Joseph James DeAngelo Jr, caused the resurfacing of our society’s recurrent predations by serial killers. DeAngelo operated for over a decade, from the 1970s to the 1980s, terrorizing parts of California with his ten murders and 46 known rapes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Underwater Robot Confirms Scientists Greatest Fears in Gulf of Oman</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/underwater-robot-confirms-scientists-greatest-fears-in-gulf-of-oman/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 15:34:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/underwater-robot-confirms-scientists-greatest-fears-in-gulf-of-oman/</guid>
      <description>Flickr | Gulf of Oman | by Francisco Anzola[/caption] It seems like every day we&amp;rsquo;re learning something new about the oceans. Sometimes we discover new sea life or new ways that animals communicate with each other under water, other times, however, we come across disturbing features like this one&amp;hellip; Recently, robots exploring the depths of the Gulf of Oman have discovered a &amp;ldquo;dead zone&amp;rdquo; the size of Scotland! From IFLScience: “Our research shows that the situation is actually worse than feared – and that the area of dead zone is vast and growing,” said Dr Bastien Queste, who led the research published this week in Geophysical Research Letter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk Just Fired His Robots and Hired Humans to Take Their Places</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/elon-musk-just-fired-his-robots-and-hired-humans-to-take-their-places/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 20:50:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/elon-musk-just-fired-his-robots-and-hired-humans-to-take-their-places/</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk, the founder and current CEO of Tesla, Inc., has been sleeping on a couch at his company’s Fremont, California plant lately following a slowdown in production that has caught the attention of the public in the last few weeks.
Flickr - pestoverde[/caption] Inconvenient Conveyors…And Automation The Freemont plant is centered around the production of the Tesla Model 3 electric car. When the model was announced, Musk told the public that it would run consumers $35,000, a very reasonable price, to purchase the car and that the California facility would pump out 5,000 vehicles a week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experts at University of Texas Launch Controversial Program Aimed at Men</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/experts-at-university-of-texas-launch-controversial-program-aimed-at-men/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 17:24:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/experts-at-university-of-texas-launch-controversial-program-aimed-at-men/</guid>
      <description>Turn on any TV show or watch any commercial and what you will most likely see are scenes with characters consisting of strong, smart women and dopey and weak men. Those of you with children in high school or college have most likely heard of Academia’s crusade against ‘toxic masculinity’.

Now, one Texas university is attempting to slap a medical motivation behind dangerous masculinity, reports PJ Media.

Tyranny of the Technocrats At the University of Texas at Austin, the Counseling and Mental Health Center has initiated a campaign to tell men that their traits of masculinity are barriers to a balanced mental health.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Yellowstone About to Blow? Recent Geyser Eruptions Have Some People Worried</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/is-yellowstone-about-to-blow-recent-geyser-eruptions-have-some-people-worried/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 15:58:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/is-yellowstone-about-to-blow-recent-geyser-eruptions-have-some-people-worried/</guid>
      <description>Things have been heating up in Yellowstone Park lately, geologically speaking, and scientists have been scratching their heads trying to figure out why. The flurry of activity revolves around the Steamboat Geyser which has erupted 3 times in recent weeks.

The infamous geyser spouted on March 15, April 19, and again on Friday April 27. Steamboat is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest geyser and sits at the crown of the Yellowstone caldera volcanic crater.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia’s ‘Floating Chernobyl’ Alarms Officials</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/russias-floating-chernobyl-alarms-officials/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 15:41:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/russias-floating-chernobyl-alarms-officials/</guid>
      <description>The nuclear age has taken to the high seas. This statement has nothing to do with nuclear-powered submarines, aircraft carriers or ice-breaking naval vessels. The ground-breaking, or rather ground-leaving, event involves nuclear reactors perched atop floating barges and hauled out to sea.

‘Nuclear Titanic’ On April 28, a Russian planned and constructed nuclear facility was successfully tugged from its berthing area in the historic naval port of St. Petersburg to Murmansk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Research Claims to Solve JFK Assassination Theories, But Does It?</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/new-research-claims-to-solve-jfk-assassination-theories-but-does-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 17:56:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/new-research-claims-to-solve-jfk-assassination-theories-but-does-it/</guid>
      <description>The assassination of President John F. Kennedy took place over 50 years ago in Dallas, Texas, yet conspiracy theories still abound as to what happened on that fateful November day. Now, thanks to advancements in technology and the ability to digitally analyze audio and video footage of the shooting and its aftermath, one research firm thinks they&amp;rsquo;ve solved a major part of the puzzle.

From IFLScience.com According to official reports, Lee Harvey Oswald was the prime (and only) suspect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Could You Follow This Flapper Diet From 100 Years Ago?</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/could-you-follow-this-flapper-diet-from-100-years-ago/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 20:31:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/could-you-follow-this-flapper-diet-from-100-years-ago/</guid>
      <description>In the second decade of the 20th Century, American society was steeped in the opulence and hedonism of the ‘Roaring 20s’. The Great War was over and economic progress had returned big time to the United States. The zeitgeist was the closest Americans came to the French joie de vivre.

According to some sociologists, the generation during that time (the Crisis stage) was the artist group. The 1920s gave birth to bohemians and flappers, so it would indeed appear that the authors were right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flying Drone Taxi Lifts Off in Oregon - Are You Ready?</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/flying-drone-taxi-lifts-off-in-oregon-are-you-ready/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 19:52:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/flying-drone-taxi-lifts-off-in-oregon-are-you-ready/</guid>
      <description>All throughout the 20th century, one of the signature features of the future that Americans looked forward to was the possibility of flying cars. Getting in your car and, just like George Jetson, blasting off to work and then home again. Well, it looks like the future is not that far off.

The world may be on the cusp of the skies being filled with flying taxis. The European company, Airbus, who produces civilian and military aircraft, has released video of tests of its ‘Vahana’ vertical takeoff and landing (VTOL) drone taxi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Texas Scientist Solves Two Ansel Adams Mysteries</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/texas-scientist-solves-two-ansel-adams-mysteries/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 17:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/texas-scientist-solves-two-ansel-adams-mysteries/</guid>
      <description>Donald Olson is an amateur sleuth, but the mysteries he solves don&amp;rsquo;t put killers behind bars or reveal the identities of murderers in some sort of overly dramatic third act. No, Olson tackles the mysteries that artists and great figures in history have left for the rest of us to figure out.

The Art Detective From Atlas Obscura: An astrophysicist and forensic astronomer, Olson uses quantitative methods to answer questions raised by artwork, literature, and historical accounts—not the heady ones, but the basic, surprisingly slippery who, what, when, and where.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yes, There Used to Be Giant Sloths and Humans Used to Hunt Them</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/yes-there-used-to-be-giant-sloths-and-humans-used-to-hunt-them/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 20:37:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/yes-there-used-to-be-giant-sloths-and-humans-used-to-hunt-them/</guid>
      <description>Today, people tend to think of sloths as cute harmless creatures. Their images are all over the internet and videos of them on YouTube garner thousands &amp;ndash; and even millions of views. Their prehistoric ancestors, however, were a little different.

Over 10,000 years ago in what is now the New Mexico White Sands National Monument at least one pre-historic hunter followed the trail of a large beast. At some point, the hunter caught up to the animal causing the beast to rear up on its hind legs in an attempt to scare away the hunter or, if that failed, defend itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archaeologists in Peru Make Gruesome Discovery</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/archaeologists-in-peru/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 16:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/archaeologists-in-peru/</guid>
      <description>In the waning days of its civilization, a gathering of Chimú priests oversaw a religious ritual they hoped would stem the endless days of rain and the rising sea levels that threatened their 15th Century society located along the Pacific Ocean in modern day Peru.

Prior rituals involving the sacrifice of adults in order to appease the gods had failed. Desperate times called for desperate measures. An Unexpected Recourse For five years an interdisciplinary team, funded by National Geographic, headed up by Gabriel Prieto of the Universidad Nacional de Trujillo and John Verano of Tulane University have been slowly peeling back the layers of a mass grave located in the Chimú town of Huanchaquito-Las Llamas, but now known as the Peruvian district of Huanchaco.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Re-Examined Museum Piece Discovered to Be Older Than the Pyramids</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/re-examined-museum-piece-discovered-to-be-older-than-the-pyramids/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 15:29:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/re-examined-museum-piece-discovered-to-be-older-than-the-pyramids/</guid>
      <description>The Pleistocene Epoch is the term scientists use to describe the last ice age that ended about 11,700 years ago. It was at about this time, almost 12,000 years ago that a group of people in Siberia (the land where the ice age never really ended), carved a tree into a human like wooden idol almost 5 meters long.

Fast forward to 1894, when gold prospectors discovered the idol while digging up a peat bog near the Russian city Yekaterinburg.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japanese Farmers Turn to Wolf-Like Creature for Protection</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/japanese-farmers-turn-to-wolf-like-creature-for-protection/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 20:51:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/japanese-farmers-turn-to-wolf-like-creature-for-protection/</guid>
      <description>It looks and sounds like something out of a sci-fi horror flick. With eyes that glow a menacing red, white fangs and inhuman howls, a new creature is stalking the rice paddies and agricultural fields of Japan.

It is called the Super Monster Wolf and stands 20 inches tall and is around 25 ½ inches long. Oh and it costs about $4,800 to buy. The creature is a solar powered robot wolf designed to scare away scavengers and other animals from farms and rice paddies throughout Japan, writes The Sun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robot Solves Popular Puzzle in Less than a Second [Video]</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/robot-solves-popular-puzzle-in-less-than-a-second-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 20:08:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/robot-solves-popular-puzzle-in-less-than-a-second-video/</guid>
      <description>Remember the Rubik’s Cube? Those old enough to can probably appreciate this author’s level of frustration with the 3D puzzle. My frustration got to the point that I even peeled off (poorly) the stickers on the segments so I could pretend I successfully finished it.

Not my proudest moment. I was certainly nowhere close to current Guinness World Records holder Patrick Ponce from the USA, who completed a 3x3x3 cube in just 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York &amp; The Great Thunder Snow Blizzard of 2018</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/new-york-the-great-thunder-snow-blizzard-of-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 19:54:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/new-york-the-great-thunder-snow-blizzard-of-2018/</guid>
      <description>The Northeast has definitely experienced some intense weather this spring and a few weeks ago, a massive storm grew miles above the Big Apple. The energy it created gave birth to thunder storms during a major snow event.

On March 7, first New York City and then northern New Jersey, experienced thunder snow during a strong coastal front. In the process billions of ice crystals high up in the atmosphere moving at a frenetic pace due to the winds of the storm, began charging each other with electrical energy This rapid movement charges an area of the atmosphere, which in turn draws more ice crystals to it like a magnet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s Why California Residents Might Want to Start Buying Bottled Water</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/heres-why-california-residents-might-want-to-start-buying-bottled-water/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 18:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/heres-why-california-residents-might-want-to-start-buying-bottled-water/</guid>
      <description>Day-by-day, California is getting closer to running out of drinking water. In the wealthiest nation on Earth, it is inconceivable that this should be happening.
Now the Dems of Cali have to drink sewage because they are totally incompetent. California to add recycled sewer water to the state reservoirs https://t.co/SNWTVx3jFA #FoxNews
&amp;mdash; Martin a Patriot (@pfiec) March 8, 2018  Adversity being the mother of invention, the SFGate reports that San Diego is hoping its’ experiment in recycled water will trickle throughout the Golden State.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Known Story of the Deaf Men Who Helped NASA Get Into Space</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/little-known-story-of-the-deaf-men-who-helped-nasa-get-into-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 17:25:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/little-known-story-of-the-deaf-men-who-helped-nasa-get-into-space/</guid>
      <description>The story of the American space program and the organized effort it took to launch astronauts into space and, eventually, onto the moon is a remarkable tale of people from all walks of life coming together to achieve a great mission.

The contribution of several remarkable women was portrayed in the recent hit movie Hidden Figures, and now Discover Magazine has the account of a group of men who, up until now, have been unheard of in the tale of the exploration of space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marine Biologists CT Scan an Entire Whale - Here&#39;s What They Found</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/marine-biologists-ct-scan-an-entire-whale-heres-what-they-found/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 16:51:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/marine-biologists-ct-scan-an-entire-whale-heres-what-they-found/</guid>
      <description>In a bid to help biologists better understand the aquatic environs of whales and how humans impact them, researchers from San Diego State University (SDSU) have completed a crucial examination of one ocean species.

Discover Magazine writes that the results “will help researchers better protect these massive mammals of the sea.” Can You Hear Me Now? Thanks to a large computed tomography (CT) machine used to scan solid-fuel rocket engines, SDSU scientists were able to analyze the interior of a deceased 11-foot young minke whale found beached years before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What the Heck Just Happened at Yellowstone?</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/yellowstone-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 15:33:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/yellowstone-video/</guid>
      <description>Things got a bit bizarre on the evening of April 21 at one of the thermal vents belonging to the increasingly active Yellowstone caldera. A video of the incidents has been posted to YouTube but result in more questions than answers.
Has Yellowstone volcano STARTED erupting? Shock claims as ‘explosion’ spotted on live feed https://t.co/VXIxDwl9dq pic.twitter.com/LRQQzr0TDf
&amp;mdash; encyclopedic (@encyclopedicuk) April 25, 2018  It Starts With a Body… In the video posted by YouTuber Kat Martin, the vent can be seen in the dark of night, spewing steam and heat into the cold Wyoming air.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shadow Security System for Seniors - More Effective Than Guard Dogs?</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/shadow-security-system-for-seniors-more-effective-than-guard-dogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 14:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/shadow-security-system-for-seniors-more-effective-than-guard-dogs/</guid>
      <description>In this day and age of escalating crime, it is understandable that people living alone, especially women, feel a bit unsecure. Those suffering from this condition can and usually get a dog or alarm system, but what about those who live in pet-free apartments or townhouses?

A solution may be in the offering from Leopalace21 Corp, a Japanese firm that designed a program to ward off possible trespassers or thieves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NASA Probe&#39;s Up Close Pictures of Jupiter</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/nasa-probes-up-close-pictures-of-jupiter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 21:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/nasa-probes-up-close-pictures-of-jupiter/</guid>
      <description>The images are breathtaking. It is as if a painter with tremendous creativity and a sense for wonderous patterns had composed them.
You&amp;#39;ve just crossed over into the Twilight Zone. This image captures the swirling cloud formations in #Jupiter’s terminator – the region where day meets night. https://t.co/BrHKWPVjtS pic.twitter.com/En9mwkcEz7
&amp;mdash; NASA&amp;#39;s Juno Mission (@NASAJuno) March 1, 2018  NASA’s Juno craft has recently taken some updated pictures of Jupiter’s interior and the results are extraordinary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Power of Breathing to Calm Your Brain</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-power-of-breathing-to-calm-your-brain/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 18:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-power-of-breathing-to-calm-your-brain/</guid>
      <description>For years, humans have relied on breathing as a way to achieve peace of mind. As you know, one of the most basic and effective forms of meditation is to become aware of your breath and follow it, in and out of your body.

Well, it looks like science is confirming all of religion&amp;rsquo;s teachings on the positive effects of breathing. A recent article in Psychology Today talks about a 2016 conducted by neuroscientists from Stanford, UCLA, and St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bezos&#39; Latest Brainstorm: A Walking, Talking Alexa in Every Home</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/bezos-latest-brainstorm-a-walking-talking-alexa-in-every-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 18:46:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/bezos-latest-brainstorm-a-walking-talking-alexa-in-every-home/</guid>
      <description>Like it or not, artificial intelligence is advancing at a phenomenal rate. While some people fear the Pandora&amp;rsquo;s Box that AI will open up and others are, at the very least, leery of the rise of the machine, some people are optimistic and welcoming of the new technology. Jeff Bezos is hoping you fall into the third category.

Here&amp;rsquo;s the story from Bloomberg: The retail and cloud computing giant has embarked on an ambitious, top-secret plan to build a domestic robot, according to people familiar with the plans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Reach Conclusions After 80 Year Long Happiness Study</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientists-reach-conclusions-after-80-year-long-happiness-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 18:41:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientists-reach-conclusions-after-80-year-long-happiness-study/</guid>
      <description>A multi-generational group of researchers have published the results of an 80-year-long study tracking the lives nearly 2,000 Americans. The study looked to answer an eternal question that has had philosophers, theologians and scientists consumed with curiosity: what is the secret to happiness?

Happy Man[/caption] The Company You Keep IFLScience writes that the study was handled by “a team of scientists at Harvard University” that discovered, thanks to evolving medical research and technology, the key to happiness was the development and maintenance of strong relationships with other people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geologist Run Earthquake Simulation in San Francisco, Here are the Results</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/geologist-run-earthquake-simulation-in-san-francisco-here-are-the-results/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 18:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/geologist-run-earthquake-simulation-in-san-francisco-here-are-the-results/</guid>
      <description>California is used to earthquakes. There are small to medium tremors that occur monthly throughout the year. The last major quake to strike California was the shallow 6.9 Loma Prieta earthquake in 1989, often referred to as the ‘World Series Quake’ since it struck during a MLB playoff game. The quake killed 67 people, injured 3,000 and cost $5 billion in damages.
  Before that, in 1906, a vicious 7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Court Hands Down Verdict in &#39;Monkey See, Monkey Selfie&#39; Case</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/court-hands-down-verdict-in-monkey-see-monkey-selfie-case/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 18:03:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/court-hands-down-verdict-in-monkey-see-monkey-selfie-case/</guid>
      <description>It’s not the equivalent of the Scope Monkey Trial of 1925, but another legal case with a primate at the center of it has found its way into American culture. Unlike the Scopes trial, which addressed the weighty subject of biological evolution, this case is a comical farce of a lawsuit over photo selfies.

‘Monkey See Monkey Sue’ The U.S. 9th Circuit Court of Appeals has recently ruled on a 2011 lawsuit filed by the People for the Ethical Treatment of Animals (PETA) over photographs inadvertently taken of an Indonesian crested macaque, named Naruto, by British nature photographer David Slater, reports the Huffington Post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archaeologists Find Rare Roman Statue... in Egypt</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/archaeologists-find-rare-roman-statue-in-egypt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 22:26:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/archaeologists-find-rare-roman-statue-in-egypt/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re an archaeologist, Egypt has got to be the place to go! Not only are they finding Eqyptian artifacts over there, but now they&amp;rsquo;re finding Roman ones, too! From Newsweek:

Archaeologists in Egypt have unearthed the bust of Roman Emperor Marcus Aurelius, who was best known for his philosophical interests. They made the discovery in the Temple of Kom Ombo, where a years-long project is being done to preserve the site from groundwater damage, The Associated Press reports.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tyson Prediction: First Trillionaire Will Make Money in Outer Space</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/tyson-prediction-first-trillionaire-will-make-money-in-outer-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 21:20:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/tyson-prediction-first-trillionaire-will-make-money-in-outer-space/</guid>
      <description>When you think of the wealthy these days, you think of billionaires like Bill Gates, Elon Musk, Warren Buffet, Mark Zuckerberg, Oprah, and Jeff Bezos. While all of these are busy stirring up their fortunes on terra firma, famed astrophysicist Neil deGrasse Tyson believe that space will produce the first trillionaire.

From the Daily Star: “The first trillionaire there will ever be is the person who exploits the natural resources on asteroids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yukon Saloon Serves Up Stomach Churning Cocktail to Guests</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/yukon-saloon-serves-up-stomach-churning-cocktail-to-guests/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 17:50:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/yukon-saloon-serves-up-stomach-churning-cocktail-to-guests/</guid>
      <description>If you are ever in the Canadian Yukon&amp;rsquo;s Dawson City, stop by the Sourdough Saloon for some food and drinks and be sure to experience a peculiar cocktail called the &amp;lsquo;Sourtoe&amp;rsquo;. Nick Griffiths would appreciate the visit.

The Drink Has (Frost)bite Griffiths, a frequent contender in extreme racings, participated this last winter in the Yukon Arctic Ultra. The race is a punishing 300-mile jaunt via foot, dogsled and mountain bikes through inhospitable freezing landscapes, with temperatures getting down to 58 degrees Fahrenheit below zero, making it one of the coldest races in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Man Gets Attacked by Rattlesnake, Bear, &amp; Tiger Shark - And Lives to Tell About It</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/man-gets-attacked-by-rattlesnake-bear-tiger-shark-and-lives-to-tell-about-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 17:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/man-gets-attacked-by-rattlesnake-bear-tiger-shark-and-lives-to-tell-about-it/</guid>
      <description>Beauty is in the eye of the beholder and the same may be said of luck. A twenty-year-old Colorado native named Dylan McWilliams may either be the most unlucky or luckiest man, reports Sky News.

On April 19, while enjoying a two week vacation to Hawaii, McWilliams was on his surfboard in the early morning waters of Shipwreck&amp;rsquo;s Beach, 50 yards off of Poipu. The avid surfer and survival instructor was enjoying a beautiful morning when he suddenly felt something clamp down on one of his submerged legs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Authorities Still Unable to ID Strange Craft in Skies Over Chile</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/authorities-still-unable-to-id-strange-craft-in-skies-over-chile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 16:21:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/authorities-still-unable-to-id-strange-craft-in-skies-over-chile/</guid>
      <description>After two years of trying to determine what it was that was drifting above the clouds off the coast of Chile on November 11 of 2014, that nation&amp;rsquo;s version of our Federal Aviation Administration (FAA), the CEFAA, has recently released nearly ten minutes of footage of an apparent UFO that has left Chilean officials at a loss to explain, reports Huffington Post.

On the date mentioned above, two Chilean naval aviators flying an Airbus Cougar AS-532 helicopter on a routine daytime patrol, spotted what they later described as a white, semi-oval shaped &amp;ldquo;flat, elongated structure that had two thermal spotlights like discharges that did not coincide with the axel of motion&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NASA Just Took a Giant Leap Forward in It&#39;s Mission to Find Habitable Planets</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/nasa-just-took-a-giant-leap-forward-in-its-mission-to-find-habitable-planets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 19:41:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/nasa-just-took-a-giant-leap-forward-in-its-mission-to-find-habitable-planets/</guid>
      <description>Last week a Space X Falcon 9 Rocket took off from Cape Canaveral Air Station in Florida and launched a very special satellite named TESS into Earth&amp;rsquo;s orbit. TESS stands for Transiting Exoplanet Surevey Satellite and its mission is to discover new planets. NASA is very excited about the possibilities.

From Space.com: &amp;ldquo;TESS is going to dramatically increase the number of planets that we have to study,&amp;rdquo; TESS principal investigator George Ricker, of the Massachusetts Institute of Technology, said during a pre-launch briefing Sunday (April 15).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guests at &#39;The Shining&#39; Hotel Accidentally Take Picture of Ghost</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/guests-at-the-shining-hotel-accidentally-take-picture-of-ghost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 17:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/guests-at-the-shining-hotel-accidentally-take-picture-of-ghost/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been almost 40 years since Stanley Kubrick&amp;rsquo;s horror masterpiece The Shining hit the silver screens of America. The movie, starring Jack Nicholson, is based on a 1977 Stephen King novel of the same name and was tremendous hit for Nicholson, Kubrick, and King when it hit theaters in the summer of 1980.

Stanley Kubrick[/caption] Many people know that much, but what you may not know is that King wrote his novel based on a paranormal experience he had while staying at The Staley Hotel in Estes Park, CO in 1974.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Journalist Accidentally Given Files to Secret Government Project</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/journalist-accidentally-given-files-to-secret-government-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 21:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/journalist-accidentally-given-files-to-secret-government-project/</guid>
      <description>A people should never fear their government, for that is tyranny. The opposite, the government fearing the people, is the guarantor of freedom. Unfortunately, we suffer under the ‘aegis’ of a meddling centralized government masquerading as a benevolent patriarch. Agencies like the CIA, the Department of Homeland Security, the FBI and the National Security Agency to name a few, operate in the shadows of unconstitutionality and violations of human rights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biblical Numerologist Predicts End of the World for Monday</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/biblical-numerologist-predicts-end-of-the-world-for-monday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 20:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/biblical-numerologist-predicts-end-of-the-world-for-monday/</guid>
      <description>It seems like we have these predictions at least a couple of times a year. Some predictions usually occur in the fall, around the Jewish New Year. Enjoy your weekend, folks because according to some Christian eschatologists and numerologists, Monday April 23 will be the end of the world, reports the UK’s Express. Those prophesizing the imminent end are divided into two camps; those that believe our termination will come at the arrival of a mysterious alien planet referred to as ‘Planet X’ or Nibiru and the other camp that says our end will come as Jesus Christ arrives for the Second Coming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk Might Have Some Explaining to Do</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/elon-musk-might-have-some-explaining-to-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 20:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/elon-musk-might-have-some-explaining-to-do/</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk is a visionary. His Tesla brand has been the hottest thing in the automotive industry, and we&amp;rsquo;re just a few months removed from him launching a convertible into space with two Falcon rocket boosters that returned to Earth and landed themselves.

As a forward thinker and futurist, he&amp;rsquo;s planning a mission to Mars and warning Americans about the dangers of the advent of artificial intelligence. After viewing this next report, however, it seems someone should be warning Mr Musk about the problems in his own company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Submarine Discovery Solves Decades Old WW2 Mystery</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/submarine-discovery-solves-decades-old-ww2-mystery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 20:09:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/submarine-discovery-solves-decades-old-ww2-mystery/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s no secret that as World War II was winding down and Germany&amp;rsquo;s defeat became imminent that many Nazis fled to South America where they established new lives for themselves in countries such as Argentina and Brazil. Most notably among these were Adolf Eichmann and Josef Mengele.

Well, earlier this week off the coast of Denmark, researchers discovered the wreckage of a German submarine that was long rumored to have played a pivotal role in carrying the Nazis to South America.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Law in India Approves Death Penalty for Child Rapists</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/new-law-in-india-approves-death-penalty-for-child-rapists/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 17:56:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/new-law-in-india-approves-death-penalty-for-child-rapists/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to combatting the rise in crimes of sexual violence against children, the nation of India is done fooling around. Prime Minister Narendra Modi officially approved an ordinance which allows the death penalty to be handed down to anyone caught raping a child under the age of 12.

Even though the ordinance will require parliamentary approval within the next six months for it to become a law, child rapists can be prosecuted under this ordinance in the mean time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Finally Explain Curious Circles in Arctic Ice</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientists-finally-explain-curious-circles-in-arctic-ice/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 16:23:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientists-finally-explain-curious-circles-in-arctic-ice/</guid>
      <description>Each year for the past 10 years NASA has conducted airborne missions over both of Earth&amp;rsquo;s polar regions to map land and sea ice. On April 14, as part of this year&amp;rsquo;s mission, scientist John Sonntag noticed something he&amp;rsquo;d never seen before. There were random circles poking through the ice exposing the ocean water below.

So, as they flew about 50 miles northwest of Canada&amp;rsquo;s Mackenzie River Delta, Sonntag snapped a picture of the strange circles from the window of the plane.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Promotional Robot Freaks Out Pub Patrons with One Creepy Question</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/promotional-robot-freaks-out-pub-patrons-with-one-creepy-question/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 20:17:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/promotional-robot-freaks-out-pub-patrons-with-one-creepy-question/</guid>
      <description>Patrons of a London neighborhood pub got more than a pint of ale and cucumber sandwiches during their visit. Daily Mail reports that Engineered Arts, a company based in Penryn, Cornwall, created and embedded an artificial intelligence-based robot inside The Prince Alfred pub as part of a marketing campaign for HBO’s dystopic ‘Westworld’.

An Eerie Doppelgänger The robot, nicknamed Fred, was modeled after English actor Tedroy Newell and was seated in a booth with a pint in hand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LA Woman Comes Home From Work to Find Intruder in Bathroom Doing THIS</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/la-woman-comes-home-from-work-to-find-intruder-in-bathroom-doing-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 19:36:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/la-woman-comes-home-from-work-to-find-intruder-in-bathroom-doing-this/</guid>
      <description>Picture this scenario: You had a long day at work and cannot wait to get home, change into something more comfortable, put your feet up and finally relax. For one Monroe, Louisiana resident such a wish did not end as expected.

In the late afternoon of April 17, an unidentified woman entered her home, weary from hours at her job, to find someone had already gone into her house and was still there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Implant Human Brain Cells into Mice - You Won&#39;t Believe What Happened Next</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientists-implant-human-brain-cells-into-mice/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 18:55:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientists-implant-human-brain-cells-into-mice/</guid>
      <description>‘Of Mice and Men’ has a new interpretation now thanks to a group of scientists in California and if this interpretation is successful, debilitating mental disorders may be a thing of the past in years to come.

A group of researchers at Salk Institute in La Jolla, San Diego, California have succeeded in implanting human brain stem cells into the brains of mice and the results have been startling, reports the UK’s Express.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>