<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Funny on Brainsation</title>
    <link>http://st.brainsation.com/tags/funny/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Funny on Brainsation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 19:27:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://st.brainsation.com/tags/funny/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ready For Takeoff! These Airport Fails Are Almost Too Funny To Handle</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/ready-for-takeoff-these-airport-fails-are-almost-too-funny-to-handle/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 19:27:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/ready-for-takeoff-these-airport-fails-are-almost-too-funny-to-handle/</guid>
      <description>youtube Travelling is on many of our bucket lists. Whether you want to travel the globe or go cross-country, jumping on a plane is a convenient and relatively fast way to get anywhere you want to go. Navigating an airport may seem like a hike in itself. There are endless terminals and countless security measures — but even more astounding are the different people you get to see. The hectic, busy atmosphere of most airports sometimes has travelers acting rather silly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazing, Perfectly-Timed Cheerleader Fails That Will Make You Cringe, Then Laugh</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/amazing-perfectly-timed-cheerleader-fails-that-will-make-you-cringe-then-laugh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 20:28:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/amazing-perfectly-timed-cheerleader-fails-that-will-make-you-cringe-then-laugh/</guid>
      <description>Cheerleading began as a way to motivate sports teams during gameplay with positive team spirit. As time has gone on, it&amp;rsquo;s really evolved into a sport of its own. Cheer competitions are now held all around the world and feature groups of incredibly talented athletes. For a sport so focused on gymnastics and routines, there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of work that goes into making the perfect cheer. Luckily for us, that means there&amp;rsquo;s plenty of footage and photographs of what happens when something goes wrong!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>