<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Economics on Brainsation</title>
    <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/tags/economics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Economics on Brainsation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 23:13:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/tags/economics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Sir Richard Branson&#39;s Bringing the Space Age to the Desert in Dubai</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/sir-richard-bransons-bringing-the-space-age-to-the-desert-in-dubai/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 23:13:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/sir-richard-bransons-bringing-the-space-age-to-the-desert-in-dubai/</guid>
      <description>The future of overland cargo shipment and human travel is taking shape in the deserts of Dubai.
The Daily Mail writes that billionaire entrepreneur Richard Branson, founder and CEO of Virgin, is getting behind the development of what is called hyperloop technology.
Daily Mail Hyperloop uses a pod and tube system in which the pods are levitated and accelerated through the tubal system through electromagnetism, reaching speeds of up to 760mph.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experts at University of Texas Launch Controversial Program Aimed at Men</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/experts-at-university-of-texas-launch-controversial-program-aimed-at-men/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 17:24:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/experts-at-university-of-texas-launch-controversial-program-aimed-at-men/</guid>
      <description>Turn on any TV show or watch any commercial and what you will most likely see are scenes with characters consisting of strong, smart women and dopey and weak men. Those of you with children in high school or college have most likely heard of Academia’s crusade against ‘toxic masculinity’.

Now, one Texas university is attempting to slap a medical motivation behind dangerous masculinity, reports PJ Media.

Tyranny of the Technocrats At the University of Texas at Austin, the Counseling and Mental Health Center has initiated a campaign to tell men that their traits of masculinity are barriers to a balanced mental health.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia’s ‘Floating Chernobyl’ Alarms Officials</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/russias-floating-chernobyl-alarms-officials/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 15:41:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/russias-floating-chernobyl-alarms-officials/</guid>
      <description>The nuclear age has taken to the high seas. This statement has nothing to do with nuclear-powered submarines, aircraft carriers or ice-breaking naval vessels. The ground-breaking, or rather ground-leaving, event involves nuclear reactors perched atop floating barges and hauled out to sea.

‘Nuclear Titanic’ On April 28, a Russian planned and constructed nuclear facility was successfully tugged from its berthing area in the historic naval port of St. Petersburg to Murmansk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Research Claims to Solve JFK Assassination Theories, But Does It?</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/new-research-claims-to-solve-jfk-assassination-theories-but-does-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 17:56:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/new-research-claims-to-solve-jfk-assassination-theories-but-does-it/</guid>
      <description>The assassination of President John F. Kennedy took place over 50 years ago in Dallas, Texas, yet conspiracy theories still abound as to what happened on that fateful November day. Now, thanks to advancements in technology and the ability to digitally analyze audio and video footage of the shooting and its aftermath, one research firm thinks they&amp;rsquo;ve solved a major part of the puzzle.

From IFLScience.com According to official reports, Lee Harvey Oswald was the prime (and only) suspect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Could You Follow This Flapper Diet From 100 Years Ago?</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/could-you-follow-this-flapper-diet-from-100-years-ago/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 20:31:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/could-you-follow-this-flapper-diet-from-100-years-ago/</guid>
      <description>In the second decade of the 20th Century, American society was steeped in the opulence and hedonism of the ‘Roaring 20s’. The Great War was over and economic progress had returned big time to the United States. The zeitgeist was the closest Americans came to the French joie de vivre.

According to some sociologists, the generation during that time (the Crisis stage) was the artist group. The 1920s gave birth to bohemians and flappers, so it would indeed appear that the authors were right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flying Drone Taxi Lifts Off in Oregon - Are You Ready?</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/flying-drone-taxi-lifts-off-in-oregon-are-you-ready/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 19:52:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/flying-drone-taxi-lifts-off-in-oregon-are-you-ready/</guid>
      <description>All throughout the 20th century, one of the signature features of the future that Americans looked forward to was the possibility of flying cars. Getting in your car and, just like George Jetson, blasting off to work and then home again. Well, it looks like the future is not that far off.

The world may be on the cusp of the skies being filled with flying taxis. The European company, Airbus, who produces civilian and military aircraft, has released video of tests of its ‘Vahana’ vertical takeoff and landing (VTOL) drone taxi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Texas Scientist Solves Two Ansel Adams Mysteries</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/texas-scientist-solves-two-ansel-adams-mysteries/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 17:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/texas-scientist-solves-two-ansel-adams-mysteries/</guid>
      <description>Donald Olson is an amateur sleuth, but the mysteries he solves don&amp;rsquo;t put killers behind bars or reveal the identities of murderers in some sort of overly dramatic third act. No, Olson tackles the mysteries that artists and great figures in history have left for the rest of us to figure out.

The Art Detective From Atlas Obscura: An astrophysicist and forensic astronomer, Olson uses quantitative methods to answer questions raised by artwork, literature, and historical accounts—not the heady ones, but the basic, surprisingly slippery who, what, when, and where.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Re-Examined Museum Piece Discovered to Be Older Than the Pyramids</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/re-examined-museum-piece-discovered-to-be-older-than-the-pyramids/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 15:29:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/re-examined-museum-piece-discovered-to-be-older-than-the-pyramids/</guid>
      <description>The Pleistocene Epoch is the term scientists use to describe the last ice age that ended about 11,700 years ago. It was at about this time, almost 12,000 years ago that a group of people in Siberia (the land where the ice age never really ended), carved a tree into a human like wooden idol almost 5 meters long.

Fast forward to 1894, when gold prospectors discovered the idol while digging up a peat bog near the Russian city Yekaterinburg.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japanese Farmers Turn to Wolf-Like Creature for Protection</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/japanese-farmers-turn-to-wolf-like-creature-for-protection/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 20:51:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/japanese-farmers-turn-to-wolf-like-creature-for-protection/</guid>
      <description>It looks and sounds like something out of a sci-fi horror flick. With eyes that glow a menacing red, white fangs and inhuman howls, a new creature is stalking the rice paddies and agricultural fields of Japan.

It is called the Super Monster Wolf and stands 20 inches tall and is around 25 ½ inches long. Oh and it costs about $4,800 to buy. The creature is a solar powered robot wolf designed to scare away scavengers and other animals from farms and rice paddies throughout Japan, writes The Sun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York &amp; The Great Thunder Snow Blizzard of 2018</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/new-york-the-great-thunder-snow-blizzard-of-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 19:54:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/new-york-the-great-thunder-snow-blizzard-of-2018/</guid>
      <description>The Northeast has definitely experienced some intense weather this spring and a few weeks ago, a massive storm grew miles above the Big Apple. The energy it created gave birth to thunder storms during a major snow event.

On March 7, first New York City and then northern New Jersey, experienced thunder snow during a strong coastal front. In the process billions of ice crystals high up in the atmosphere moving at a frenetic pace due to the winds of the storm, began charging each other with electrical energy This rapid movement charges an area of the atmosphere, which in turn draws more ice crystals to it like a magnet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s Why California Residents Might Want to Start Buying Bottled Water</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/heres-why-california-residents-might-want-to-start-buying-bottled-water/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 18:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/heres-why-california-residents-might-want-to-start-buying-bottled-water/</guid>
      <description>Day-by-day, California is getting closer to running out of drinking water. In the wealthiest nation on Earth, it is inconceivable that this should be happening.
Now the Dems of Cali have to drink sewage because they are totally incompetent. California to add recycled sewer water to the state reservoirs https://t.co/SNWTVx3jFA #FoxNews
&amp;mdash; Martin a Patriot (@pfiec) March 8, 2018  Adversity being the mother of invention, the SFGate reports that San Diego is hoping its’ experiment in recycled water will trickle throughout the Golden State.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Known Story of the Deaf Men Who Helped NASA Get Into Space</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/little-known-story-of-the-deaf-men-who-helped-nasa-get-into-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 17:25:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/little-known-story-of-the-deaf-men-who-helped-nasa-get-into-space/</guid>
      <description>The story of the American space program and the organized effort it took to launch astronauts into space and, eventually, onto the moon is a remarkable tale of people from all walks of life coming together to achieve a great mission.

The contribution of several remarkable women was portrayed in the recent hit movie Hidden Figures, and now Discover Magazine has the account of a group of men who, up until now, have been unheard of in the tale of the exploration of space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Power of Breathing to Calm Your Brain</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/the-power-of-breathing-to-calm-your-brain/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 18:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/the-power-of-breathing-to-calm-your-brain/</guid>
      <description>For years, humans have relied on breathing as a way to achieve peace of mind. As you know, one of the most basic and effective forms of meditation is to become aware of your breath and follow it, in and out of your body.

Well, it looks like science is confirming all of religion&amp;rsquo;s teachings on the positive effects of breathing. A recent article in Psychology Today talks about a 2016 conducted by neuroscientists from Stanford, UCLA, and St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bezos&#39; Latest Brainstorm: A Walking, Talking Alexa in Every Home</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/bezos-latest-brainstorm-a-walking-talking-alexa-in-every-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 18:46:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/bezos-latest-brainstorm-a-walking-talking-alexa-in-every-home/</guid>
      <description>Like it or not, artificial intelligence is advancing at a phenomenal rate. While some people fear the Pandora&amp;rsquo;s Box that AI will open up and others are, at the very least, leery of the rise of the machine, some people are optimistic and welcoming of the new technology. Jeff Bezos is hoping you fall into the third category.

Here&amp;rsquo;s the story from Bloomberg: The retail and cloud computing giant has embarked on an ambitious, top-secret plan to build a domestic robot, according to people familiar with the plans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geologist Run Earthquake Simulation in San Francisco, Here are the Results</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/geologist-run-earthquake-simulation-in-san-francisco-here-are-the-results/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 18:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/geologist-run-earthquake-simulation-in-san-francisco-here-are-the-results/</guid>
      <description>California is used to earthquakes. There are small to medium tremors that occur monthly throughout the year. The last major quake to strike California was the shallow 6.9 Loma Prieta earthquake in 1989, often referred to as the ‘World Series Quake’ since it struck during a MLB playoff game. The quake killed 67 people, injured 3,000 and cost $5 billion in damages.
  Before that, in 1906, a vicious 7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Court Hands Down Verdict in &#39;Monkey See, Monkey Selfie&#39; Case</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/court-hands-down-verdict-in-monkey-see-monkey-selfie-case/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 18:03:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/court-hands-down-verdict-in-monkey-see-monkey-selfie-case/</guid>
      <description>It’s not the equivalent of the Scope Monkey Trial of 1925, but another legal case with a primate at the center of it has found its way into American culture. Unlike the Scopes trial, which addressed the weighty subject of biological evolution, this case is a comical farce of a lawsuit over photo selfies.

‘Monkey See Monkey Sue’ The U.S. 9th Circuit Court of Appeals has recently ruled on a 2011 lawsuit filed by the People for the Ethical Treatment of Animals (PETA) over photographs inadvertently taken of an Indonesian crested macaque, named Naruto, by British nature photographer David Slater, reports the Huffington Post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Man Gets Attacked by Rattlesnake, Bear, &amp; Tiger Shark - And Lives to Tell About It</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/man-gets-attacked-by-rattlesnake-bear-tiger-shark-and-lives-to-tell-about-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 17:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/man-gets-attacked-by-rattlesnake-bear-tiger-shark-and-lives-to-tell-about-it/</guid>
      <description>Beauty is in the eye of the beholder and the same may be said of luck. A twenty-year-old Colorado native named Dylan McWilliams may either be the most unlucky or luckiest man, reports Sky News.

On April 19, while enjoying a two week vacation to Hawaii, McWilliams was on his surfboard in the early morning waters of Shipwreck&amp;rsquo;s Beach, 50 yards off of Poipu. The avid surfer and survival instructor was enjoying a beautiful morning when he suddenly felt something clamp down on one of his submerged legs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NASA Just Took a Giant Leap Forward in It&#39;s Mission to Find Habitable Planets</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/nasa-just-took-a-giant-leap-forward-in-its-mission-to-find-habitable-planets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 19:41:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/nasa-just-took-a-giant-leap-forward-in-its-mission-to-find-habitable-planets/</guid>
      <description>Last week a Space X Falcon 9 Rocket took off from Cape Canaveral Air Station in Florida and launched a very special satellite named TESS into Earth&amp;rsquo;s orbit. TESS stands for Transiting Exoplanet Surevey Satellite and its mission is to discover new planets. NASA is very excited about the possibilities.

From Space.com: &amp;ldquo;TESS is going to dramatically increase the number of planets that we have to study,&amp;rdquo; TESS principal investigator George Ricker, of the Massachusetts Institute of Technology, said during a pre-launch briefing Sunday (April 15).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guests at &#39;The Shining&#39; Hotel Accidentally Take Picture of Ghost</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/guests-at-the-shining-hotel-accidentally-take-picture-of-ghost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 17:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/guests-at-the-shining-hotel-accidentally-take-picture-of-ghost/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been almost 40 years since Stanley Kubrick&amp;rsquo;s horror masterpiece The Shining hit the silver screens of America. The movie, starring Jack Nicholson, is based on a 1977 Stephen King novel of the same name and was tremendous hit for Nicholson, Kubrick, and King when it hit theaters in the summer of 1980.

Stanley Kubrick[/caption] Many people know that much, but what you may not know is that King wrote his novel based on a paranormal experience he had while staying at The Staley Hotel in Estes Park, CO in 1974.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Journalist Accidentally Given Files to Secret Government Project</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/journalist-accidentally-given-files-to-secret-government-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 21:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/journalist-accidentally-given-files-to-secret-government-project/</guid>
      <description>A people should never fear their government, for that is tyranny. The opposite, the government fearing the people, is the guarantor of freedom. Unfortunately, we suffer under the ‘aegis’ of a meddling centralized government masquerading as a benevolent patriarch. Agencies like the CIA, the Department of Homeland Security, the FBI and the National Security Agency to name a few, operate in the shadows of unconstitutionality and violations of human rights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biblical Numerologist Predicts End of the World for Monday</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/biblical-numerologist-predicts-end-of-the-world-for-monday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 20:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/biblical-numerologist-predicts-end-of-the-world-for-monday/</guid>
      <description>It seems like we have these predictions at least a couple of times a year. Some predictions usually occur in the fall, around the Jewish New Year. Enjoy your weekend, folks because according to some Christian eschatologists and numerologists, Monday April 23 will be the end of the world, reports the UK’s Express. Those prophesizing the imminent end are divided into two camps; those that believe our termination will come at the arrival of a mysterious alien planet referred to as ‘Planet X’ or Nibiru and the other camp that says our end will come as Jesus Christ arrives for the Second Coming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk Might Have Some Explaining to Do</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/elon-musk-might-have-some-explaining-to-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 20:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/elon-musk-might-have-some-explaining-to-do/</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk is a visionary. His Tesla brand has been the hottest thing in the automotive industry, and we&amp;rsquo;re just a few months removed from him launching a convertible into space with two Falcon rocket boosters that returned to Earth and landed themselves.

As a forward thinker and futurist, he&amp;rsquo;s planning a mission to Mars and warning Americans about the dangers of the advent of artificial intelligence. After viewing this next report, however, it seems someone should be warning Mr Musk about the problems in his own company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Submarine Discovery Solves Decades Old WW2 Mystery</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/submarine-discovery-solves-decades-old-ww2-mystery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 20:09:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/submarine-discovery-solves-decades-old-ww2-mystery/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s no secret that as World War II was winding down and Germany&amp;rsquo;s defeat became imminent that many Nazis fled to South America where they established new lives for themselves in countries such as Argentina and Brazil. Most notably among these were Adolf Eichmann and Josef Mengele.

Well, earlier this week off the coast of Denmark, researchers discovered the wreckage of a German submarine that was long rumored to have played a pivotal role in carrying the Nazis to South America.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Law in India Approves Death Penalty for Child Rapists</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/new-law-in-india-approves-death-penalty-for-child-rapists/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 17:56:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/new-law-in-india-approves-death-penalty-for-child-rapists/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to combatting the rise in crimes of sexual violence against children, the nation of India is done fooling around. Prime Minister Narendra Modi officially approved an ordinance which allows the death penalty to be handed down to anyone caught raping a child under the age of 12.

Even though the ordinance will require parliamentary approval within the next six months for it to become a law, child rapists can be prosecuted under this ordinance in the mean time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Finally Explain Curious Circles in Arctic Ice</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/scientists-finally-explain-curious-circles-in-arctic-ice/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 16:23:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/scientists-finally-explain-curious-circles-in-arctic-ice/</guid>
      <description>Each year for the past 10 years NASA has conducted airborne missions over both of Earth&amp;rsquo;s polar regions to map land and sea ice. On April 14, as part of this year&amp;rsquo;s mission, scientist John Sonntag noticed something he&amp;rsquo;d never seen before. There were random circles poking through the ice exposing the ocean water below.

So, as they flew about 50 miles northwest of Canada&amp;rsquo;s Mackenzie River Delta, Sonntag snapped a picture of the strange circles from the window of the plane.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Promotional Robot Freaks Out Pub Patrons with One Creepy Question</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/promotional-robot-freaks-out-pub-patrons-with-one-creepy-question/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 20:17:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/promotional-robot-freaks-out-pub-patrons-with-one-creepy-question/</guid>
      <description>Patrons of a London neighborhood pub got more than a pint of ale and cucumber sandwiches during their visit. Daily Mail reports that Engineered Arts, a company based in Penryn, Cornwall, created and embedded an artificial intelligence-based robot inside The Prince Alfred pub as part of a marketing campaign for HBO’s dystopic ‘Westworld’.

An Eerie Doppelgänger The robot, nicknamed Fred, was modeled after English actor Tedroy Newell and was seated in a booth with a pint in hand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LA Woman Comes Home From Work to Find Intruder in Bathroom Doing THIS</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/la-woman-comes-home-from-work-to-find-intruder-in-bathroom-doing-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 19:36:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/la-woman-comes-home-from-work-to-find-intruder-in-bathroom-doing-this/</guid>
      <description>Picture this scenario: You had a long day at work and cannot wait to get home, change into something more comfortable, put your feet up and finally relax. For one Monroe, Louisiana resident such a wish did not end as expected.

In the late afternoon of April 17, an unidentified woman entered her home, weary from hours at her job, to find someone had already gone into her house and was still there.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>