<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Entertainment on Brainsation</title>
    <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/tags/entertainment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Entertainment on Brainsation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 22:20:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/tags/entertainment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Amazing Historical Photos That Show Exactly How Our Culture Has Evolved</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/20-amazing-historical-photos-that-show-exactly-how-our-culture-has-evolved/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 22:20:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/20-amazing-historical-photos-that-show-exactly-how-our-culture-has-evolved/</guid>
      <description>They say that the past can teach us many lessons, but the truth is that many of us never paid that much attention in history classes at school. That&amp;rsquo;s because history in school is always so boring. Who wants to be bored all the time? Not us. So, we don&amp;rsquo;t remember much from back then. That&amp;rsquo;s why we&amp;rsquo;ve delved into the archives to bring you 20 images from the past with real stories to tell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ready For Takeoff! These Airport Fails Are Almost Too Funny To Handle</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/ready-for-takeoff-these-airport-fails-are-almost-too-funny-to-handle/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 19:27:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/ready-for-takeoff-these-airport-fails-are-almost-too-funny-to-handle/</guid>
      <description>youtube Travelling is on many of our bucket lists. Whether you want to travel the globe or go cross-country, jumping on a plane is a convenient and relatively fast way to get anywhere you want to go. Navigating an airport may seem like a hike in itself. There are endless terminals and countless security measures — but even more astounding are the different people you get to see. The hectic, busy atmosphere of most airports sometimes has travelers acting rather silly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insane Pictures Of The Most Flexible Girls In The World</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/insane-pictures-of-the-most-flexible-girls-in-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 04:24:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/insane-pictures-of-the-most-flexible-girls-in-the-world/</guid>
      <description>Although the human body is incredibly resilient in terms of what it can endure, most people aren&amp;rsquo;t very flexible. Mastering the art of contortion takes a lot of training and good, rubbery genes. Many factors are taken into account when establishing personal flexibility: joint structure, ligaments, tendons, muscles, skin, tissue injury, fat (or adipose) tissue, body temperature, activity level, age and sex all influence an individual&amp;rsquo;s range of motion about a joint.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazing, Perfectly-Timed Cheerleader Fails That Will Make You Cringe, Then Laugh</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/amazing-perfectly-timed-cheerleader-fails-that-will-make-you-cringe-then-laugh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 20:28:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/amazing-perfectly-timed-cheerleader-fails-that-will-make-you-cringe-then-laugh/</guid>
      <description>Cheerleading began as a way to motivate sports teams during gameplay with positive team spirit. As time has gone on, it&amp;rsquo;s really evolved into a sport of its own. Cheer competitions are now held all around the world and feature groups of incredibly talented athletes. For a sport so focused on gymnastics and routines, there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of work that goes into making the perfect cheer. Luckily for us, that means there&amp;rsquo;s plenty of footage and photographs of what happens when something goes wrong!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>These Perfectly-Timed Sports Photos Will Make Even Non-Sports Fans Literal LOL</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/these-perfectly-timed-sports-photos-will-make-even-non-sports-fans-literal-lol/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 01:44:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/these-perfectly-timed-sports-photos-will-make-even-non-sports-fans-literal-lol/</guid>
      <description>pinkfinishpicture You might think that sports are all about good timing in the first place, and that&amp;rsquo;s certainly true. You need that perfect opportunity to set up a field goal or find space to drop the ball in the basket. But that&amp;rsquo;s a different kind of timing than comedic timing, and we want to laugh today. These fantastic photos are moments that won&amp;rsquo;t ever happen again. They required a lucky photographer to be in the right place at the right time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ridiculous People of Walmart</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/the-ridiculous-people-of-walmart/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 22:53:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/the-ridiculous-people-of-walmart/</guid>
      <description>LipstickAlley Who doesn&amp;rsquo;t love to shop at Walmart? This leading retail chain has everything that you need ranging from clothing, food, jewelry, electronics, and household items. With such a vast collection, the retail store attracts different types of people. In fact, the store may be America&amp;rsquo;s real retail convergence zone. However, everyone has a unique experience purchasing at the store. Some of the clients who shop at Walmart walk in with unique costumes and habits that no one else can match.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Horribly Awkward Wedding Fails</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/20-horribly-awkward-wedding-fails/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 21:43:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/20-horribly-awkward-wedding-fails/</guid>
      <description>BridalHairArt Weddings are meant to be beautiful. When we think of two people committing to love each other for the rest of our lives, our minds conjure pictures of white doves and perfumed flowers. Motivated brides spend months and small fortunes to plan and execute the perfect experience. Sometimes, however, good planning just isn’t enough. No matter how carefully an event is prepared, the unexpected can still happen. But that doesn’t have to ruin the big day!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Amazingly Perfectly Timed Photos</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/20-amazingly-perfectly-timed-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 06:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/20-amazingly-perfectly-timed-photos/</guid>
      <description>wnewslife
You might be the best photographer there is out there but sometimes, you don’t have to be the best to take a perfect photo. You just need to be at the right place in the right moment. It will not matter if you take it with a phone or a very good camera; you just need to be passionate about what you do. Most of the time, you won’t even notice you took an awesome photo till you sit down to look at them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 20 Most Dangerous Prisons In The World</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/the-20-most-dangerous-prisons-in-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 21:33:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/the-20-most-dangerous-prisons-in-the-world/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re guilty of binge watching _Orange is the New Black_ and imagining what life would be like serving time in a corrections facility, you&amp;rsquo;re not alone. However, if you care to preserve that misguided fantasy, turn back now. In reality, prison doesn’t generally conjure feelings of safety or warm, fuzzy thoughts. But there are institutions that are so extraordinarily unsafe and inhumane, it defies imagination. For those who are curious about real life in some of the most notoriously dangerous prisons in the world, click on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 20 Most Deadly Animals in the World</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/the-20-most-deadly-animals-in-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/the-20-most-deadly-animals-in-the-world/</guid>
      <description>Over the years, there are those animals that have continued to steal the top position among the deadliest animals in the world. Although you cannot rule them out, there’s more to it than just brawn, large teeth, and venom defensive mechanisms when it comes to categorizing the most life-threatening creatures on the earth and in water. You think sharks, lions, and elephants are deadliest animals? You&amp;rsquo;re dead wrong. Some of the little creatures that you find cute and probably been playing around with are surprisingly extremely dangerous.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Behind The Scenes Facts About Forrest Gump You Didn&#39;t Know</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/behind-the-scenes-facts-about-forrest-gump-you-didnt-know/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 20:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/behind-the-scenes-facts-about-forrest-gump-you-didnt-know/</guid>
      <description>Forrest Gump turned Hollywood upside-down in 1994. Tom Hanks delivered, possibly, his finest performance to date, and many believe it to be one of the greatest films ever made. The movie had the perfect blend of humor, action and emotional drama, that really resonated with its audience. At the &amp;lsquo;Oscars&amp;rsquo; it won Best Picture and Tom Hanks won Best Actor. With all of its popularity, Forrest Gump has some unknown behind the scenes aspects, that even the most hardcore fan probably doesn&amp;rsquo;t even know about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Most Expensive &amp; Shocking Celebrity Plastic Surgeries</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/most-expensive-shocking-celebrity-plastic-surgeries/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 22:20:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/most-expensive-shocking-celebrity-plastic-surgeries/</guid>
      <description>Donatella Versace – $25,000 She is synonymous with her last name in the fashion industry. As she has aged she has tried to keep herself young. $25k, might seem like alot, but compared to the other names on this list, it is actually quite cheap. We&amp;rsquo;re thinking she wishes she had shelled out more money, because she looks sort of inhuman at this point!

Pinterest
Lil’ Kim – $19,625 With the passing of time comes a change for the better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extremely Rare Historical Photos You Won&#39;t Find In History Books</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/extremely-rare-historical-photos-you-wont-find-in-history-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 19:28:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/extremely-rare-historical-photos-you-wont-find-in-history-books/</guid>
      <description>If you think you know your history, get ready to be humbled. The rare photographs below show a different perspective of historical events, and you probably wouldn’t find them in any school textbook.
Imgur
Che Guevera &amp;amp; Fidel Castro BlazePress
Two very controversial political figures from Cuba, hang out together whilst fishing in the 60&amp;rsquo;s. Police Woman Chasing Skinny Dippers Vintag
Some brave fellas there, going skinny dipping in the middle of the day in a crowded park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kardashians: The Unknown Early Years</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/kardashians-early-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 20:21:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/kardashians-early-years/</guid>
      <description>Even if you are not a fan, it is hard to look away from the rumors and gossip that follow the wealthy family. And safe to say there are many of them. From Kim’s bold magazine cover to Khloe’s real biological father, even if you don’t watch the show you most likely are aware of all the drama, since it is plastered all over our television sets, smartphones, tablets and computers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Most Shocking Wives and Girlfriends of NBA Stars</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/the-23-hottest-wags-in-the-nba/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 20:05:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/the-23-hottest-wags-in-the-nba/</guid>
      <description>Over the past several years the NBA has turned into quite possibly the biggest sport in america, with more stars in the league than any other. With all of this new star-power, the pretty, and not so pretty, women are sure to not be far behind. We are here to keep you up to date with all of the off-court drama, and bring you the hottest (and strangest) wives and girlfriends of the NBA superstars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Horribly Awkward Prom Photos</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/20-horribly-awkward-prom-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 21:04:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/20-horribly-awkward-prom-photos/</guid>
      <description>Highschool is a very awkward time to be alive. We are growing into out bodies, and learning how to be a social human. Have you ever gone back and looked at your cringeworthy prom photo from many years ago? Well, these are the worst of the worst! Enjoy!

Complex
Class Act Michelle Obama Caught in Wicked Chair 
Pinterest
Whoever thought that wicker would be great for a formal prom photo that would stick around for decades did not have two cents to rub together in the common sense category.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 20 Celebs You Didn&#39;t Know Were Gay</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/top-20-celebs-you-didnt-know-were-gay/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 18:31:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/top-20-celebs-you-didnt-know-were-gay/</guid>
      <description>Many movie stars and artists are in gay relationships. Even though they try to keep their private life away from the public domain, they are eventually exposed. However, there are those who embrace who they are by admitting to the world that they are gay. Below is a list of 20 celebrities who you didn&amp;rsquo;t know were gay.
1. Tom Daley 
DailyStar Tom used a homemade video to break his silence regarding his relationship status.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Lame To Fame: Amazing Celebrity Transformations That&#39;ll Make You Double-Take!</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/from-lame-to-fame-amazing-celebrity-transformations-thatll-make-you-double-take/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 18:47:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/from-lame-to-fame-amazing-celebrity-transformations-thatll-make-you-double-take/</guid>
      <description>Stars grow up just like regular people. Plus, with the added pressure from fans and critics, it makes sense that celebrities would want to change a few things every now and again. From weight loss to total make overs, these 30 stars have had the biggest transformations of our time.

BET
Jonah Hill - 2016 
InTouch
Jonah Hill has become rather well known for his rapid weight fluctuations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game of Thrones Characters - How They Are Described in Book and How They Appear on TV</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/game-of-thrones-characters-how-they-are-described-in-book-and-how-they-appear-on-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 19:36:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/game-of-thrones-characters-how-they-are-described-in-book-and-how-they-appear-on-tv/</guid>
      <description>Lovers of HBO’s TV series Game of Thrones who have read George R.R Martin’s book _A Song of Ice and Fire_ upon which the series is based, acknowledge the fact that key differences exist between the characters in the book and TV series. Naturally, the nature of the medium allows some changes to take place as we transit from the books to a television show. Even as the show continues to develop through season 7, the differences between the book version and the show become more pronounced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Actors You didn&#39;t Realize Passed Away in 2017</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/20-actors-you-didnt-realize-passed-away-in-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 19:07:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/20-actors-you-didnt-realize-passed-away-in-2017/</guid>
      <description>Reddit Life is short, so they say. Any moment someone can die and when death strikes all we can do is mourn the departed soul and wish that it rest s in eternal peace. Unfortunately, death isn&amp;rsquo;t selective about who should go and who should remain on earth. Over the past few years, we have lost some of the greatest men and women who brought us unforgettable memories. 2017 hasn&amp;rsquo;t been any different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Celebrity Children All Grown Up</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/10-celebrity-children-all-grown-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 23:23:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/10-celebrity-children-all-grown-up/</guid>
      <description>Celebrities’ lives are splashed across a myriad of media outlets every day, all day. The reality is reporting on celebrities is really big business.
The children of these gifted, renowned individuals, however, are often purposefully hidden from the public for obvious reasons. What is quite fascinating is that celebrity offspring are frequently even more impressive than their parents. A large percentage of these celebrity children try to follow their parents’ professional career paths.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What The Cast Of Game Of Thrones Were Like Before They Got Famous</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/what-the-cast-of-game-of-thrones-were-like-before-they-got-famous/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 00:05:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/what-the-cast-of-game-of-thrones-were-like-before-they-got-famous/</guid>
      <description>Game of Thrones is undoubtedly one of the most popular shows to have ever graced the small screen. With its vast world and intriguing characters, this monster HBO original from writer George R.R. Martin premiered to great acclaim and a healthy fan craze. Part of the success is the cast, who are made up of some well-known names and newcomers alike.
TheSuperficial
Here is a look at what some of the brilliant cast was up to before they entered the world of Westeros.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>These 30 Celebrities Dodged Their Taxes And Ran From The IRS</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/these-30-celebrities-dodged-taxes-ran-from-the-irs-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2017 20:43:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/these-30-celebrities-dodged-taxes-ran-from-the-irs-2/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Money is a problem until you&amp;rsquo;ve got some.&amp;rdquo; This adage is true for some, but not for these riches-to-rags celebrities. Whether it be gambling, bad investing, or poor spending, these people have all had to evade the taxman at least once in their lives. From boxers to actors to presidents of the United States, here are 30 celebrities who fled the IRS.
Flickr
Pamela Anderson Flickr
Known as a bona fide sex symbol in the 1990s, Pamela Anderson has had a rough going of things as of late.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Shocking Net Worth Of These Celebs Will Completely Boggle Your Mind</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/shocking-net-worths/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 17:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/shocking-net-worths/</guid>
      <description>Reddit Life is short, so they say. Any moment someone can die and when death strikes all we can do is mourn the departed soul and wish that it rest s in eternal peace. Unfortunately, death isn&amp;rsquo;t selective about who should go and who should remain on earth. Over the past few years, we have lost some of the greatest men and women who brought us unforgettable memories. 2017 hasn&amp;rsquo;t been any different.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>