<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Animal on Brainsation</title>
    <link>http://st.brainsation.com/tags/animal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Animal on Brainsation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 20:13:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://st.brainsation.com/tags/animal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Stunned Grandma Learns &#39;Puppy&#39; That Never Barked and Hated Dog Food Is Actually a...</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/stunned-grandma/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 20:13:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/stunned-grandma/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;I was told that he was a Japanese Spitz puppy,&amp;rdquo; said Mrs. Wang. &amp;ldquo;But I knew that something was strange about the animal. He never ate dog food. Not once. And he never barked either.&amp;rdquo; When a grandmother in China visited her neighborhood pet shop looking for a companion, she was originally considering a cat. She thought a feline would be trouble-free and &amp;ldquo;more independent than a dog.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Wolfeboro Millionaire Sobbed When the Judge Read the Verdict</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/owner-neglects-dogs-health-and-pays-for-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2018 03:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/owner-neglects-dogs-health-and-pays-for-it/</guid>
      <description>A scandal involving a millionaire pet owner recently came to light and shocked every on-looker. Please share your thoughts with us at the bottom of this post! Most pet owners care for their furry friends as if they were born into the family. In fact, in the past several decades, this had led to the explosive growth of the pet industry. Nowadays, owners are able to treat their pets with many of the same luxuries that people enjoy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Authorities Raid Poacher&#39;s House in Madagascar - Agents Shocked at What They Found</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/authorities-raid-poachers-house-in-madagascar-agents-shocked-at-what-they-found/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 18:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/authorities-raid-poachers-house-in-madagascar-agents-shocked-at-what-they-found/</guid>
      <description>Wikimedia Commons[/caption] An emergency visit by a team from Madagascar’s environmental agency as well as police to a home in Toliara recently uncovered what looks to be a smuggling operation of epic proportions. As agents from the government descended on the abode, following complaints from neighbors of a rancid smell coming from the two story building, they interrupted the work of three people in the process of burying deceased radiated tortoises.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harvard Scientists Hope This Extinct Animal Can Make a &#39;Mammoth&#39; Comeback</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/harvard-scientists-hope-this-extinct-animal-can-make-a-mammoth-comeback/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 18:13:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/harvard-scientists-hope-this-extinct-animal-can-make-a-mammoth-comeback/</guid>
      <description>Wikimedia Commons[/caption] The Flintstones&amp;rsquo; dishwasher is one step closer to being resurrected. Move over Maytag! Make way for the Woolly Mammoth! C/Net reports now that scientists have successfully duplicated 44 mammoth genes, they are now hoping to grow a mammoth-hybrid in an artificial womb. The large hairy elephant walked the earth as early as 2.5 million years ago before going extinct around 3rd millennium B.C. A team of researchers at Harvard University, headed up by well-known geneticist Professor George Church, participated in the Fourth International Vatican Conference in Vatican City on April 27.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Police Found in This Doctor&#39;s Mansion Has San Antonio Residents Freaking Out!</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/what-police-found-in-this-doctors-mansion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 21:28:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/what-police-found-in-this-doctors-mansion/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;We couldn&amp;rsquo;t believe what we found inside the home,&amp;rdquo; San Antonio police officer Chet Daniels said. &amp;ldquo;In all my years on the force, I&amp;rsquo;ve never seen anything like this. There were cats and dogs everywhere, just covered in fecal matter. It was sad.&amp;rdquo; 
When police officer C. Daniels served a warrant on a luxurious home around 8 a.m. on Sunday, he expected it to be a routine call. After receiving noise and smell complaints from neighbors, officer Daniels and his partner Jason Stewart paid a visit to the well-to-do 100 block of Sioux Circle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Real Life &#39;Lassie&#39; Leads Rescuers to Little Girl Lost in Wilderness</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/real-life-lassie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 19:03:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/real-life-lassie/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to the incredibly heroic actions of a physically impaired dog an Australian family has their three-year-old daughter back safe and sound, reports Fox News. The backstory is a heart-warming story of survival and loyalty.

Every Parents Worst Nightmare On a cool and rainy April 20 day in Queensland, Australia the Bennett family was enjoying the beginning of the weekend when Leisa Bennett noticed that her three-year-old granddaughter, Aurora, had could not be found in the house and in the immediate vicinity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Most Insane Animal Attacks</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-most-insane-animal-attacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 20:25:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-most-insane-animal-attacks/</guid>
      <description>ThePinsta Animal attacks are a common cause of either human injuries or fatalities. In the U.S. alone, up to five million people are attacked by dogs and cats each year, with the frequency of animal attacks varying depending on geographical location. In the U.S., an individual is more likely to be killed by domesticated animals than they are to die from being hit by lighting. When agitated, hungry, or scared, animals go back to their true nature - the instinct to survive no matter the cause.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 20 Cutest Interspecies Friendships of All Time!</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-20-cutest-interspecies-friendships-of-all-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 20:22:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-20-cutest-interspecies-friendships-of-all-time/</guid>
      <description>While some friendships are as a result of the coming together of similar personalities, others are made up of the strangest of characters. This is the case when two animals from different species meet and form an unbreakable bond of friendship. The interspecies friendships are not only strong but also cute, a factor that makes them a source of inspiration even for humans. There have been several instances where animals of different species developed unbelievable bonds, with some interspecies friendships being termed as adoptions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Hilarious Photos of Bad Dogs</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-hilarious-photos-of-bad-dogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 19:34:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-hilarious-photos-of-bad-dogs/</guid>
      <description>Humans and dogs share a special bond – a symbiotic one for that matter. Our furry friends not only provide us companionship, but they&amp;rsquo;re also probably the most loyal pets we can own. However, that doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean that every day is cuddles, rocking, and joy.
Seenox It reaches a time when they get rebellious and engage in all manner trouble in the house. Sometimes we scold them. Other times we cannot help it but burst out laughing at their funny and stupid behavior.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hilarious Photos Of Animals Taken At The Exact Perfect Moment</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/hilarious-photos-of-animals-taken-at-the-exact-perfect-moment/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2017 22:54:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/hilarious-photos-of-animals-taken-at-the-exact-perfect-moment/</guid>
      <description>DailyStar Wild animals are majestic, fascinating, frightening and at times, downright hilarious. Animal photography is a labor of love that requires a lot of patience and it may take a great deal of time to capture that perfect moment. However, whether out of pure luck or preparedness, some talented wildlife photographers have successfully captured some perfectly timed animal photos. Most of these incredible shots of animals looking goofy are so unbelievable such that you would have missed the moment just by blinking.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>