<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Culture on Brainsation</title>
    <link>http://st.brainsation.com/tags/culture/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Culture on Brainsation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 21:30:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://st.brainsation.com/tags/culture/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The &#39;Most Beautiful Girl in the World&#39; Is All Grown Up Now...</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-most-beautiful-girl-in-the-world-is-all-grown-up-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 21:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-most-beautiful-girl-in-the-world-is-all-grown-up-now/</guid>
      <description>The 16-year-old model who was dubbed the “most beautiful girl in the world” at the age of six walked the catwalk for Dolce &amp;amp; Gabbana at Milan Fashion Week in a 2017 &amp;ldquo;secret&amp;rdquo; off-schedule show. Thylane Blondeau found fame at the tender age of four after she made her fashion debut on Jean Paul Gaultier&amp;rsquo;s runway and appeared in several iconic photo shoots. The French teen is now signed with IMG models and boasts more than 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remember the Strongest Boy in the World? -- Fifteen Years Later, He&#39;s All Grown Up...</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/remember-the-strongest-boy-in-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 21:07:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/remember-the-strongest-boy-in-the-world/</guid>
      <description>Once known as the &amp;ldquo;world’s strongest boy,&amp;rdquo; Richard Sandrak&amp;rsquo;s childhood was an endless routine of grueling training sessions, strict diets, and emotional abuse from his father. As a four-year-old, he was doing 600 sit-ups and push-ups a day and bench-pressing over three times his body weight. But for all his accomplishments in the gym, Sandrak grew up knowing only a life of intense training and discipline.
 &amp;ldquo;I didn&amp;rsquo;t really have a childhood,&amp;rdquo; said Sandrak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>40 Incredible Photos Where The Timing Was Just Perfect</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/40-incredible-photos-where-the-timing-was-just-perfect/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 17:02:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/40-incredible-photos-where-the-timing-was-just-perfect/</guid>
      <description>twitter
You might be the best photographer there is out there but sometimes, you don’t have to be the best to take a perfect photo. You just need to be at the right place in the right moment. It will not matter if you take it with a phone or a very good camera; you just need to be passionate about what you do. Most of the time, you won’t even notice you took an awesome photo till you sit down to look at them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Check Out These Latest Air Travel Nightmares!</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/air-travel-nightmares/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 18:10:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/air-travel-nightmares/</guid>
      <description>So far, the year of 2018 has been a miserable experience for airline passengers, inflight staff, and the carriers that operate more than 87,000 flights in the continental U.S. every single day. From dead pets to exotic stowaways, flying the friendly skies can often feel more like riding a rollercoaster. To ease your pre-flight anxieties, we&amp;rsquo;ve put together an epic list of the top ten air travel debacles since New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Just Got Dark: The Hidden Island Park They Want To Keep Secret</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/disney-hidden-island/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 18:04:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/disney-hidden-island/</guid>
      <description>A courageous photographer went deep undercover to show the grim truth behind the Disney parks. Little did we know that part of Disney&amp;rsquo;s magic is dark magic.
Walt Disney himself has experienced his fair share of infamy. His anti-semitism is widely known, so it&amp;rsquo;s not surprising that even more secrets are right near the parks.
The place commonly known as the &amp;ldquo;happiest place on Earth&amp;rdquo; may be the exact opposite for some people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crime Researcher Releases Shocking Fact About Number of Serial Killers in US</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/crime-researcher-releases-shocking-fact-about-number-of-serial-killers-in-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 16:01:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/crime-researcher-releases-shocking-fact-about-number-of-serial-killers-in-us/</guid>
      <description>Vox[/caption] “The taste of death that lives within He loves it when he Tastes their final breath Stalking gives him pleasure Killing is the final act He takes no pity With his lust for death.” &amp;mdash;-’Psycho Man’, Ozzy Osbourne The recent arrest of the notorious Golden State Killer, a man now identified as 72-year-old Joseph James DeAngelo Jr, caused the resurfacing of our society’s recurrent predations by serial killers. DeAngelo operated for over a decade, from the 1970s to the 1980s, terrorizing parts of California with his ten murders and 46 known rapes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Man Emerges As Vietnam War Soldier Missing For 40 Years</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/man-emerges-as-vietnam-war-soldier-missing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 17:46:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/man-emerges-as-vietnam-war-soldier-missing/</guid>
      <description>The Vietnam war came to an end in 1975, leaving countless men lost or presumed dead. One soldier, Army Sgt. 1st Class John Hartley Robinson, was assumed to be one of the men who became a prisoner of war of the Vietcong or to have lost his life in battle. Then, nearly 40 years later, a man turned up claiming to be Army Sgt. 1st Class Robinson. He told stories of living a life in secret in the Vietnamese jungle after the war ended until he was found in 2008.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When 3 Conservatives Stop Into This Liberal Restaurant For Lunch, The Waitress Is In For A Big Surprise</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/when-3-conservatives-stop-into-this-liberal-restaurant-for-lunch-the-waitress-is-in-for-a-big-surprise/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 17:43:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/when-3-conservatives-stop-into-this-liberal-restaurant-for-lunch-the-waitress-is-in-for-a-big-surprise/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve all heard the old adage &amp;ldquo;never judge a book by its cover,&amp;rdquo; but the truth is we&amp;rsquo;re constantly making judgments about people and things around us. Most of the time it&amp;rsquo;s without even realizing it, just an automatic thing. You see someone wearing certain clothes or who looks a certain way and assume you know something about them. Rosalynd Harris thought she knew all about the three men who were seated in her section of the restaurant that afternoon just by the hats they were wearing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insane Pictures Of The Most Flexible Girls In The World</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/insane-pictures-of-the-most-flexible-girls-in-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 04:24:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/insane-pictures-of-the-most-flexible-girls-in-the-world/</guid>
      <description>Although the human body is incredibly resilient in terms of what it can endure, most people aren&amp;rsquo;t very flexible. Mastering the art of contortion takes a lot of training and good, rubbery genes. Many factors are taken into account when establishing personal flexibility: joint structure, ligaments, tendons, muscles, skin, tissue injury, fat (or adipose) tissue, body temperature, activity level, age and sex all influence an individual&amp;rsquo;s range of motion about a joint.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just Some Pics Of Girls Wearing Yoga Pants To Help Brighten Your Day</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/just-some-pics-of-girls-wearing-yoga-pants-to-help-brighten-your-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 19:44:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/just-some-pics-of-girls-wearing-yoga-pants-to-help-brighten-your-day/</guid>
      <description>pantso When you think of art, you probably don&amp;rsquo;t immediately think about the female body, even though it&amp;rsquo;s what 90% of art throughout history is based on. Sometimes the natural beauty of the everyday real world is right in front of you, possibly in downward-facing dog position. Though we&amp;rsquo;re not the type to mess with perfection, adding a pair of yoga pants to a beautiful body is an undeniable improvement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oops! These Are The Most Awkward &#39;Walk Of Shame&#39; Photos We&#39;ve Ever Seen</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/oops-these-are-the-most-awkward-walk-of-shame-photos-weve-ever-seen/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 06:56:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/oops-these-are-the-most-awkward-walk-of-shame-photos-weve-ever-seen/</guid>
      <description>sickchirpse Everyone likes to party now and then to let off some steam and get crazy with friends. What you have to remember when you&amp;rsquo;re partying, however, is how you&amp;rsquo;re planning to get home the next day! Not everyone knows exactly where they&amp;rsquo;ll end up the night of a party, and the next day, they&amp;rsquo;re forced to do the Walk of Shame. From the heels they&amp;rsquo;re still wearing to the messy hair, you can tell these ladies got down with their bad selves last night, and who knows what kind of trouble they got into.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>These Politicians Are Popular, But Their Kids Are Absolute Nightmares</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/these-politicians-are-popular-but-their-kids-are-absolute-nightmares/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 01:55:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/these-politicians-are-popular-but-their-kids-are-absolute-nightmares/</guid>
      <description>dailymail We tend to hold those in political power to a higher standard than we do ourselves. We see them as the golden moral pillars of society; perfect humans who never so much as double park. Why? Great question. Politicians and the people that surround them are, in fact, normal humans. Hence, they are susceptible to the same struggles and moral failings as anyone, and that means that they can be pretty crappy parents sometimes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Amazingly Perfectly Timed Photos</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/timed-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 20:04:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/timed-photos/</guid>
      <description>twitter
You might be the best photographer there is out there but sometimes, you don’t have to be the best to take a perfect photo. You just need to be at the right place in the right moment. It will not matter if you take it with a phone or a very good camera; you just need to be passionate about what you do. Most of the time, you won’t even notice you took an awesome photo till you sit down to look at them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Cancer Symptoms You Should Not Ignore!</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-cancer-symptoms-you-should-not-ignore/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 21:59:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-cancer-symptoms-you-should-not-ignore/</guid>
      <description>Cancer is a disease that comes with very few visible symptoms. It is always good to have it detected early before it spreads to others parts of the body. It is curable if diagnosed in its initial stages. There are cancer symptoms that you should not ignore, and that means you see need your doctor for immediate cancer screening. It will help you start treatment on time or even prevent the disease.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>21 Rare Vietnam War Photos You Never Knew Existed</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/21-rare-vietnam-war-photos-you-never-knew-existed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/21-rare-vietnam-war-photos-you-never-knew-existed/</guid>
      <description>The Vietnam War remains to be one of the most controversial and deadliest in the world’s history especially the United States. The war lasted for 20 years and claimed approximately 3.5 million lives. It is estimated that about 60,000 of those who died were Americans who were fighting the Soviet Union. The cold war was based on the fact that the Soviet Union had to be stopped due to its political influence as well as the spread of its communism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 20 Smartest Presidents of All Time (And Where Trump Ranks Among Them)</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/top-20-smartest-presidents-of-all-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/top-20-smartest-presidents-of-all-time/</guid>
      <description>In 2006 Dean Simonton, psychology professor at University of California at Davis, finished researching the &amp;ldquo;intellectual brilliance&amp;rdquo; of 42 U.S. presidents. Some presidents pre-dated modern IQ testing. So Simonton estimated their scores with personality traits referenced in their biographies that indicate an above-average level of intelligence ­‑‑ &amp;ldquo;wise,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;inventive,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;artistic,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;curious,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;sophisticated,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;complicated,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;insightful.” From that study, we compiled a list of the top 20 smartest presidents. And where the current President (Donald Trump) ranks among them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 20 Celebs You Didn&#39;t Know Were Gay</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/top-20-celebs-you-didnt-know-were-gay/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 18:31:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/top-20-celebs-you-didnt-know-were-gay/</guid>
      <description>Many movie stars and artists are in gay relationships. Even though they try to keep their private life away from the public domain, they are eventually exposed. However, there are those who embrace who they are by admitting to the world that they are gay. Below is a list of 20 celebrities who you didn&amp;rsquo;t know were gay.
1. Tom Daley 
DailyStar Tom used a homemade video to break his silence regarding his relationship status.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Lame To Fame: Amazing Celebrity Transformations That&#39;ll Make You Double-Take!</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/from-lame-to-fame-amazing-celebrity-transformations-thatll-make-you-double-take/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 18:47:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/from-lame-to-fame-amazing-celebrity-transformations-thatll-make-you-double-take/</guid>
      <description>Stars grow up just like regular people. Plus, with the added pressure from fans and critics, it makes sense that celebrities would want to change a few things every now and again. From weight loss to total make overs, these 30 stars have had the biggest transformations of our time.

BET
Jonah Hill - 2016 
InTouch
Jonah Hill has become rather well known for his rapid weight fluctuations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game of Thrones Characters - How They Are Described in Book and How They Appear on TV</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/game-of-thrones-characters-how-they-are-described-in-book-and-how-they-appear-on-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 19:36:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/game-of-thrones-characters-how-they-are-described-in-book-and-how-they-appear-on-tv/</guid>
      <description>Lovers of HBO’s TV series Game of Thrones who have read George R.R Martin’s book _A Song of Ice and Fire_ upon which the series is based, acknowledge the fact that key differences exist between the characters in the book and TV series. Naturally, the nature of the medium allows some changes to take place as we transit from the books to a television show. Even as the show continues to develop through season 7, the differences between the book version and the show become more pronounced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harrowing Confession Might Finally Crack Natalee Holloway Case</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/harrowing-confession-might-finally-crack-natalee-holloway-case/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 15:28:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/harrowing-confession-might-finally-crack-natalee-holloway-case/</guid>
      <description>Hollywoodlife In 2005, Alabama teen Natalee Holloway disappeared during her graduation trip in the Carribean island of Aruba. 12 years since Natalee went missing, the crime still remains unsolved. However, recent developments that have surfaced may offer new clues regarding her disappearance. Will this case full of mystery and intrigue finally be solved soon?
An Alabama Girl Hollywoodlife In 1986, Natalee was born in Clinton, Mississippi to David and Beth Holloway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Abandoned, Slowly Decaying Cruise Ship Given New Life With These Amazing Photos</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/abandoned-cruise-ship/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 18:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/abandoned-cruise-ship/</guid>
      <description>On January 13, 2012, a cruise ship hit an underwater rock formation off the coast of Tuscany. The Costa Concordia capsized, killing a total of 31 passengers and one crew member. In 2016, a photographer by the name of Jonathan Danko Kielkowski illegally swam out to the ship in order to take some photos. Here is a look at some of the amazing, eerie footage that he was able to capture once he climbed onboard&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Employee&#39;s Cruise Disappearance 5 Years Ago Still Unsolved</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/missing-disney-cruise-line-crew-member/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 23:56:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/missing-disney-cruise-line-crew-member/</guid>
      <description>Embarking on a Disney cruise is intended to be a once in a lifetime experience, including character visits and excitement at every turn. Every aspect of the journey—from the food to the entertainment—is magical, but the disappearance of a ship&amp;rsquo;s employee in 2011 brought the joyful voyage to a sudden halt. The tragic disappearance of employee Rebecca Coriam on the cruise ship the Wonder in 2011 is still unexplained to this day, but there have been a couple of encouraging new breaks in the case that took our breath away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artsy, Clever Vandalism That&#39;ll Make You Look At Your Dull World Differently</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/times-vandalism-improved-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 03:12:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/times-vandalism-improved-things/</guid>
      <description>and expensive way to ruin the environment around us and just means that resources are diverted away from more important matters just to tidy the place up. However, at its finest, vandalism can also be high art and truly capture some insight into the human condition. These pics don&amp;rsquo;t show that kind of vandalism, but it is the kind that makes you laugh when you see it. These vandals weren&amp;rsquo;t out to change the world, they were just out to make your day brighter!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>