<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Crime on Brainsation</title>
    <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/tags/crime/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Crime on Brainsation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 21:05:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/tags/crime/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>After Biohacker&#39;s Sudden Death, Followers are Wondering, &#34;What&#39;s Next?&#34;</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/after-biohackers-sudden-death-followers-are-wondering-whats-next/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 21:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/after-biohackers-sudden-death-followers-are-wondering-whats-next/</guid>
      <description>Law enforcement officials were called to a spa in Washington, D.C. on May 6. Once they arrived on scene they discovered the body of 28-year-old Ascendance Biomedical founder Aaron Traywick in a flotation therapy tank, reports Independent. Traywick gained recent notoriety when he injected himself with an untested herpes drug while in front of an audience. Traywick and his company advocated for biohacking, a broad term applied to methods of treating disease or overall health without the aid of pharmaceutical products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scientist: $180 Kit Can Help Criminals Avoid Prosecution</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/scientist-180-kit-can-help-criminals-avoid-prosecution/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 18:21:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/scientist-180-kit-can-help-criminals-avoid-prosecution/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been over a century since the police started using fingerprint evidence to solve crimes. As a work around, criminals simply started wearing gloves or wiping down whatever they touched at a crime scene. DNA is much more pervasive. A hair at a crime scene or dead skin under a victim&amp;rsquo;s fingernails could be matched to a criminal with DNA analysis, and there was nothing the bad guys could do about it, until now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Criminal Gangs Use High Tech to Fight the FBI</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/criminal-gangs-use-high-tech-to-fight-the-fbi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 02:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/criminal-gangs-use-high-tech-to-fight-the-fbi/</guid>
      <description>Last winter at an undisclosed town in the United States, officials with the Federal Bureau of Investigation&amp;rsquo;s hostage rescue unit moved in to begin an extraction operation. Agents fanned out around the scene, some in obvious positions while others sat or lay concealed in other spots.
Digital Addicts Blog Not long after arriving on scene and staging personnel, the FBI team was harassed by a swarm of drones that made &amp;ldquo;high-speed, low passes at agents in the observation post&amp;rdquo; in an attempt to flush them out and prevent the Bureau from having eyes on the scene.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Authorities Raid Poacher&#39;s House in Madagascar - Agents Shocked at What They Found</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/authorities-raid-poachers-house-in-madagascar-agents-shocked-at-what-they-found/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 18:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/authorities-raid-poachers-house-in-madagascar-agents-shocked-at-what-they-found/</guid>
      <description>Wikimedia Commons[/caption] An emergency visit by a team from Madagascar’s environmental agency as well as police to a home in Toliara recently uncovered what looks to be a smuggling operation of epic proportions. As agents from the government descended on the abode, following complaints from neighbors of a rancid smell coming from the two story building, they interrupted the work of three people in the process of burying deceased radiated tortoises.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Missing Son Comes Home 3 Years Later (Except It Isn&#39;t Him)</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/missing-son-comes-home-3-years-later/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 20:53:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/missing-son-comes-home-3-years-later/</guid>
      <description>YouTube The year was 1994 when Nicholas Barclay, a 13-year-old boy, completely vanished from his San Antonio home. For over three years, Nicholas remained a ghost and his parents and even the authorities had no leads on where he disappeared to. One day, the family received an unsettling phone call. It was a boy in Spain who claimed to be Nicholas. Who was this boy, actually? Keep reading to find out the shocking truth!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harrowing Confession Might Finally Crack Natalee Holloway Case</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/harrowing-confession-might-finally-crack-natalee-holloway-case/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 15:28:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/harrowing-confession-might-finally-crack-natalee-holloway-case/</guid>
      <description>Hollywoodlife In 2005, Alabama teen Natalee Holloway disappeared during her graduation trip in the Carribean island of Aruba. 12 years since Natalee went missing, the crime still remains unsolved. However, recent developments that have surfaced may offer new clues regarding her disappearance. Will this case full of mystery and intrigue finally be solved soon?
An Alabama Girl Hollywoodlife In 1986, Natalee was born in Clinton, Mississippi to David and Beth Holloway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It Took 45 Years For &#39;The Keepers&#39; Investigators To Rule This Out</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/the-keepers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 18:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/the-keepers/</guid>
      <description>Netflix Some cases become so mystifying that they become lost in the shuffle. Others tend to be dusted off with even a morsel of new evidence presented. The case you&amp;rsquo;re about to read about became so bizarre that it&amp;rsquo;s the subject of a new documentary. The subject of this case had big dreams as a high schooler&amp;hellip;
The Brightest In The Room Netflix Born in Lawrenceville, Pennsylvania, Sister Catherine &amp;ldquo;Cathy&amp;rdquo; Cesnik was one of the smartest kids in St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Texas Teens Disappeared 30 Years Ago. Today, Cops Got A New Lead</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/two-texas-teens-disappeared/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 17:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/two-texas-teens-disappeared/</guid>
      <description>Facebook For law enforcement, nothing is worse than when a murder case goes old. The public is begging for answers, the family for closure, and the system for justice. But sometimes there&amp;rsquo;s just not enough evidence. Like with the 1988 murder of two Texas teenagers in what investigators considered a possible religious (read Satanic) ritual. But their story isn&amp;rsquo;t over by a long shot. Now 30 years later, Texas police have made an arrest that just so happened to uncover new evidence in one of the state&amp;rsquo;s most grisly cold cases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Missing Son Comes Home 3 Years Later (Except It Isn&#39;t Him)</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/missing-son-comes-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 17:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/missing-son-comes-home/</guid>
      <description>YouTube The year was 1994 when Nicholas Barclay, a 13-year-old boy, completely vanished from his San Antonio home. For over three years, Nicholas remained a ghost and his parents and even the authorities had no leads on where he disappeared to. One day, the family received an unsettling phone call. It was a boy in Spain who claimed to be Nicholas. Who was this boy, actually? Keep reading to find out the shocking truth!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>