<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Trending on Brainsation</title>
    <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/tags/trending/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Trending on Brainsation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 17:46:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/tags/trending/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Man Emerges As Vietnam War Soldier Missing For 40 Years</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/man-emerges-as-vietnam-war-soldier-missing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 17:46:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/man-emerges-as-vietnam-war-soldier-missing/</guid>
      <description>The Vietnam war came to an end in 1975, leaving countless men lost or presumed dead. One soldier, Army Sgt. 1st Class John Hartley Robinson, was assumed to be one of the men who became a prisoner of war of the Vietcong or to have lost his life in battle. Then, nearly 40 years later, a man turned up claiming to be Army Sgt. 1st Class Robinson. He told stories of living a life in secret in the Vietnamese jungle after the war ended until he was found in 2008.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>15 Marvel Actresses Who Sizzle On And Off The Screen</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/15-marvel-actresses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 06:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/15-marvel-actresses/</guid>
      <description>All too often, the men of the Marvel universe take center stage. It makes sense on the surface of things, given that most superheroes are men. In the past few decades, however, our superheroine sisters have all been busy making names for themselves and changing the landscape of comic-inspired cinema. The Marvel-verse couldn&amp;rsquo;t survive without the women behind it, and those heroines wouldn&amp;rsquo;t exist without the indomitable actors who brought them to life on the big screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>15 Of The Sexiest Women In American Sports</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/15-of-the-sexiest-women-in-american-sports/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 09:28:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/15-of-the-sexiest-women-in-american-sports/</guid>
      <description>With the 2018 Winter Olympics coming to a close, I&amp;rsquo;m sure many of us are left wondering how so many of our highest-achieving athletes can also be graced with such good looks. We haven&amp;rsquo;t yet come up with the formula for Olympian success, but we did come up with a list of the 15 hottest female American athletes for you to swoon over.
Allison Stokke Cleverst Track and field athlete Allison Stokke got her start during school, breaking a number of American records for high school pole vaulting.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>