<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Brainsation</title>
    <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Brainsation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 17:58:59 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://st.brainsation.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>test</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 17:58:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/test/</guid>
      <description>test pages for subpages</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meghan Markle Makes Royal Faux Pas In Awkward Moment With Queen Elizabeth</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/meghan-markle-makes-royal-faux-pas-in-awkward-moment-with-queen-elizabeth/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 05:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/meghan-markle-makes-royal-faux-pas-in-awkward-moment-with-queen-elizabeth/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Of course, she&amp;rsquo;s a novice when it comes to protocol,&amp;rdquo; said a Buckingham Palace insider. &amp;ldquo;She&amp;rsquo;s having to learn all this as she goes. The Duchess of Cambridge was a natural, however, Meghan Markle seems rather dense by comparison.&amp;rdquo; Meghan Markle had her first joint appearance with Queen Elizabeth on Thursday, but unfortunately for her, she didn&amp;rsquo;t impress anyone with her understanding of royal protocol.

Image Credit &amp;ldquo;She looked like a fool,&amp;rdquo; said Ashley Winslow, a reporter for the BBC who was present for incident.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kate Middleton Refuses To Make Same Mistake With Prince Louis That She Did With Charlotte -- She’s Not Backing Down…</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/kate-middleton-refuses-to-make-same-mistake-with-prince-louis-that-she-did-with-charlotte-shes-not-backing-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 05:30:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/kate-middleton-refuses-to-make-same-mistake-with-prince-louis-that-she-did-with-charlotte-shes-not-backing-down/</guid>
      <description>On April 23rd of this year, Prince William and his wife Kate Middleton happily welcomed their third child, Prince Louis, into this world. Several hours after his birth, Louis was presented to the public when the Duke and Duchess of Cambridge stepped out of the Lindo Wing and allowed the press to photograph the newborn as he slept. Afterwards, Kate returned to her home at Kensington Palace with Louis to rest and recover.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bodybuilder Does What It Takes To Look Like The Incredible Hulk</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/bodybuilder-does-what-it-takes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 22:07:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/bodybuilder-does-what-it-takes/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s nothing out of the ordinary about wanting to tweak your appearance a bit, but for most people, there are boundaries. While some are just getting used to the idea of surgery, others are pushing the boundaries of safety in order to max out their look. There is perhaps no better example of this than Valdir Segato, the body builder with a risky goal in mind.
1. Humble Beginnings Mirror Now famous for his abnormally-bulging muscles, Valdir Segato wasn&amp;rsquo;t always spending large portions of his everyday routine focusing on his looks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The &#39;Most Beautiful Girl in the World&#39; Is All Grown Up Now...</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-most-beautiful-girl-in-the-world-is-all-grown-up-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 21:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-most-beautiful-girl-in-the-world-is-all-grown-up-now/</guid>
      <description>The 16-year-old model who was dubbed the “most beautiful girl in the world” at the age of six walked the catwalk for Dolce &amp;amp; Gabbana at Milan Fashion Week in a 2017 &amp;ldquo;secret&amp;rdquo; off-schedule show. Thylane Blondeau found fame at the tender age of four after she made her fashion debut on Jean Paul Gaultier&amp;rsquo;s runway and appeared in several iconic photo shoots. The French teen is now signed with IMG models and boasts more than 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remember the Strongest Boy in the World? -- Fifteen Years Later, He&#39;s All Grown Up...</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/remember-the-strongest-boy-in-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 21:07:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/remember-the-strongest-boy-in-the-world/</guid>
      <description>Once known as the &amp;ldquo;world’s strongest boy,&amp;rdquo; Richard Sandrak&amp;rsquo;s childhood was an endless routine of grueling training sessions, strict diets, and emotional abuse from his father. As a four-year-old, he was doing 600 sit-ups and push-ups a day and bench-pressing over three times his body weight. But for all his accomplishments in the gym, Sandrak grew up knowing only a life of intense training and discipline.
 &amp;ldquo;I didn&amp;rsquo;t really have a childhood,&amp;rdquo; said Sandrak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stunned Grandma Learns &#39;Puppy&#39; That Never Barked and Hated Dog Food Is Actually a...</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/stunned-grandma/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 20:13:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/stunned-grandma/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;I was told that he was a Japanese Spitz puppy,&amp;rdquo; said Mrs. Wang. &amp;ldquo;But I knew that something was strange about the animal. He never ate dog food. Not once. And he never barked either.&amp;rdquo; When a grandmother in China visited her neighborhood pet shop looking for a companion, she was originally considering a cat. She thought a feline would be trouble-free and &amp;ldquo;more independent than a dog.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>40 Incredible Photos Where The Timing Was Just Perfect</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/40-incredible-photos-where-the-timing-was-just-perfect/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 17:02:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/40-incredible-photos-where-the-timing-was-just-perfect/</guid>
      <description>twitter
You might be the best photographer there is out there but sometimes, you don’t have to be the best to take a perfect photo. You just need to be at the right place in the right moment. It will not matter if you take it with a phone or a very good camera; you just need to be passionate about what you do. Most of the time, you won’t even notice you took an awesome photo till you sit down to look at them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conjoined Twins Stun Fans With Huge Announcement: &#39;We&#39;ve Prayed About It...&#39;</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/conjoined-twins-stun-their-fans/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 18:35:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/conjoined-twins-stun-their-fans/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Of course we&amp;rsquo;ve thought about this long and hard,&amp;rdquo; said Abby Hensel. &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;ve prayed about it and we&amp;rsquo;re confident that this is the right decision for us.&amp;rdquo; Her sister Brittany added, &amp;ldquo;You only live once and we just feel like it&amp;rsquo;s time.&amp;rdquo; Sisters Abby and Brittany Hensel are conjoined twins that have been defying expectations since the day they made their debut into this world. When they were born, they made international headlines for being one of the very few conjoined twins to survive the pregnancy and delivery processes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Major Cancer Breakthrough - Blood Test Detects Disease Years Before It Occurs</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/major-cancer-breakthrough-blood-test-detects-disease-years-before-it-occurs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 21:42:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/major-cancer-breakthrough-blood-test-detects-disease-years-before-it-occurs/</guid>
      <description>One of the major factors in treating cancer is catching the disease early enough to attack it and stop it from spreading. Well, scientists from England have found a way to catch some types of cancer before they even start.
Health.mil Experts are hailing this as a major breakthrough in humanity&amp;rsquo;s continued fight against the dreaded disease. Here&amp;rsquo;s more from The Independent website: A new blood test that allows doctors to detect 10 types of cancer years before a person becomes sick with the disease has been developed by scientists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Explosion Rocks Kilauea - Triggers Earthquake &amp; Ash Cloud 1 Mile High</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/explosion-rocks-kilauea-triggers-earthquake-ash-cloud-1-mile-high/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 21:27:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/explosion-rocks-kilauea-triggers-earthquake-ash-cloud-1-mile-high/</guid>
      <description>Kilauea still remains very active and today was rocked by a massive explosion that sent a plume of ash 1 mile up into the atmosphere. In addition, the geothermal fireworks triggered an earthquake that measured 5.5 on the Richter scale. The good news is that that&amp;rsquo;s strong enough to cause a tsunami.
EPA
The USGS Volcano team Tweeted out the following:
Kīlauea Message Tue, 05 Jun 2018 04:50:56 HST: A small explosion occurred at Kīlauea&amp;rsquo;s summit at 4:32 AM HST.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>53 Yrs Ago This Week, Gemini Astronauts Took the Best UFO Picture Ever</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/53-yrs-ago-this-week-gemini-astronauts-took-the-best-ufo-picture-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 20:38:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/53-yrs-ago-this-week-gemini-astronauts-took-the-best-ufo-picture-ever/</guid>
      <description>In June of 1965 astronauts James McDivitt and Ed Pilot took part in the Gemini IV mission launched by NASA. The purpose of the mission was to show that humans could stay in space for extended lengths of time. It was the 2nd manned Gemini space flight and the 10th manned spaceflight by the US.
Wikimedia Commons For four days, McDivitt and White circled the Earth 66 times, and even took the first spacewalk ever by an American astronaut, as White floated free outside of the spacecraft for about 20 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You Know This Heimlich Maneuver for Dogs?</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/do-you-know-this-heimlich-maneuver-for-dogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 20:25:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/do-you-know-this-heimlich-maneuver-for-dogs/</guid>
      <description>It seems most humans love their dogs more than they love themselves. Well, at least we usually treat our dog&amp;rsquo;s bodies better than our own. We put off doctor visits for ourselves, but never miss one for out pets. And while we make sure they have the best pet food we can give them, we &amp;ldquo;wolf down&amp;rdquo; (pun intended) whatever food is fast and convenient. This technique started making the rounds on the Internet after a Twitter user whose dog had choked on a piece of plastic Tweeted out instructions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NASA Hacked a Workaround for Mars Rover&#39;s Broken Drill -- And It&#39;s Brilliant</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/nasa-hacked-a-workaround-for-mars-rovers-broken-drill-and-its-brilliant/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 18:32:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/nasa-hacked-a-workaround-for-mars-rovers-broken-drill-and-its-brilliant/</guid>
      <description>Ever break a tool you need for work when you&amp;rsquo;re 33.9 million miles away from home? Well, NASA&amp;rsquo;s Mars rover did, and ever since December of 2016, it&amp;rsquo;s been unable to do its job. But, after over a year of brainstorming and hacking by the folks over at the Jet Propulsion Laboratory (JPL), the rover is once again hard at work collecting and analyzing samples from the Martian terrain in its onboard laboratory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Nursing Shortage Reaching the Crisis Level - This is Not Good</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/us-nursing-shortage-reaching-the-crisis-level-this-is-not-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 17:35:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/us-nursing-shortage-reaching-the-crisis-level-this-is-not-good/</guid>
      <description>One quick perusal for Google news and you&amp;rsquo;ll see dozens of articles from all across the country warning that the current nursing shortage is real, and that it&amp;rsquo;s only going to get worse. In Texas and Florida, the state legislatures are being called upon to fix the problem, and local stories from Connecticut to Green Bay, WI, to Phoenix, AZ show that communities everywhere are worried about the problem.
Flickr But what&amp;rsquo;s behind this?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>23 Yr Old Dutch Inventor&#39;s Bold Plan to Clean Up the Pacific - It Just Might Work</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/23-yr-old-dutch-inventors-bold-plan-to-clean-up-the-pacific-it-just-might-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 15:55:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/23-yr-old-dutch-inventors-bold-plan-to-clean-up-the-pacific-it-just-might-work/</guid>
      <description>Environmental remediation has various forms. Some companies focus on ridding older homes and buildings of asbestos related materials, some provide deep cleaning services to hospitals and other environments, and some crews are dispersed to the scene of environmental disasters, such as oil slicks, to try and clean up the environment and return it to its natural state.
Flickr The environmental remediation experts at The Ocean Cleanup have a different and more focused target in mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breathtaking Images from Atop the Great Pyramid of Giza [Photos &amp; Video]</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/breathtaking-images-from-atop-the-great-pyramid-of-giza-photos-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 14:55:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/breathtaking-images-from-atop-the-great-pyramid-of-giza-photos-video/</guid>
      <description>In case you were wondering, scaling the side of the Great Pyramid of Giza with your buddies is a big No-No. In fact, the Russian teenagers who pulled off this stunt faced criminal charges and even jail time for their feat. And while we in no way whatsoever condone what they did &amp;ndash; especially to a treasured monument like the Great Pyramid, we&amp;rsquo;ve got to say that the photos they came back with are nothing short of spectacular!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tiny Ancient Bird Mummy Turns Out to Be a Human</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/tiny-ancient-bird-mummy-turns-out-to-be-a-human/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 21:10:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/tiny-ancient-bird-mummy-turns-out-to-be-a-human/</guid>
      <description>Mummified animal remains weren&amp;rsquo;t all that rare in ancient Egypt. In fact, over the years, scientists have encountered snake, cat, crocodile, and dog mummies. So, when a mummified hawk was discovered, scientists just added it to the collection thinking it was just another prized pet, only it wasn&amp;rsquo;t a hawk. Here&amp;rsquo;s the story from CNET.com:
YouTube Bioarchaeologist Andrew Nelson of Western University in Canada undertook a much more in-depth study of the artifact with &amp;ldquo;the highest-resolution scan ever conducted of a fetal mummy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Just Detected a Particle That Shouldn&#39;t Even Exist</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientists-just-detected-a-particle-that-shouldnt-even-exist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 17:20:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientists-just-detected-a-particle-that-shouldnt-even-exist/</guid>
      <description>Neutrinos are mysterious particles that have the ability to pass through matter without interacting with it at all. Scientists have theorized about them for decades, but have been unable to turn up any concrete evidence to prove they exist. Until now. Here&amp;rsquo;s more from LiveScience.com:
Octanis.org Back in the mid-1990s, the Liquid Scintillator Neutrino Detector (LSND), an experiment at Los Alamos National Laboratory in New Mexico, found evidence of a mysterious new particle: a &amp;ldquo;sterile neutrino&amp;rdquo; that passes through matter without interacting with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asteroid Discovered Saturday Morning Entered Atmosphere Later That Night</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/asteroid-discovered-saturday-morning-entered-atmosphere-later-that-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 16:20:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/asteroid-discovered-saturday-morning-entered-atmosphere-later-that-night/</guid>
      <description>People in South Africa got quite the light show on Saturday night as an asteroid, discovered just hours before, entered Earth&amp;rsquo;s atmosphere in lit up the night sky in a spectacular display. Here&amp;rsquo;s more on the story from EarthSky.org:
YouTube Screenshot The International Astronomical Union has now confirmed that a small asteroid – discovered Saturday morning, June 2, 2018 – entered Earth’s atmosphere later that day. The asteroid was originally designated ZLAF9B2 and is now officially called 2018 LA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>500&#43; Earthquakes Around Kilauea - Is Something Big About to Happen?</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/500-earthquakes-around-kilauea-is-something-big-about-to-happen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 14:43:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/500-earthquakes-around-kilauea-is-something-big-about-to-happen/</guid>
      <description>As our hearts go out to the volcano victims in Guatemala, we&amp;rsquo;re reminded every day of the ticking time bomb that is Kilauea in Hawaii. To add to the drama, the big island of Hawaii was hit with a rash of earthquakes yesterday, with the most intense one measuring 5.5 on the Richter scale.
USGS With an earthquake that strong, there&amp;rsquo;s always the fear that it will create a tsunami, but officials said that they did not expect that to be the case with this one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It Blew - Deadly Eruption Kills 25, But It&#39;s Not Kilauea</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/it-blew-deadly-eruption-kills-25-but-its-not-kilauea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 13:55:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/it-blew-deadly-eruption-kills-25-but-its-not-kilauea/</guid>
      <description>The Earth has been pretty active of late. A record setting 500 earthquakes rocked the big island of Hawaii yesterday as lava continued to flow out of the Kilauea Volcano, but across the Pacific Ocean things got even more intense &amp;ndash; and deadly &amp;ndash; as Guatemala&amp;rsquo;s Fuego volcano erupted, injuring 300 people and killing 25.
By Travicted Photography - Flickr Here&amp;rsquo;s more from Reuters: &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s a river of lava that overflowed its banks and affected the El Rodeo village.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yale Educated Psychiatrist Stuns Colleagues: &#34;Demonic Possession is Real&#34;</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/yale-educated-psychiatrist-stuns-colleagues-demonic-possession-is-real/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 20:32:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/yale-educated-psychiatrist-stuns-colleagues-demonic-possession-is-real/</guid>
      <description>It seems everyday there&amp;rsquo;s another story of paranormal phenomena entering the mainstream of science and thought. Recently, our Navy&amp;rsquo;s encounter with the Tic Tac UFO that stalked on of our ships and was able to cloak itself into invisibility made the the rounds. This week, we get news that an Ivy League educated, mainstream psychiatrist has come forward to proclaim that demonic possession is real and that people seeking help should not be ignored.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drone Footage Reveals Mysterious New Cracks in Kilauea - Scientists Concerned</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/drone-footage-reveals-mysterious-new-cracks-in-kilauea-scientists-concerned/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 19:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/drone-footage-reveals-mysterious-new-cracks-in-kilauea-scientists-concerned/</guid>
      <description>If there&amp;rsquo;s one positive from this story it&amp;rsquo;s that the advent of drone technology has been very helpful in helping scientists evalulate the situation at Kilauea and anticipate what&amp;rsquo;s going to happen next. The bad news is that the recent drone footage scientists observed of the volcano&amp;rsquo;s crater indicates that something very, very bad is on its way.
USGS Basically, the new footage shows that one of Kilauea&amp;rsquo;s main craters has developed alarming new cracks, some of which are spewing out some pretty intense steam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This One Trick Saved Her Life &amp; Caused Harvard Researchers to Take Notice</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/this-one-trick-saved-her-life-caused-harvard-researchers-to-take-notice/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 18:54:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/this-one-trick-saved-her-life-caused-harvard-researchers-to-take-notice/</guid>
      <description>When a Kathy Bero of Delafield, Wisconsin was diagnosed with cancer, doctors set her prognosis for survival at 21 months. The then 41 year old mother of two tried surgery, chemotherapy, and radiation, all to no avail, and her condition was getting progressively worse.
Kathy Bero Website She was soon diagnosed with another tumor in her head and neck and the medication was taking a devastating toll on her body. Here&amp;rsquo;s more on her story from Hawaii News Now: &amp;ldquo;My kidneys were failing; my liver was failing,&amp;rdquo; Bero said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s Why a Massachusetts Judge Threw Out Thousands of Breathalyzer Tests</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/heres-why-a-massachusetts-judge-threw-out-thousands-of-breathalyzer-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 21:24:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/heres-why-a-massachusetts-judge-threw-out-thousands-of-breathalyzer-tests/</guid>
      <description>When a DUI attorney defends a client charged with drunk driving, the first thing a good lawyer will do is try to find a reason to get the charges dismissed.
Pixabay Did the arresting officer make a mistake? Was there an underlying medical condition which led to the defendant appearing drunk? Was there an inaccurate measurement of the alcohol level? While some people might scoff at these attempts as those of a sleazy lawyer trying to game the system, sometimes they actually do have merit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Miracle Mineral to Toxic Killer, The Strange Story of Asbestos</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/from-miracle-mineral-to-toxic-killer-the-strange-story-of-asbestos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 21:13:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/from-miracle-mineral-to-toxic-killer-the-strange-story-of-asbestos/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;ve watched any amount of cable television, you&amp;rsquo;ve likely been subjected to a barrage of commercials by mesothelioma lawyers and attorneys representing clients struck with that debilitating disease. What you may not know is that the mineral that was the cause of all those mesothelioma lawsuits had been hailed as a miracle substance as far back as the first century.
Asbestos Pit - Wikimedia Commons While many modern inventions at first seemed like good ideas before we discovered their toxic elements, the history of asbestos actually goes back over 4,000 years when inhabitants of what is now East Finland used anthophyllite, an asbestos minderal, to strengthen earthenware pots and cooking utensils.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Life Saving Hero Nurse of the Las Vegas Shooting</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-life-saving-hero-nurse-of-the-las-vegas-shooting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 20:38:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-life-saving-hero-nurse-of-the-las-vegas-shooting/</guid>
      <description>There are just some things they don&amp;rsquo;t teach you in nursing school. One is how to be a caring human being. The second is that, if you&amp;rsquo;re a caring human being, and you&amp;rsquo;re a nurse, you&amp;rsquo;re never really off the clock. Such is the case with Lorisa Loy a Las Vegas nurse who jumped into action last year during that city&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ndash; and this nation&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ndash; deadliest mass shooting at a country music concert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Her Cancer Treatment Was Shutting Down Her Organs, So She Did This Instead</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/her-cancer-treatment-was-shutting-down-her-organs-so-she-did-this-instead/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 19:31:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/her-cancer-treatment-was-shutting-down-her-organs-so-she-did-this-instead/</guid>
      <description>When a Kathy Bero of Delafield, Wisconsin was diagnosed with cancer, doctors set her prognosis for survival at 21 months. The then 41 year old mother of two tried surgery, chemotherapy, and radiation, all to no avail, and her condition was getting progressively worse.
Kathy Bero Website She was soon diagnosed with another tumor in her head and neck and the medication was taking a devastating toll on her body. Here&amp;rsquo;s more on her story from Hawaii News Now: &amp;ldquo;My kidneys were failing; my liver was failing,&amp;rdquo; Bero said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Addiction Rates are Off the Charts - Here&#39;s What You Can Do To Help</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/addiction-rates-are-off-the-charts-heres-what-you-can-do-to-help/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 18:45:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/addiction-rates-are-off-the-charts-heres-what-you-can-do-to-help/</guid>
      <description>The dark side of life in the 21st century is our societal proclivity toward addiction. From alcohol and opioids to video games, overeating, and porn, we live in a time where there&amp;rsquo;s a virtual cafeteria of addictions to choose from. While some may be seen as benign, others are downright deadly. PXHere Take opiod addiction for example. Here&amp;rsquo;s a little on the current epidemic we&amp;rsquo;re facing from the National Institute on Drug Abuse from drugabuse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Tic Tac&#34; UFO Baffles Experts - What Is This &amp; What Was It Doing?</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/tic-tac-ufo-baffles-experts-what-is-this-what-was-it-doing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 21:42:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/tic-tac-ufo-baffles-experts-what-is-this-what-was-it-doing/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday we had a story about how Blink-182 frontman Tom DeLonge has played a major roll in exposing some secret government UFO programs and pulling the curtain back on some incidents that our military had with UFO&amp;rsquo;s and have kept secret. The biggest encounter that DeLonge helped expose is the one our military had with some UFO&amp;rsquo;s off the coast of California in 2004. This story was also picked up and reported by the New York Times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii Mayor Issues Stern Warning in Lieu of Latest Kilauea Developments</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/hawaii-mayor-issues-stern-warning-in-lieu-of-latest-kilauea-developments/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 20:41:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/hawaii-mayor-issues-stern-warning-in-lieu-of-latest-kilauea-developments/</guid>
      <description>Things are literally heating up on the big island of Hawaii as the USGS reported on Thursday that lava bubbling to the surface is the hottest and most fluid that officials have seen since the volcano started erupting four weeks ago. The warned that the temperature is actually even hotter.
USGS Here&amp;rsquo;s more from FoxNews.com: “It’s hard to get to the center, which is the hottest portion of the fountain,” Stovall said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Semi Carrying 30 Million Bees Overturns in Texas</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/semi-carrying-30-million-bees-overturns-in-texas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 19:46:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/semi-carrying-30-million-bees-overturns-in-texas/</guid>
      <description>People in the vicinity of Paris, Texas have been advised to call authorities if they see a giant swarm of bees attached to anything on their property. This is because a semi truck hauling 15 - 30 million bees overturned on the highway this past Monday.
eParisExtra.com Here&amp;rsquo;s more from the CBSlocal.com: One witness said as her truck approached the scene, hundreds of bees buzzed around the vehicle. “It wasn’t enough to block out the sun, but we could tell it wasn’t normal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blood Test Can Detect Cancer Years Before Diagnosis - Hailed as Major Breakthrough</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/blood-test-can-detect-cancer-years-before-diagnosis-hailed-as-major-breakthrough/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 18:51:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/blood-test-can-detect-cancer-years-before-diagnosis-hailed-as-major-breakthrough/</guid>
      <description>One of the major factors in treating cancer is catching the disease early enough to attack it and stop it from spreading. Well, scientists from England have found a way to catch some types of cancer before they even start.
Health.mil Experts are hailing this as a major breakthrough in humanity&amp;rsquo;s continued fight against the dreaded disease. Here&amp;rsquo;s more from The Independent website: A new blood test that allows doctors to detect 10 types of cancer years before a person becomes sick with the disease has been developed by scientists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Target for a Major Earthquake is... London?</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/new-target-for-a-major-earthquake-is-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 16:42:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/new-target-for-a-major-earthquake-is-london/</guid>
      <description>When we think of earthquake zones, we think of the area along the unstable and constantly shifting Ring of Fire in the Pacific Ocean or along one of the many major fault lines that runs through California, but after a recent discover in England, scientists are saying that London may be in the running for a pretty strong earthquake as well.
Pixabay Here&amp;rsquo;s more from the Daily Mirror: Fault lines running under London could cause a magnitude five earthquake, scientists have warned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mesothelioma Patient is Alive Today Thanks to This North American Frog</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/mesothelioma-patient-is-alive-today-thanks-to-this-north-american-frog/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 16:12:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/mesothelioma-patient-is-alive-today-thanks-to-this-north-american-frog/</guid>
      <description>David Broyles thought he was going in for a routine hernia surgery. After all what could be wrong with him? He was young, owned his own construction company, was an avid competitive mountain biker, and felt indestructible. That&amp;rsquo;s why he was shocked when, after the surgery, his doctor told him to get his affairs in order because he had mesothelioma, a rare cancer caused by exposure to asbestos, and only had six months to live.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Massachusetts Marijuana Shops Open Their Doors on July 1 - Here&#39;s the Scoop</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/massachusetts-marijuana-shops-open-their-doors-on-july-1-heres-the-scoop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 19:36:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/massachusetts-marijuana-shops-open-their-doors-on-july-1-heres-the-scoop/</guid>
      <description>With each passing day, marijuana becomes less and less stygmatized. New studies are showing its effectiveness in treating a variety of medical conditions and, culturally, it&amp;rsquo;s becoming more accepted, like alcohol, as a an acceptable way to relax and unwind.
Public Domain As a result, the recreational and medical marijuana industries are booming and no place is this more apparent than in Massachusetts where voters approved the legal sale of the marijuana to anyone over 21 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The New Hallucinatory Drug: Staring Into Someone&#39;s Eyes for 10 Minutes</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-new-hallucinatory-drug-staring-into-someones-eyes-for-10-minutes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 17:57:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-new-hallucinatory-drug-staring-into-someones-eyes-for-10-minutes/</guid>
      <description>They say the eyes are windows to the soul, well according to this scientific study out of Italy, they&amp;rsquo;re also portals into completely altered states of consciousness. If this is true, then the illegal drug trade in this country may be in for some serious competition. From ScienceAlert.com:
Pixabay Not only did the deceptively simple task bring on strange &amp;lsquo;out of body&amp;rsquo; experiences for the volunteers, it also caused them to see hallucinations of monsters, their relatives, and themselves in their partner&amp;rsquo;s face.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blink 182 Frontman Helped Expose Pentagon&#39;s Secret UFO Program</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/blink-182-frontman-helped-expose-pentagons-secret-ufo-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 16:09:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/blink-182-frontman-helped-expose-pentagons-secret-ufo-program/</guid>
      <description>Music fans know Tom DeLonge as the frontman for the rock band Blink 182 but in the world of paranormal investigations, he&amp;rsquo;s a rock star of a whole different kind. It seems that since he was a teenager, DeLonge has been obsessed with UFO&amp;rsquo;s and the paranormal. In fact, when he got the money from his first big record contract, DeLonge used the funds to buy a computer so that he could research the possibility of extraterrestrial intelligent life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wisconsin Woman Take Cancer Treatment Into Her Own Hands, Now Harvard is Paying Attention</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/wisconsin-woman-take-cancer-treatment-into-her-own-hands-now-harvard-is-paying-attention/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 14:49:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/wisconsin-woman-take-cancer-treatment-into-her-own-hands-now-harvard-is-paying-attention/</guid>
      <description>When a Kathy Bero of Delafield, Wisconsin was diagnosed with cancer, doctors set her prognosis for survival at 21 months. The then 41 year old mother of two tried surgery, chemotherapy, and radiation, all to no avail, and her condition was getting progressively worse.
Kathy Bero Website She was soon diagnosed with another tumor in her head and neck and the medication was taking a devastating toll on her body. Here&amp;rsquo;s more on her story from Hawaii News Now: &amp;ldquo;My kidneys were failing; my liver was failing,&amp;rdquo; Bero said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Latest Update from Kilauea - Volcano-Created Glass Blowing in the Wind</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/latest-update-from-kilauea-volcano-created-glass-blowing-in-the-wind/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 13:21:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/latest-update-from-kilauea-volcano-created-glass-blowing-in-the-wind/</guid>
      <description>Unless you&amp;rsquo;re a vulcanologist, you probably haven&amp;rsquo;t heard the term &amp;ldquo;Pele&amp;rsquo;s hair&amp;rdquo; before now, but it&amp;rsquo;s another one of the interesting, awe inspiring, and deadly natural phenomena that&amp;rsquo;s a result of Kilauea&amp;rsquo;s eruption in Hawaii.
Pele&amp;rsquo;s Hair - USGS Pele&amp;rsquo;s hair refers to the fine strands of volcanic glass that are blowing in the wind around that rumbling Hawaiian volcano. Here&amp;rsquo;s more from HawaiiNewsNow.com: _It’s certainly a perplexing sight as its appearance does resemble strands of golden hair, but officials warn that the public should stay away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Half Mammal Half Reptile? Yep, &amp; One&#39;s Skeleton Was Just Discovered in Utah</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/half-mammal-half-reptile-yep-ones-skeleton-was-just-discovered-in-utah/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 22:20:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/half-mammal-half-reptile-yep-ones-skeleton-was-just-discovered-in-utah/</guid>
      <description>Utah continues to be a paleontologist playground, delivering a new and exciting trove of fossils on a regular basis. This fossil, however, just might change everything we thought we knew about how the continents were formed.
DeseretNews From CBS Denver: It may have weighed only 2 1&amp;frasl;2 pounds and stood about 6 inches tall, but the discovery of a half mammal, half reptile’s skull in eastern Utah has huge implications for geologic timelines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is This the Source of the Mysterious Booms We&#39;ve Been Hearing?</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/is-this-the-source-of-the-mysterious-booms-weve-been-hearing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 21:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/is-this-the-source-of-the-mysterious-booms-weve-been-hearing/</guid>
      <description>To say that there have been several instances of mysterious &amp;ldquo;booms&amp;rdquo; reported around the US in the last 6 - 8 months is not a conpsiracy theory. Local news stations have reported on them as well as the National Weather Service. This alleged source of the booms, however, is a little more controversial and, if it&amp;rsquo;s true, is actually quite disturbing.
Pexels First a little backstory on the booms. This is from a Newsweek article toward the end of last year: Loud, booming noises have startled people across the United States, and it was unclear what was actually happening or if the separate events were even related.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Manhattan-henge&#34; Returns to the Big Apple -- Here&#39;s How to See It</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/manhattan-henge-returns-to-the-big-apple-heres-how-to-see-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 20:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/manhattan-henge-returns-to-the-big-apple-heres-how-to-see-it/</guid>
      <description>This time of year marks the return of Manhattanhenge to New York City. It&amp;rsquo;s that magical time of the year when the setting of the sun lines up perfectly with the streets of Manhattan &amp;ndash; most notably 42nd, 34th, and 14th streets.
Flickr The effect is at its fullest on May 29 and 30, but will still be visible for the next few days. EarthSky.org has more on the story: The phenomenon of Manhattanhenge isn’t mysterious, of course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How a Beloved Miracle Mineral was Revealed to Be a Toxic Killer</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/how-a-beloved-miracle-mineral-was-revealed-to-be-a-toxic-killer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 18:46:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/how-a-beloved-miracle-mineral-was-revealed-to-be-a-toxic-killer/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;ve watched any amount of cable television, you&amp;rsquo;ve likely been subjected to a barrage of commercials by mesothelioma lawyers and attorneys representing clients struck with that debilitating disease. What you may not know is that the mineral that was the cause of all those mesothelioma lawsuits had been hailed as a miracle substance as far back as the first century.
Asbestos Pit - Wikimedia Commons While many modern inventions at first seemed like good ideas before we discovered their toxic elements, the history of asbestos actually goes back over 4,000 years when inhabitants of what is now East Finland used anthophyllite, an asbestos minderal, to strengthen earthenware pots and cooking utensils.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boston Man Pulled Over for Drunk Driving - His DUI Lawyer Knew One Trick the Cops Didn&#39;t</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/boston-man-pulled-over-for-drunk-driving-his-dui-lawyer-knew-one-trick-the-cops-didnt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 15:05:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/boston-man-pulled-over-for-drunk-driving-his-dui-lawyer-knew-one-trick-the-cops-didnt/</guid>
      <description>When a DUI attorney defends a client charged with drunk driving, the first thing a good lawyer will do is try to find a reason to get the charges dismissed.
Pixabay Did the arresting officer make a mistake? Was there an underlying medical condition which led to the defendant appearing drunk? Was there an inaccurate measurement of the alcohol level? While some people might scoff at these attempts as those of a sleazy lawyer trying to game the system, sometimes they actually do have merit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>These Islands 2,000 Miles Away are in Danger from Kilauea</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/these-islands-2000-miles-away-are-in-danger-from-kilauea/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 16:46:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/these-islands-2000-miles-away-are-in-danger-from-kilauea/</guid>
      <description>The effects of volcanic eruptions are never just local. Earthquakes associated with them can be strong enough to trigger tsunamis in some ocean regions, and the ash and fog that they spew forth can impact areas that are downwind for miles. It&amp;rsquo;s the latter effect that&amp;rsquo;s taking place thanks to the Kilauea eruption in Hawaii.
National Park Service Officials are reporting that haze from Mt Kilauea blanketed the Marshall Islands on Sunday, and show no signs in stopping as its way across Micronesia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DUI Attorneys Love Challenging Them in Court, But Field Sobriety Tests are Surprisingly Accurate</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/dui-attorneys-love-challenging-them-in-court-but-field-sobriety-tests-are-surprisingly-accurate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2018 22:36:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/dui-attorneys-love-challenging-them-in-court-but-field-sobriety-tests-are-surprisingly-accurate/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s long been a favorite trick of DUI lawyers to help their clients accused of drunk driving: pick apart the dashcam footage of the field sobriety test given by the officer. If the attorney can prove that there was some extinuating circumstance that led to their clients failing the test, then they just might have a shot at getting them off without a penalty.
Pixabay What&amp;rsquo;s hard to dispute, however, is the ability of the test to assess the telltale physiological signs that betray a person&amp;rsquo;s sobriety or lack thereof.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Wolfeboro Millionaire Sobbed When the Judge Read the Verdict</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/owner-neglects-dogs-health-and-pays-for-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2018 03:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/owner-neglects-dogs-health-and-pays-for-it/</guid>
      <description>A scandal involving a millionaire pet owner recently came to light and shocked every on-looker. Please share your thoughts with us at the bottom of this post! Most pet owners care for their furry friends as if they were born into the family. In fact, in the past several decades, this had led to the explosive growth of the pet industry. Nowadays, owners are able to treat their pets with many of the same luxuries that people enjoy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ancient Clay Tablets Reveal Location of Lost City</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/ancient-clay-tablets-reveal-location-of-lost-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 21:19:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/ancient-clay-tablets-reveal-location-of-lost-city/</guid>
      <description>Archaeologists had always known that the Northern Mesopotamian city of Mardaman had existed, they just didn&amp;rsquo;t know where. They had read about it in ancient texts, and knew that it had existed as a provincial capital that had been conquered and destroyed many times between 2200 and 1200 BC, but they just didn&amp;rsquo;t know exactly where it lay.
University of Tuebingen Until now. From the NY Post: The discovery of clay tablets in Iraqi Kurdistan has helped archaeologists unlock the mystery of an ancient lost city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Something&#39;s Killing Sharks for Their Livers &amp; It&#39;s Not Humans</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/somethings-killing-sharks-for-their-livers-its-not-humans/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 21:07:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/somethings-killing-sharks-for-their-livers-its-not-humans/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s difficult to imagine a great white shark as anyone&amp;rsquo;s prey, but carcasses have been washing up on South African beaches this year, and they&amp;rsquo;re all missing one vital organ. The question, though, is who, or what, is repsonsible. Were this a story on rhinos or elephants, the first and most logical guess would be the human element, but this time the hunters are other ocean dwellers.
Terry Goss - Wikipedia Here&amp;rsquo;s the story from IFLScience: This year, five carcasses of the formidable hunters have been washed up, with the remains ranging in size from 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If You Did What Alexa Just Did, the Cops Would Be Knocking on Your Door</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/if-you-did-what-alexa-just-did-the-cops-would-be-knocking-on-your-door/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 19:45:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/if-you-did-what-alexa-just-did-the-cops-would-be-knocking-on-your-door/</guid>
      <description>Alexa owner Danielle and her husband were sitting at home about two weeks ago when they got a message from one of her husband&amp;rsquo;s employees who said, &amp;ldquo;Unplug your Alexa devices right now. You&amp;rsquo;re being hacked.&amp;rdquo; From the Dailywire:
Amazon Danielle said, &amp;ldquo;We unplugged all of them and he proceeded to tell us that he had received audio files of recordings from inside our house. At first, my husband was, like, &amp;lsquo;No, you didn&amp;rsquo;t!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Half Human, Half Chicken Embryos Created in Lab - Is This Going Too Far?</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/half-human-half-chicken-embryos-created-in-lab-is-this-going-too-far/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 16:37:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/half-human-half-chicken-embryos-created-in-lab-is-this-going-too-far/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re definitely entering a bold new era in human history. A report out yesterday said that by the year 2045 AI robots will now be our equals, and now this story out of Rockefeller University where scientists have successfully combined artificial human and chicken cells in an embryo. The experiment was done by a team of stem cell researchers who are trying to better understand developing life.
Pixabay Here&amp;rsquo;s more from the Daily Express: Until now, scientists have been unable to answer how certain cells in a developing embryo decide to become muscles or limbs, while others become bones and nerves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s Why The Blue Flames That Cropped Up Around Kilauea Have Experts Worried</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/heres-why-the-blue-flames-that-cropped-up-around-kilauea-have-experts-worried/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 14:58:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/heres-why-the-blue-flames-that-cropped-up-around-kilauea-have-experts-worried/</guid>
      <description>Things have shown no signs of settling down around the Kilauea volcano on the big island of Hawaii, and now experts are worried that the presence of blue flames could be a sign of more ominous things to come. Adding to their fears is the concern that Hawaii&amp;rsquo;s last remaining open highway could be blocked if new fissures open. If that happens, approximately 1,000 people would have to be helicoptered to safety.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wolf-Like Creature Killed on Montana Ranch - What is This?</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/wolf-like-creature-killed-on-montana-ranch-what-is-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 13:20:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/wolf-like-creature-killed-on-montana-ranch-what-is-this/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve had several stories lately about bizarre looking sea creatures washing ashore all around the globe from the Philippines to New Jersey. Today, this story comes to us from Denton, Montana where a bizarre looking creature was shot and killed on a ranch there.
Great Falls Tribune From the Great Falls Tribune: On May 16 a lone wolf-like animal was shot and killed on a ranch outside Denton. With long grayish fur, a large head and an extended snout, the animal shared many of the same characteristics as a wolf; but its ears were too large, it&amp;rsquo;s legs and body too short, its fur uncharacteristic of that common to a wolf.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snake Head &#43; Shark Body = This Freaky Sea Creature</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/snake-head-shark-body-this-freaky-sea-creature/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 22:29:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/snake-head-shark-body-this-freaky-sea-creature/</guid>
      <description>It seems like every week we&amp;rsquo;re hearing about some new freaky creature from the depths of the ocean emerging to strike fear into any human even thinking about stepping foot in the water. Such is the case with the creature that researchers spotted swimming off the coast of portugal. Though it&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;new&amp;rdquo; to most humans, the frilled shark has been around for about 80 million years and is considered a &amp;ldquo;living fossil,&amp;rdquo; as Newsweek explains:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>High School Chemistry Student Makes Game Changing Scientific Discovery</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/high-school-chemistry-student-makes-game-changing-scientific-discovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 22:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/high-school-chemistry-student-makes-game-changing-scientific-discovery/</guid>
      <description>When a professor used a recent scientific paper to challenge his chemistry students during one of his lectures, little did he know that one of them, would take up the challenge and create a new breakthrough in chemistry. From IFLScience:
Inverse.com High school chemistry tells us all about the versatility of carbon. You might recall that carbon is missing four electrons in its outer shell so it&amp;rsquo;s looking to form up to four bonds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heartwarming Moment a Baby Sloth is Reunited With It&#39;s Mother</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/heartwarming-moment-a-baby-sloth-is-reunited-with-its-mother/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 21:26:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/heartwarming-moment-a-baby-sloth-is-reunited-with-its-mother/</guid>
      <description>Tourists on a Costa Rican beach found a baby sloth. The youngster was lost, alone covered by sand and ants on the Central American beach. The tourists rescued the sloth and took it to the Jaguar Rescue Center where a veterinarian inspected it and found that, in spite of its traumatic adventure, the sloth was still in good shape.
Flickr The vet estimated that the little sloth, which weighed about the same as a can of soup, was approximately three weeks old, and most likely would not have survived the night had the tourists not rescued it from the beach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yes, the &#34;Green Flash&#34; is Real - Here&#39;s How You Can See It</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/yes-the-green-flash-is-real-heres-how-you-can-see-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 20:09:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/yes-the-green-flash-is-real-heres-how-you-can-see-it/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a phenomenone that happens every single day on Earth, yet it&amp;rsquo;s one that very few people have every witnessed. In fact, it&amp;rsquo;s happening somewhere on Earth right now as the last sliver of the Sun dips below the horizon and day slowly fades into night. What is it? It&amp;rsquo;s the green flash, of course.
Wikimedia Commons No, it&amp;rsquo;s not a comic book character, but a natural phenomenon that occurs just as the Sun sets for the evening.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accidental Discovery:  Grean Tea Nanoparticles Kill Lung Cancer Cells</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/accidental-discovery-grean-tea-nanoparticles-kill-lung-cancer-cells/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 19:10:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/accidental-discovery-grean-tea-nanoparticles-kill-lung-cancer-cells/</guid>
      <description>From the microwave and teflon, to penicillin and viagra, many inventions and discoveries owe themselves to chance or a total accident, and that&amp;rsquo;s the story of this next breakthrough in the fight against cancer. This story comes to us from Swansea University in the UK where British and Indian scientiests recently discovered that nanoparticles from tea leaves can actually destroy lung cancer cells.
Pexels This is all thanks to incredibly small nanoparticles known as quantum dots that are just 1/4000th the thickness of human hair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Observation from Space Could Change Everything We Know About the History of North America</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/observation-from-space-could-change-everything-we-know-about-the-history-of-north-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 17:39:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/observation-from-space-could-change-everything-we-know-about-the-history-of-north-america/</guid>
      <description>Although Christopher Colombus has been credited with discovering North America, others have laid claim to the distinction long before him. One legend says that the Welsh prince Madoc, for example, landed in the America over 300 years before Colombus. Still others claim that the Vikings landed and even established a settlement here. It&amp;rsquo;s this latter theory that&amp;rsquo;s gaining a little more credence thanks to an observation from space.
The Landing of Vikings in America - H.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vintage Footage of the AI Robot That Wowed Visitors at the 1939 World&#39;s Fair</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/vintage-footage-of-the-ai-robot-that-wowed-visitors-at-the-1939-worlds-fair/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 16:04:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/vintage-footage-of-the-ai-robot-that-wowed-visitors-at-the-1939-worlds-fair/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to companies such as Boston Dynamics, we&amp;rsquo;re developing robots and AI that are capable of remarkable things. We have robots that can walk, run, fight, cook meals, and grow human organs. In addition, today&amp;rsquo;s aritificial intelligence can teach itself to learn, and kick anyone&amp;rsquo;s ass in Jeopardy, but in 1939, when the first &amp;ldquo;Moto Man&amp;rdquo; robot was unveiled at the Worlds Fair in New York City, the vision for the future was a little bit different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Holy Grail&#34; of Shipwrecks Just Found in the Caribbean - $17 Billion Haul</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/holy-grail-of-shipwrecks-just-found-in-the-caribbean-17-billion-haul/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 14:39:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/holy-grail-of-shipwrecks-just-found-in-the-caribbean-17-billion-haul/</guid>
      <description>In the Caribbean waters off the coast of Colombia, treasure hunters have found what many are calling the holy grail of shipwrecks with a treasure of gold, silver, and emeralds that could be worth as much as $17 billion!
Wikimedia Commons The search was conducted by the Woods Hole Oceanographic Institution, which used an underwater submarine to investigate the ocean depths. The first sign that they&amp;rsquo;d found the shipwreck were the cannons strewn all over the bottom of the ocean floor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s What Nearby Galaxies Look Like in Ultraviolet Light  [Photos]</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/heres-what-nearby-galaxies-look-like-in-ultraviolet-light-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 22:22:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/heres-what-nearby-galaxies-look-like-in-ultraviolet-light-photos/</guid>
      <description>NASA just released some images of nearby galaxies photographed by the Hubble space telescope and they are nothing short of breathtaking.
NGC 4490 Galaxy - ESA/Hubble The ultraviolet images were all taken as part of the LEGUS project, which is short for Legacy Extra Galactic UV Survey. As part of this project, scientists studied 50 dwarf and spiral galaxies in our local universe (11 to 58 million light years away) by using old and new Hubble observations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Planet Hunting Telescope Does Moon Fly-by &amp; Sends First Pictures Back to Earth</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/planet-hunting-telescope-does-moon-fly-by-sends-first-pictures-back-to-earth/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 22:06:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/planet-hunting-telescope-does-moon-fly-by-sends-first-pictures-back-to-earth/</guid>
      <description>Almost a month to the day after launch NASA&amp;rsquo;s latest planet hunting satellite sent back its first test image to excited scientists back on earth. The Transiting Exoplanet Survey Satellite (TESS) is designed to look for nearby exoplanets, and so far it&amp;rsquo;s performing exactly the way it&amp;rsquo;s supposed to.
NASA Launched on Aril 18, the satellite conducted a moon fly-by in order to get a gravity boos that will help launch it toward its final orbit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wildlife Photographer Captures Battle Between Eagle &amp; a Fox Over Dinner [Photos]</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/wildlife-photographer-captures-battle-between-eagle-a-fox-over-dinner-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 21:08:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/wildlife-photographer-captures-battle-between-eagle-a-fox-over-dinner-photos/</guid>
      <description>Kleptoparasitism is the phenomenon of one animal stealing food or prey from another animal, and it was on full display last week in very dramatic fashion at the San Juan Island National Historical Park in Washington State. Even better, it was all captured on video!
PublicDomainPictures.net Here&amp;rsquo;s the story from ScienceAlert.com: Nature photographer Kevin Ebi of Living Wilderness witnessed this &amp;ldquo;especially dramatic act of thievery&amp;rdquo; as he spent a day observing young foxes rest, play, and hunt on the park&amp;rsquo;s grasslands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citizen Scientists Take Part in Creating Breathtaking Images of Jupiter</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/citizen-scientists-take-part-in-creating-breathtaking-images-of-jupiter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 19:52:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/citizen-scientists-take-part-in-creating-breathtaking-images-of-jupiter/</guid>
      <description>The picture below shows a southerly view of Jupiter. It was snapped by the Juno spacecraft earlier this year in a fly-by when Juno buzzed the orange-spotted planet at a distance of just 10,768 miles.
NASA/JPL-Caltech/SwRI/MSSS/Gerald Eichstad/Sean Doran The image clearly shows Jupiter&amp;rsquo;s Great Red Spot, which is about 1.3 times as wide as Earth. The uniqueness of this photo, however, is due to its view. Prior to Juno&amp;rsquo;s arrival there in 2016, we were unable to get an image like this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Years Later Scientists Break Down Michael Jackson&#39;s Killer Dance Move</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/30-years-later-scientists-break-down-michael-jacksons-killer-dance-move/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 19:03:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/30-years-later-scientists-break-down-michael-jacksons-killer-dance-move/</guid>
      <description>Michael Jackson&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Smooth Criminal&amp;rdquo; video hit the airwaves over 30 years ago in 1987 and it contained a dance move that people are still talking about &amp;ndash; and scientists are still studying &amp;ndash; to this day.
Discover Magazine Right around minute 7:00 in the video below you&amp;rsquo;ll see MJ lean about 45 degrees forward from a standing position. The average human can only lean 20 degrees or so before falling face first onto the floor, so, naturally, people thought that it was a cinematic special effect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Denmark Discovery Paints Brutal Picture of Barbarian War Rituals</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/denmark-discovery-paints-brutal-picture-of-barbarian-war-rituals/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 16:19:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/denmark-discovery-paints-brutal-picture-of-barbarian-war-rituals/</guid>
      <description>Archaeologists just unearthed a 2,000 year old mass grave in Denmark and the conclusions they&amp;rsquo;re drawing from what they found paint a picture of some pretty gruesome war rituals. The bodies in the grave are victims of a battle fought 2,000 years ago by barbarian Germanic tribes in Northern Europe.
PNAS The skeletal remains in the mass grave discovered in the Alken Enge wetlands in Jutland, Denmark gives archaeologists the earliest direct evidence of conflict among the Germanic peoples.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lava Closing in on Hawaiian Power Plant - This is NOT Good</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/lava-closing-in-on-hawaiian-power-plant-this-is-not-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 15:12:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/lava-closing-in-on-hawaiian-power-plant-this-is-not-good/</guid>
      <description>All eyes this morning are focused on the Puna Geothermal Venture power plant on the big island of Hawaii as lava from the erupting Kilauea volcano gets closer to the site. The plant provides 25% of the power for the island, and its loss would be devastating, but it&amp;rsquo;s the toxic element that has people more concerned.
PXHere From NPR: The plant harvests hot liquid and steam from underground wells to drive turbine generators for electricity, which is then sold to the state&amp;rsquo;s utility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>These Stonehenge Images Will Make You Re-Think Everything You Knew About It</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/these-stonehenge-images-will-make-you-re-think-everything-you-knew-about-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 21:56:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/these-stonehenge-images-will-make-you-re-think-everything-you-knew-about-it/</guid>
      <description>When one thinks of timeless monuments to humanity, they often (probably) think of the pyramids of Giza, the giant heads on Easter Island and the monoliths of Stonehenge.
Wikimedia Commons Based on the findings of archaeologists and other scientists, the Wiltshire, England circle of large stones is believed to have dated back to 3000 to 2000 BC, with recent tests pointing to the site being 500 years older than previously thought.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Strange Sea Creature Washes Ashore - What&#39;s Going On?</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/another-strange-sea-creature-washes-ashore-whats-going-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 21:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/another-strange-sea-creature-washes-ashore-whats-going-on/</guid>
      <description>Something is going on in the lightless depths of our oceans and seas. For months now, various seaside communities have been witnesses to the sudden arrival of washed-up corpses of mysterious or extremely rare marine creatures. The trend actually began several years ago when a previously unknown organism that looked like a cross between an alligator and a sturgeon washed ashore in England
Daily Express Then, in March of 2018, residents in Waycross, Georgia awoke one morning to find a ‘Loch Ness’ like creature lying dead on the unpopulated beach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deciphered Clay Tablets Reveal Whereabouts of Lost City</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/deciphered-clay-tablets-reveal-whereabouts-of-lost-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 20:58:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/deciphered-clay-tablets-reveal-whereabouts-of-lost-city/</guid>
      <description>Archaeologists had always known that the Northern Mesopotamian city of Mardaman had existed, they just didn&amp;rsquo;t know where. They had read about it in ancient texts, and knew that it had existed as a provincial capital that had been conquered and destroyed many times between 2200 and 1200 BC, but they just didn&amp;rsquo;t know exactly where it lay.
University of Tuebingen Until now. From the NY Post: The discovery of clay tablets in Iraqi Kurdistan has helped archaeologists unlock the mystery of an ancient lost city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>170 Million Year Old Living Fossil Now Being Eaten Out of Existence</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/170-million-year-old-living-fossil-now-being-eaten-out-of-existence/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 14:58:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/170-million-year-old-living-fossil-now-being-eaten-out-of-existence/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been on earth for about 170 million years, but thanks to a epicurean demand for its meat, this salamander now finds itself on the verge of extinction. This has come to light after a four year research study has shown that the muddy brown salamander has almost completely vanished from its freshwater habitats.
Flickr The problem stems from the rise in popularity of the salamander as a favorite dish in China and the East.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>California&#39;s Recent Quake Storm Has Some People Worried - Is Something Bigger Around the Corner</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/californias-recent-quake-storm-has-some-people-worried-is-something-bigger-around-the-corner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 21:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/californias-recent-quake-storm-has-some-people-worried-is-something-bigger-around-the-corner/</guid>
      <description>California has been recently shaken by relatively small earthquakes, but there is concern that the tremors may be something similar to the birth pangs of women, in that they start out weak and infrequent and grow in number and intensity. In the early evening of May 14, the San Francisco Bay area was roiled by what was originally reported as a 3.8 magnitude quake with an epicenter 2 miles east of Oakland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last Week an Asteroid the Size of A Pyramid Buzzed the Earth - Here&#39;s How Close It Got</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/last-week-an-asteroid-the-size-of-a-pyramid-buzzed-the-earth-heres-how-close-it-got/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 21:01:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/last-week-an-asteroid-the-size-of-a-pyramid-buzzed-the-earth-heres-how-close-it-got/</guid>
      <description>Believed to have disappeared in some cosmic mishap of change in trajectory, asteroid 2019 WC9 has reappeared in foreboding fashion, writes the UK’s Express.
Max Pixel Said to be bigger than the Great Pyramid of Giza in Egypt, WC9 was first spotted in 2010 by astronomers in Australia. As quickly as it was located, it disappeared. On May 15, however, the asteroid hurtled perilously close to Earth, skimming by at just 126,000 miles from our planet, the closest it will be to earth for the next 300 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Announces Project with Defense Dept, Then Strikes &#34;Don&#39;t Be Evil&#34; From Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/google-announces-project-with-defense-dept-then-strikes-dont-be-evil-from-code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 20:23:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/google-announces-project-with-defense-dept-then-strikes-dont-be-evil-from-code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>The main question you&amp;rsquo;ll have after reading this article is whether or not Google made this decision before or after entering into a secret project with the government. Totalitarianism is the form of government that subjects the individual to the centralized rule of a tyrannical master that puts all forms of public and private production and consumption under its control.
Wikimedia Commons A big part of a government’s ability to wrangle in the population is its co-opting of large corporations under the banner of carrying out the ‘state’s business’.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Something&#39;s Targeting Great White Sharks - And It&#39;s NOT Humans</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/somethings-targeting-great-white-sharks-and-its-not-humans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 19:22:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/somethings-targeting-great-white-sharks-and-its-not-humans/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s difficult to imagine a great white shark as anyone&amp;rsquo;s prey, but carcasses have been washing up on South African beaches this year, and they&amp;rsquo;re all missing one vital organ. The question, though, is who, or what, is repsonsible. Were this a story on rhinos or elephants, the first and most logical guess would be the human element, but this time the hunters are other ocean dwellers.
Terry Goss - Wikipedia Here&amp;rsquo;s the story from IFLScience: This year, five carcasses of the formidable hunters have been washed up, with the remains ranging in size from 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Were These &#34;Moon-Eyed&#34; Inhabitants of Appalachia?</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/who-were-these-moon-eyed-inhabitants-of-appalachia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 16:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/who-were-these-moon-eyed-inhabitants-of-appalachia/</guid>
      <description>Nobody knows exactly when the Cherokee people came to inhabit the land that now makes up the southeastern United States. Some theorize that they were latecomers to southern Appalachia who migrated down from northern areas during prehistoric times. Others contend that they&amp;rsquo;d been there for thousands of years.
Wikimedia Commons Whatever the case, when they got to their homelands in southern Appalachia, it was already inhabited by a strange people that the Cherokee pushed out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oklahoma High School Student Makes Huge Scientific Discovery in Chemistry</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/oklahoma-high-school-student-makes-huge-scientific-discovery-in-chemistry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 14:43:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/oklahoma-high-school-student-makes-huge-scientific-discovery-in-chemistry/</guid>
      <description>When a professor used a recent scientific paper to challenge his chemistry students during one of his lectures, little did he know that one of them, would take up the challenge and create a new breakthrough in chemistry. From IFLScience:
Inverse.com High school chemistry tells us all about the versatility of carbon. You might recall that carbon is missing four electrons in its outer shell so it&amp;rsquo;s looking to form up to four bonds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Body of a Shark, Head of a Snake? Yes, It&#39;s a Real Thing [VIDEO]</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/body-of-a-shark-head-of-a-snake-yes-its-a-real-thing-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 13:46:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/body-of-a-shark-head-of-a-snake-yes-its-a-real-thing-video/</guid>
      <description>It seems like every week we&amp;rsquo;re hearing about some new freaky creature from the depths of the ocean emerging to strike fear into any human even thinking about stepping foot in the water. Such is the case with the creature that researchers spotted swimming off the coast of portugal. Though it&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;new&amp;rdquo; to most humans, the frilled shark has been around for about 80 million years and is considered a &amp;ldquo;living fossil,&amp;rdquo; as Newsweek explains:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Ancient Temple Was Carved Top-Down Out of a Single, Massive Rock [Photos]</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/this-ancient-temple-was-carved-top-down-out-of-a-single-massive-rock-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 16:51:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/this-ancient-temple-was-carved-top-down-out-of-a-single-massive-rock-photos/</guid>
      <description>The Temple at Kailasa is a marvel to behold. The giant structure, 164 feet deep, 109 feet wide, and 98 feet high, is one of the biggest monolithic structures in the world. And, by &amp;ldquo;monolithic&amp;rdquo; we mean that the whole thing was carved out of a single rock.
Wikipedia The legend goes that a local king in India suffered from a serious, debilitating disease. His wife offered up a prayer to the Hindu god Ghrishneshwar (Shiva) to cure her husband and, as part of her bargain to save him, vowed to build a temple if he was healed of his disease.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conditions at Kilauea Steadily Worsening - &#34;Like a Warzone&#34;</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/conditions-at-kilauea-steadily-worsening-like-a-warzone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 16:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/conditions-at-kilauea-steadily-worsening-like-a-warzone/</guid>
      <description>The situation around Kilauea is deteriorating as a giant eruption took place over the weekend at the Kilauea volcano on the big island of Hawaii. The area also saw its first serious injury when a man suffered serious injuries from lava falling from the sky. From EarthSky.org:
USGS/DailyMail Kilauea Volcano has been spewing lava and belching hazardous gases on Hawaii’s Big Island since early May, and the BBC reported on Sunday, May 20, 2018, that the situation for residents is “steadily worsening.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NASA&#39;s Planet Hunter Buzzes the Moon &amp; Sends Back First Image</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/nasas-planet-hunter-buzzes-the-moon-sends-back-first-image/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 15:35:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/nasas-planet-hunter-buzzes-the-moon-sends-back-first-image/</guid>
      <description>Almost a month to the day after launch NASA&amp;rsquo;s latest planet hunting satellite sent back its first test image to excited scientists back on earth. The Transiting Exoplanet Survey Satellite (TESS) is designed to look for nearby exoplanets, and so far it&amp;rsquo;s performing exactly the way it&amp;rsquo;s supposed to.
NASA Launched on Aril 18, the satellite conducted a moon fly-by in order to get a gravity boos that will help launch it toward its final orbit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>National Guard Makes Dramatic Helicopter Rescue as Kilauea Lava Intensifies</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/national-guard-makes-dramatic-helicopter-rescue-as-kilauea-lava-intensifies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2018 19:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/national-guard-makes-dramatic-helicopter-rescue-as-kilauea-lava-intensifies/</guid>
      <description>With Kilauea continuing to rumble and erupt and new development has threatened the homes of the last remaining residents in the Leilani Estates and dashing the hope that this will come to an end sometime soon. There&amp;rsquo;s now a fast moving lava flow that&amp;rsquo;s headed straight toward the residential area and isolated about 40 homes, prompting a dramatic helicopter rescue of homeowners who&amp;rsquo;d been trying to wait out the volcano.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NASA Releases Hubble&#39;s Ultraviolet Images of Nearby Galaxies [Photos}</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/nasa-releases-hubbles-ultraviolet-images-of-nearby-galaxies-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2018 18:30:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/nasa-releases-hubbles-ultraviolet-images-of-nearby-galaxies-photos/</guid>
      <description>NASA just released some images of nearby galaxies photographed by the Hubble space telescope and they are nothing short of breathtaking.
NGC 4490 Galaxy - ESA/Hubble The ultraviolet images were all taken as part of the LEGUS project, which is short for Legacy Extra Galactic UV Survey. As part of this project, scientists studied 50 dwarf and spiral galaxies in our local universe (11 to 58 million light years away) by using old and new Hubble observations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NASA Releases Hubble Ultraviolet Picture of Nearby Galaxies [Photos]</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/nasa-releases-hubble-ultraviolet-picture-of-nearby-galaxies-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2018 18:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/nasa-releases-hubble-ultraviolet-picture-of-nearby-galaxies-photos/</guid>
      <description>NASA just released some images of nearby galaxies photographed by the Hubble space telescope and they are nothing short of breathtaking.
NGC 4490 Galaxy - ESA/Hubble The ultraviolet images were all taken as part of the LEGUS project, which is short for Legacy Extra Galactic UV Survey. As part of this project, scientists studied 50 dwarf and spiral galaxies in our local universe (11 to 58 million light years away) by using old and new Hubble observations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How the Gemini Astronauts Took the Best UFO Picture Ever</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/how-the-gemini-astronauts-took-the-best-ufo-picture-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 22:41:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/how-the-gemini-astronauts-took-the-best-ufo-picture-ever/</guid>
      <description>In June of 1965 astronauts James McDivitt and Ed Pilot took part in the Gemini IV mission launched by NASA. The purpose of the mission was to show that humans could stay in space for extended lengths of time. It was the 2nd manned Gemini space flight and the 10th manned spaceflight by the US.
Wikimedia Commons For four days, McDivitt and White circled the Earth 66 times, and even took the first spacewalk ever by an American astronaut, as White floated free outside of the spacecraft for about 20 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here are the Stonehenge Images the Tourism Bureau Doesn&#39;t Want You to See</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/here-are-the-stonehenge-images-the-tourism-bureau-doesnt-want-you-to-see/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 21:04:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/here-are-the-stonehenge-images-the-tourism-bureau-doesnt-want-you-to-see/</guid>
      <description>When one thinks of timeless monuments to humanity, they often (probably) think of the pyramids of Giza, the giant heads on Easter Island and the monoliths of Stonehenge.
Wikimedia Commons Based on the findings of archaeologists and other scientists, the Wiltshire, England circle of large stones is believed to have dated back to 3000 to 2000 BC, with recent tests pointing to the site being 500 years older than previously thought.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Engineering Student&#39;s Quick Thinking &amp; a Ball Point Pen Save Airplane Passenger</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/engineering-students-quick-thinking-a-ball-point-pen-save-airplane-passenger/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 20:36:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/engineering-students-quick-thinking-a-ball-point-pen-save-airplane-passenger/</guid>
      <description>Next time there&amp;rsquo;s a medical emergency and you&amp;rsquo;re forced to yell, &amp;ldquo;Is there a doctor in the house,&amp;rdquo; go ahead and add, &amp;ldquo;And an engineer, too?&amp;rdquo; It turns out that you can never tell when one you may need one.
Pexels This story takes place on an airplane where a 30 year old male passenger with Type 1 diabetes had lost his insulin pump while going through airport security. With the plane in the air and his blood sugar spiking to dangerous levels, flight attendants leapt into action to get him the medical attention he so desperately needed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vladimir Putin Just Unveiled the Poseidon Drone -- This is NOT Good</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/vladimir-putin-just-unveiled-the-poseidon-drone-this-is-not-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 19:27:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/vladimir-putin-just-unveiled-the-poseidon-drone-this-is-not-good/</guid>
      <description>If Vladimir Putin&amp;rsquo;s plans come to fruition, the Russians will soon have an underwater drone capable of wreaking disastrous havoc. TASS is reporting that Russia is working on a nuclear powered underwater drone capable of carrying a two megatonne nuclear warhead.
Kremlin.ru From the Daily Mirror: &amp;ldquo;It will be possible to mount various nuclear charges on the ‘torpedo’ of the Poseidon multipurpose seaborne system, with the thermonuclear single warhead&amp;hellip; to have the maximum capacity of up to 2 megatonnes in TNT equivalent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Science Detectives Explain Secret of Ancient Oracle at Delphi</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/science-detectives-explain-secret-of-ancient-oracle-at-delphi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 16:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/science-detectives-explain-secret-of-ancient-oracle-at-delphi/</guid>
      <description>When the ancients had taxing problems or life issues that required an expert&amp;rsquo;s opinion, they often sought the counsel and sage advice of an oracle. These givers of wisdom were often located at &amp;ldquo;mystical&amp;rdquo; locations that gave them special powers of discernment and vision.
Wikimedia Commons One such location was outside of Selcuk in southwestern Turkey. Here the oracle of Cybele, the earth goddess of Asia Minor, would grant healing to the sick, fertility to the childless, and wisdom to all who came seeking it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Employees Resign En Masse Over Government Project</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/google-employees-resign-en-masse-over-government-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 20:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/google-employees-resign-en-masse-over-government-project/</guid>
      <description>Totalitarianism is the form of government that subjects the individual to the centralized rule of a tyrannical master that puts all forms of public and private production and consumption under its control.
Wikimedia Commons A big part of a government’s ability to wrangle in the population is its co-opting of large corporations under the banner of carrying out the ‘state’s business’. This unofficial merger becomes especially dangerous when it is controlled by what President Dwight Eisenhower called the ‘military industrial complex’.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Startup Company Aims to Reverse Aging in Dogs - Humans are Next</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/startup-company-aims-to-reverse-aging-in-dogs-humans-are-next/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 20:06:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/startup-company-aims-to-reverse-aging-in-dogs-humans-are-next/</guid>
      <description>It takes a lot for a novel innovation or scientific breakthrough to make others think that “what Elon Musk is doing look fairly pedestrian.” That, however is exactly what famed Harvard biologist George Church might just do with the announcement that he is backing a new startup biogenic company that is focused on making history.
Harvard.edu MIT Technology Review reports that Church, who is also involved in bringing the extinct woolly mammoth back to life (an effort cited in Ben Mezrich’s excellent book ‘Woolly: The True Story to Revive One of History’s Most Iconic Extinct Creatures) and Rejuvenate Bio are working on transplanting the progress made in reversing the signs of aging made in worms and mice to Man’s best friend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kilauea Prompts Red Air Alert in Hawaii - This is NOT Good</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/kilauea-prompts-red-air-alert-in-hawaii-this-is-not-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 19:41:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/kilauea-prompts-red-air-alert-in-hawaii-this-is-not-good/</guid>
      <description>Hawaii, ‘The Big Island’, is experiencing the unfolding of a hellish tragedy. Mt. Kilauea began erupting on May 3 and since then the southeastern area of the island has been ripped asunder by 21 fissures scarring the jungle paradise, while tremors continue to leave residents feeling the ground beneath their feet is far from stable. Seismologists are now warning that the Kilauea volcano may be getting ready for a major eruption, reports CNN.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Internet Nerd Cracks the Yanny and Laurel Riddle</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/internet-nerd-cracks-the-yanny-and-laurel-riddle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 19:13:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/internet-nerd-cracks-the-yanny-and-laurel-riddle/</guid>
      <description>For the past few days the internet has provided us with yet another a new thing to obsess over and debate with others while avoiding doing actual work. Last year the same crowd of people fought each other over the color of a dress posted online.
Wired.com Now it is an audio clip of a woman saying, depending on who you ask, either “Yanny” or “Laurel”, reports C/Net.
What do you hear?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guess Whose Beds are Cleaner Than Humans&#39;?</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/guess-whose-beds-are-cleaner-than-humans/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 18:24:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/guess-whose-beds-are-cleaner-than-humans/</guid>
      <description>It could be termed ‘The Rise of the Bedroom of the Apes’. Researchers from North Carolina State University have found that the beds of chimpanzees are cleaner than those of humans, reports The Telegraph.
Pexels The study was born out of a curiosity over the cleanliness of human beds compared to our closest genetic relatives. &amp;ldquo;We know that human homes are effectively their own ecosystems, and human beds often contain a subset of the taxa - or types - of organisms found in the home,” said Megan Thoemmes, who led the research in Tanzania.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stunning Photos of Ancient Temple Carved Out of a Single, Massive Rock</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/stunning-photos-of-ancient-temple-carved-out-of-a-single-massive-rock/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 15:51:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/stunning-photos-of-ancient-temple-carved-out-of-a-single-massive-rock/</guid>
      <description>The Temple at Kailasa is a marvel to behold. The giant structure, 164 feet deep, 109 feet wide, and 98 feet high, is one of the biggest monolithic structures in the world. And, by &amp;ldquo;monolithic&amp;rdquo; we mean that the whole thing was carved out of a single rock.
Wikipedia The legend goes that a local king in India suffered from a serious, debilitating disease. His wife offered up a prayer to the Hindu god Ghrishneshwar (Shiva) to cure her husband and, as part of her bargain to save him, vowed to build a temple if he was healed of his disease.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mystery Creature Washes Ashore in Philippines - What IS This?</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/mystery-creature-washes-ashore-in-philippines-what-is-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 14:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/mystery-creature-washes-ashore-in-philippines-what-is-this/</guid>
      <description>Something is going on in the lightless depths of our oceans and seas. For months now, various seaside communities have been witnesses to the sudden arrival of washed-up corpses of mysterious or extremely rare marine creatures. The trend actually began several years ago in England when a previously unknown organism that looked like a cross between an alligator and a sturgeon.
   (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});   Daily Express In March of 2018, residents in Waycross, Georgia awoke one morning to find a ‘Loch Ness’ like creature lying dead on the unpopulated beach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Study: Octopuses Came From Outer Space</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/new-study-octopuses-came-from-outer-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 13:24:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/new-study-octopuses-came-from-outer-space/</guid>
      <description>Looking at all of Earth&amp;rsquo;s species if you had to guess which one had an alien origin, the octopus might make the short list, and now some scientists are actually making that case.
Wikipedia A controversial paper recently appeared in the science journal Progress in Biophysics and Molecular Biology and it argues that octopuses are such complex beings that they can only be explained from an extraterrestrial perspective. Though the journal lists 33 researchers as collaborating on the paper, it&amp;rsquo;s being criticized for having zero zoologists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Underwater Expedition Confirms Scientists&#39; Worst Nightmare in Gulf of Oman</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/underwater-expedition-confirms-scientists-worst-nightmare-in-gulf-of-oman/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 22:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/underwater-expedition-confirms-scientists-worst-nightmare-in-gulf-of-oman/</guid>
      <description>[caption id=&amp;ldquo;attachment_38738&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;ldquo;alignnone&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;ldquo;640&amp;rdquo;]Flickr | Gulf of Oman | by Francisco Anzola[/caption] It seems like every day we&amp;rsquo;re learning something new about the oceans. Sometimes we discover new sea life or new ways that animals communicate with each other under water, other times, however, we come across disturbing features like this one&amp;hellip; Recently, robots exploring the depths of the Gulf of Oman have discovered a &amp;ldquo;dead zone&amp;rdquo; the size of Scotland!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welsh Scientist Thinks He&#39;s Solved One of Stonehenge&#39;s Most Baffling Mysteries</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/welsh-scientist-thinks-hes-solved-one-of-stonehenges-most-baffling-mysteries/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 21:42:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/welsh-scientist-thinks-hes-solved-one-of-stonehenges-most-baffling-mysteries/</guid>
      <description>It has stood for somewhere between 4,000 to 5,000 years amidst the verdant expanse of a Wiltshire field in England. It has weathered millenniums of raw English seasons, storms, rare earthquakes and even the urban sprawl of man.
Wikimedia Commons The theorized Druidic site of Stonehenge is a monument to the cosmic and astrological fascinations of a bygone age. It was erected, so we are told, to unlock the mysteries of the heavens and to note the cycles of nature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UK Audit of UFO Files Reveals Government Cover Up</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/uk-audit-of-ufo-files-reveals-government-cover-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 21:07:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/uk-audit-of-ufo-files-reveals-government-cover-up/</guid>
      <description>At a time when 21st Century Fox was enjoying the widespread success of its TV show, ‘The X-Files’, the British government was conducting an audit of a decade of UFO sightings and related phenomenon.
Pixabay Called Project Condign, condign meaning a deserved punishment for a crime, the effort was handled by the U.K’s Ministry of Defence (MoD). Investigators and analysts studied a database of sightings between 1987 and 1997 to determine not so much the validity of the incidents (but they did offer opinions) but any patterns in the sightings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quake Swarm Hits California - Is Something Bigger on the Way?</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/quake-swarm-hits-california-is-something-bigger-on-the-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 20:28:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/quake-swarm-hits-california-is-something-bigger-on-the-way/</guid>
      <description>California has been recently shaken by relatively small earthquakes, but there is concern that the tremors may be something similar to the birth pangs of women, in that they start out weak and infrequent and grow in number and intensity. In the early evening of May 14, the San Francisco Bay area was roiled by what was originally reported as a 3.8 magnitude quake with an epicenter 2 miles east of Oakland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asteroid the Size of a Pyramid Buzzed the Earth Last Night - Here&#39;s How Close It Got</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/asteroid-the-size-of-a-pyramid-buzzed-the-earth-last-night-heres-how-close-it-got/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 17:26:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/asteroid-the-size-of-a-pyramid-buzzed-the-earth-last-night-heres-how-close-it-got/</guid>
      <description>Believed to have disappeared in some cosmic mishap of change in trajectory, asteroid 2019 WC9 has reappeared in foreboding fashion, writes the UK’s Express.
Max Pixel Said to be bigger than the Great Pyramid of Giza in Egypt, WC9 was first spotted in 2010 by astronomers in Australia. As quickly as it was located, it disappeared. On May 15, however, the asteroid hurtled perilously close to Earth, skimming by at just 126,000 miles from our planet, the closest it will be to earth for the next 300 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multiverse Dark Matter Findings Have Scientists Looking for New Law of Physics</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/multiverse-dark-matter-findings-have-scientists-looking-for-new-law-of-physics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 16:53:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/multiverse-dark-matter-findings-have-scientists-looking-for-new-law-of-physics/</guid>
      <description>The precise setting of the variables that went in to making our universe the way it is are beyond belief. Just a smidgen change here and there and the constitution of the cosmos could change and possibly make life extinct.
Pixnio Take that fragility of this cosmic stasis and try to replicate it in a parallel universe the balance becomes even harder to achieve. Thanks to a pair of research papers that have been published in the &amp;lsquo;Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society&amp;rsquo;, it appears that one variable could be increased on hundreds of magnitudes in a parallell universe and it would not deter the formation of life-giving planets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Old NASA Data Reveals Active Geyser on Jupiter Moon - Possibility of Extraterrestrial Life</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/old-nasa-data-reveals-active-geyser-on-jupiter-moon-possibility-of-extraterrestrial-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 14:58:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/old-nasa-data-reveals-active-geyser-on-jupiter-moon-possibility-of-extraterrestrial-life/</guid>
      <description>Massive geysers have been detected and found to be spewing its contents heavenwards in impressive displays. No these are not the geysers of Yellowstone National Park or the resultant activities of Mt. Kilauea in Hawaii. These eruptions are taking place on Jupiter’s distant moon, Europa.
NASA/JPL Xianzhe Jia, a researcher at the University of Michigan, has published a study of Europa’s geysers based on indirect evidence gathered by NASA’s Galileo satellite that passed by the moon back in 1997, writes Science Alert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jupiter at It&#39;s Closest in Years - Here&#39;s How to See It</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/jupiter-at-its-closest-in-years-heres-how-to-see-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 14:31:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/jupiter-at-its-closest-in-years-heres-how-to-see-it/</guid>
      <description>Starting on May 8, our solar systems largest planet entered into an orbital phase that brings it the closest it comes in the course of its celestial trek.
Pixabay Throughout the month, Jupiter will appear a bit bigger and a bit brighter, writes IFL Science. That is because it will be ‘only’ 409 million miles from earth, 5 million miles closer than its last close pass in 2017. On May 8th, the planet was aligned directly opposite the sun, making it on the “exact opposite side of Earth to the sun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plant Full of Dangerous Chemicals Now Threatened By Kilauea</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/plant-full-of-dangerous-chemicals-now-threatened-by-kilauea/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 12:52:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/plant-full-of-dangerous-chemicals-now-threatened-by-kilauea/</guid>
      <description>Hawaii’s Kilauea continues to erupt and the earth around it continues to rumble and crack apart, opening hellish fissures that scar the plush green countryside of the island.
PX Here More and more residents are being forced to flee the glacial advance of lava, the downpour of rocks and boulders falling back to earth after each volcanic burst and now Hawaiian residents have another threat to worry about: a clean energy plant that could go boom if steps are not taken to ‘kill it’ before the volcano uses it to amplify its destructive reign, reports Science Alert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Check Out These Latest Air Travel Nightmares!</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/air-travel-nightmares/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 18:10:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/air-travel-nightmares/</guid>
      <description>So far, the year of 2018 has been a miserable experience for airline passengers, inflight staff, and the carriers that operate more than 87,000 flights in the continental U.S. every single day. From dead pets to exotic stowaways, flying the friendly skies can often feel more like riding a rollercoaster. To ease your pre-flight anxieties, we&amp;rsquo;ve put together an epic list of the top ten air travel debacles since New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Just Got Dark: The Hidden Island Park They Want To Keep Secret</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/disney-hidden-island/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 18:04:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/disney-hidden-island/</guid>
      <description>A courageous photographer went deep undercover to show the grim truth behind the Disney parks. Little did we know that part of Disney&amp;rsquo;s magic is dark magic.
Walt Disney himself has experienced his fair share of infamy. His anti-semitism is widely known, so it&amp;rsquo;s not surprising that even more secrets are right near the parks.
The place commonly known as the &amp;ldquo;happiest place on Earth&amp;rdquo; may be the exact opposite for some people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snails Help Researcher Crack Memory Workings of the Brain</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/snails-help-researcher-crack-memory-workings-of-the-brain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 22:34:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/snails-help-researcher-crack-memory-workings-of-the-brain/</guid>
      <description>There is an adage that says, &amp;lsquo;Memories are fleeting&amp;rsquo;. This may or not be true depending on the person. Researchers from the University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA), however, may have just proven that certain types of memories are permanent and may be etched in our biological make up.
Wikipedia In a story by Live Science, it is reported that the UCLA team has extracted the imprinted memories of one snail and implanted them in another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Strange Way Jupiter &amp; Venus Have Been Messing With Our Climate</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-strange-way-jupiter-venus-have-been-messing-with-our-climate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 22:23:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-strange-way-jupiter-venus-have-been-messing-with-our-climate/</guid>
      <description>A Rutgers University researcher has confirmed a phenomenon that has been happening every 400,000 years or so for the last 200 million years, and it involves our planet and a couple of other planets in our Milky Way neighborhood.
Pixabay You ever have those people in your life that, whenever you&amp;rsquo;re around them, can just kind of knock you out of your orbit? Well, the Earth does, too! Except those people are planets and they go by the name of &amp;ldquo;Jupiter&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Venus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk&#39;s 124 mph Traffic Shortcut Tunnel is Awesome &amp; Almost Open for Riders</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/elon-musks-124-mph-traffic-shortcut-tunnel-is-awesome-almost-open-for-riders/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 21:04:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/elon-musks-124-mph-traffic-shortcut-tunnel-is-awesome-almost-open-for-riders/</guid>
      <description>Unless you&amp;rsquo;re one of the lucky few billionaires who can commute from home to office via helicopter, you probably, at some point during your work day, have to deal with traffic. Well, if one Elon Musk has his way, those present day traffic aggravations will soon be coming to an end.
Flickr Frustrated by his daily commute, Tesla and Space-X CEO Elon Musk once vowed that he would dig a tunnel beneath Los Angeles and bypass the bumper-to-bumper traffic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fly from LA to NY in Half the Time with No Sonic Boom? NASA Says They Can Do It</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/fly-from-la-to-ny-in-half-the-time-with-no-sonic-boom-nasa-says-they-can-do-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 20:35:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/fly-from-la-to-ny-in-half-the-time-with-no-sonic-boom-nasa-says-they-can-do-it/</guid>
      <description>If NASA is correct, some frequent flyers may soon get to cut the amount of time they spend on board an airplane in half. That&amp;rsquo;s because NASA has been busy making gains in improving super sonic air travel &amp;ndash; and not just for astronauts.
CNN Supersonic commercial flights have been hiatus since 2003, after the British-French Concorde went belly up to due to expensive operations and prohibitive passenger fares. While aeronautic enthusiasts mourned the end of such flights, those living in the path of the incoming and outgoing airplanes felt relief that the loud, bone rattling sonic booms of the Concorde would no longer be heard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welsh Scientist Cracks Mystery of the Stonehenge Bluestones</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/welsh-scientist-cracks-mystery-of-the-stonehenge-bluestones/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 17:34:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/welsh-scientist-cracks-mystery-of-the-stonehenge-bluestones/</guid>
      <description>It has stood for somewhere between 4,000 to 5,000 years amidst the verdant expanse of a Wiltshire field in England. It has weathered millenniums of raw English seasons, storms, rare earthquakes and even the urban sprawl of man.
Pixabay The theorized Druidic site of Stonehenge is a monument to the cosmic and astrological fascinations of a bygone age. It was erected, so we are told, to unlock the mysteries of the heavens and to note the cycles of nature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Explore Body Changes of Schizophrenic Patients</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/researchers-explore-body-changes-of-schizophrenic-patients/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 16:45:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/researchers-explore-body-changes-of-schizophrenic-patients/</guid>
      <description>Amalgamated from the Greek words skhizein and phren, Swiss psychiatrist Eugen Bleuler introduced the word schizophrenie into the psychological lexicon in 1910. The word meant ‘a splitting of the mind’ and was seen as an apt term to describe the deteriorating mental health of those suffering from the diagnosed disease.
Healthncare.info That diagnostic consensus has been the accepted one for decades, but now Toby Pillinger, a Doctor and Clinical Researcher at King&amp;rsquo;s College in London, and a team of colleagues has completed a study that alleges that there are correlations between the disease and physical changes in the body.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scientists: Our Universe is Like... Raisin Bread?</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientists-our-universe-is-like-raisin-bread/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 14:56:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientists-our-universe-is-like-raisin-bread/</guid>
      <description>We have all heard the expression, ‘He/She thinks they are the center of the universe.’ Western Civilization’s infatuation with the cosmos began with the belief that our collective terra firma was the focal point of a geocentric solar system.
MaxPixel It seems a part of human nature to view ourselves at the center of universal existence but are we the center of the cosmos? Is there even a true center? Live Science reports that, based on the majority consensus of astrophysicists, there is no actual center of the universe because our cosmic reality is ever-expanding, pushing all celestial bodies further apart as it grows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Think They Might Have Found Another Planet Like Earth</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientists-think-they-might-have-found-another-planet-like-earth/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 21:37:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientists-think-they-might-have-found-another-planet-like-earth/</guid>
      <description>Astronomers and other scientists focused on finding a habitable &amp;lsquo;earth-like&amp;rsquo; exoplanet in the cosmos have many requirements that have to be met before they seriously zero in on a candidate. One of these requirements is that the planet have a sizable iron core that would lend itself to the creation and maintenance of a magnetosphere.
NASA In February of 2017, European astronomers went public with the news that they had discovered a seven-planet orbiting the nearby star TRAPPIST-1, a celestial object located 39.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experts Issue Dire Warning for Hawaiians as Kilauea Continues to Rumble</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/experts-issue-dire-warning-for-hawaiians-as-kilauea-continues-to-rumble/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 21:29:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/experts-issue-dire-warning-for-hawaiians-as-kilauea-continues-to-rumble/</guid>
      <description>With Kilauea continuing to rumble, residents there are filled with more uncertainty than not, and some are even beginning to wonder if life as as they knew it will ever be attainable again. Sadly, geologists and vulcanologists monitoring the situation, don&amp;rsquo;t have much in the way of good news to offer. From NBC:
NBC News If Hawaii&amp;rsquo;s Kilauea volcano blows its top in the coming days or weeks, as experts fear, it could hurl ash and boulders the size of refrigerators miles into the air, shutting down airline traffic and endangering lives in all directions, scientists say.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>After Biohacker&#39;s Sudden Death, Followers are Wondering, &#34;What&#39;s Next?&#34;</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/after-biohackers-sudden-death-followers-are-wondering-whats-next/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 21:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/after-biohackers-sudden-death-followers-are-wondering-whats-next/</guid>
      <description>Law enforcement officials were called to a spa in Washington, D.C. on May 6. Once they arrived on scene they discovered the body of 28-year-old Ascendance Biomedical founder Aaron Traywick in a flotation therapy tank, reports Independent. Traywick gained recent notoriety when he injected himself with an untested herpes drug while in front of an audience. Traywick and his company advocated for biohacking, a broad term applied to methods of treating disease or overall health without the aid of pharmaceutical products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Britain’s ‘X-Files’ Reveal Something That&#39;s Very Disturbing</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/britains-x-files-reveal-something-thats-very-disturbing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 20:43:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/britains-x-files-reveal-something-thats-very-disturbing/</guid>
      <description>At a time when 21st Century Fox was enjoying the widespread success of its TV show, ‘The X-Files’, the British government was conducting an audit of a decade of UFO sightings and related phenomenon.
Pixabay Called Project Condign, condign meaning a deserved punishment for a crime, the effort was handled by the U.K’s Ministry of Defence (MoD). Investigators and analysts studied a database of sightings between 1987 and 1997 to determine not so much the validity of the incidents (but they did offer opinions) but any patterns in the sightings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NASA Just Took 3D Printing to Whole New Level with Rocket Engine</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/nasa-just-took-3d-printing-to-whole-new-level-with-rocket-engine/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 19:57:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/nasa-just-took-3d-printing-to-whole-new-level-with-rocket-engine/</guid>
      <description>When 3D printing first appeared on the scene it was said by many scientists and economists that the process would spur a resurgence in ‘cottage industry’ entrepreneurship. While that prophecy has for the most part proven to be true, 3D printing has also been used by the ‘big boys’ to improve their operations. Take NASA for example. Popular Mechanics (PM) writes that the nation’s space agency has used a 3D printer to successfully produce a combustion chamber for a rocket engine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tired of Sitting in Traffic? Elon Musk Has a Solution &amp; It&#39;s a Beauty</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/tired-of-sitting-in-traffic-elon-musk-has-a-solution-its-a-beauty/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 19:35:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/tired-of-sitting-in-traffic-elon-musk-has-a-solution-its-a-beauty/</guid>
      <description>Frustrated by his daily commute, Tesla and Space-X CEO Elon Musk once vowed that he would dig a tunnel beneath Los Angeles and bypass the bumper-to-bumper traffic.
Traffic is driving me nuts. Am going to build a tunnel boring machine and just start digging...
&amp;mdash; Elon Musk (@elonmusk) December 17, 2016  Now, Musk is just months away from offering commuters the first maiden voyage of his subterranean shuttle system, writes the Los Angeles Times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Houston Company Creates Underwater &#34;Transformer&#34; - With a Submarine Instead of a Car</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/houston-company-creates-underwater-transformer-with-a-submarine-instead-of-a-car/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 17:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/houston-company-creates-underwater-transformer-with-a-submarine-instead-of-a-car/</guid>
      <description>A partnership between the U.S. Department of Defense and members of corporate oil is looking to make Mattel’s ‘Transformers’ a reality.
SubSeaWorldNews According to Live Science, DOD contractor Houston Mechatronics is a company founded by a former NASA robot engineer who is looking to design the first ever transforming submersible robot that will have both civilian and military applications.
SubSeaWorldNews On May 1, Houston Mechatronics announced that it had completed the hardest part of what will be called ‘Aquanaut’, a unmanned underwater vehicle (UUV) and remotely operated vehicle (ROV) weighing just over 2,000 lbs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robots Gain Incredible New Skills - Should Humans Be Worried?</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/robots-gain-incredible-new-skills-should-humans-be-worried/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 16:12:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/robots-gain-incredible-new-skills-should-humans-be-worried/</guid>
      <description>The age of mechanical devices performing programmed tasks has given way to the reign of the autonomous robot. Last year, Boston Dynamics released video of its four-legged robot called SpotMini. In the video, the robot showed how it could open and close doors, even holding it for open for others. When a human tried to prevent SpotMini from opening the door by swatting at its mechanical arm, the dog-like robot tried to continue with its task until it basically fought off the human.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>After Losing Ear in Tragic Accident, Doctors Grow Her a Replacement</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/after-losing-ear-in-tragic-accident-doctors-grow-her-a-replacement/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 15:39:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/after-losing-ear-in-tragic-accident-doctors-grow-her-a-replacement/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to medical advances and science, it is now possible for the body to aid in the regeneration of certain body parts. In 2016, Army Pvt. Shamika Burrage was involved in an auto accident that resulted in the loss of her right ear. She could still hear but without the funneling accoutrement of the exterior ear, Burrage did not get the best quality.
Live Science Surgeons at the William Beaumont Army Medical Center in El Paso, Texas decided to try a new procedure called prelaminated forearm free flap surgery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand Farmer Wakes Up to 200 Yd Wide Sink Hole</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/new-zealand-farmer-wakes-up-to-200-yd-wide-sink-hole/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 23:54:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/new-zealand-farmer-wakes-up-to-200-yd-wide-sink-hole/</guid>
      <description>The Earth appears to be going through some growing pains. In the news recently was the report of the massive fissure that appeared overnight in Kenya on March 18 and has been labeled the &amp;lsquo;Grand Kenyan&amp;rsquo;. At more than fifty feet deep and 65 feet wide, the fissure rungs for hundreds of yards and scientists believe it is a sign that the Dark Continent is succumbing to tectonic forces that are ripping the eastern half of the land mass apart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scientists in Lab Gain New Insight into How HIV Virus Works</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientists-in-lab-gain-new-insight-into-how-hiv-virus-works/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 23:42:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientists-in-lab-gain-new-insight-into-how-hiv-virus-works/</guid>
      <description>It looks like something out of a sci-fi horror movie. A glowing green alien life form closes in on its prey and shoots out green blasts of energy at its victim. The alien closes in and infects his adversary with a virus that he/she will spread to others. The incident detailed above occurred and was recorded by pathologists at the Institut Cochin in Paris who were studying the actual method and playing out of an HIV viral cell attacking a healthy cell in the human body.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>University of Toronto&#39;s 3D Skin Printer is AWESOME</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/university-of-torontos-3d-skin-printer-is-awesome/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 22:20:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/university-of-torontos-3d-skin-printer-is-awesome/</guid>
      <description>What do you get when you combine a hot glue gun, a 3D printer and modern skin-grafting techniques? Why you get the sci-fi-looking contraption developed by researchers at the University of Toronto, Canada.
Digital Trends Live Science writes that the prototype device — which weighs less than 2 lbs. (0.9 kilograms) —deposits a layer of &amp;ldquo;&amp;lsquo;bio-ink&amp;rsquo; when dragged across a surface. This ink contains materials normally present in the skin, including collagen, a protein that allows cells to grow and thrive; and fibrin, a protein that aids in blood clotting to help heal wounds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experts Reveal What&#39;s Next for Kilauea - And It&#39;s NOT Good</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/experts-reveal-whats-next-for-kilauea-and-its-not-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 22:06:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/experts-reveal-whats-next-for-kilauea-and-its-not-good/</guid>
      <description>A series of unfolding events in and around Hawaii’s Kilauea volcano has the potential to rain trouble down on the immediate area… literally. Before it started leaking lava last week, the lava lake in the crater atop Kilauea had ballooned like a Jiffy Pop bag due to the tremendous pressure from an expanding pool of magma and accompanying volcanic gas.
Wiki Commons Earthquakes triggered the “popping” of this balloon, sending lava slowly cascading down the east side of the mountain and causing numerous pockets of vapor to shoot out of the ground.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>For 2020: Uber Flying Taxis - Are You Ready?</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/for-2020-uber-flying-taxis-are-you-ready/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 19:36:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/for-2020-uber-flying-taxis-are-you-ready/</guid>
      <description>If their plans can become reality, Uber may one day be shuttling commuters and other patrons from one point to another aboard flying taxis. In a recent interview with CBS News&amp;rsquo; &amp;ldquo;CBS This Morning&amp;rdquo;, Uber CEO Dara Khosrowshahi revealed that &amp;lsquo;Uber Air&amp;rsquo; is in the conception phase, but the company is looking to make it a reality for people living in highly congested urban centers in the United States.
YouTube &amp;ldquo;We think cities are going to go vertical in terms of transportation and we want to make that a reality,&amp;ldquo; Khosrowshahi told CBS News&amp;rsquo; Bianna Golodryga.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Woman&#39;s Runny Nose Turns Out to Be Something Much More Serious</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/womans-runny-nose-turns-out-to-be-something-much-more-serious/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 18:57:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/womans-runny-nose-turns-out-to-be-something-much-more-serious/</guid>
      <description>Kendra Jackson of Omaha, Nebraska counted herself lucky in 2013 when she walked away from a car accident with a minor head injury resulting from her head hitting the dashboard of the car she was in. The bruising slowly went away. The pain receded as well&amp;hellip;at least temporarily.
Week Facts Years after her accident Jackson began to be plagued with debilitating headaches, dizziness, sleeplessness and a constant runny nose. Her primary care physician diagnosed her symptoms as results of severe allergies that were causing sinus infections.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Up Their Game in Search for Intelligent Life</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientists-up-their-game-in-search-for-intelligent-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 18:39:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientists-up-their-game-in-search-for-intelligent-life/</guid>
      <description>The search for extraterrestrial life got an upgrade recently, writes the Daily Mail. A scientific team from the University of California Berkeley launched their Breakthrough Listen project back in 2016. The team has been using the Parkes Radio Telescope in New South Wales, Australia to record any signals from space that it deems may be indicative of emanating from an intelligent source. The telescope recently got a new receiver hosting 13 beams and capable to scan the entire spectrum of the galaxy as seen from Down Under.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scientist: $180 Kit Can Help Criminals Avoid Prosecution</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientist-180-kit-can-help-criminals-avoid-prosecution/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 18:21:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientist-180-kit-can-help-criminals-avoid-prosecution/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been over a century since the police started using fingerprint evidence to solve crimes. As a work around, criminals simply started wearing gloves or wiping down whatever they touched at a crime scene. DNA is much more pervasive. A hair at a crime scene or dead skin under a victim&amp;rsquo;s fingernails could be matched to a criminal with DNA analysis, and there was nothing the bad guys could do about it, until now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Did the Vikings Navigate on Cloudy Days?  Scientists Now Think They Know</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/how-did-the-vikings-navigate-on-cloudy-days-scientists-now-think-they-know/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 19:52:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/how-did-the-vikings-navigate-on-cloudy-days-scientists-now-think-they-know/</guid>
      <description>How is it that the Vikings were able to ply the waters of the North Atlantic no matter the weather and occasions when celestial navigation points were hidden by cloud cover? Historians and scientists have long pondered the methods that could have been used. Recently a method long thought to be the musings of mystics has emerged as being, well, a very probable tool.
Pixabay During and after the time of the Vikings, from the 8th to the 11th centuries AD, there were folkish stories about how the Nordic seamen used &amp;lsquo;sunstones&amp;rsquo; to aid in navigating the waters of the fjords and beyond.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brain Breakthrough In Mice Could Mean Huge Help for Schizophrenia Patients</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/brain-breakthrough-in-mice-could-mean-huge-help-for-schizophrenia-patients/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 19:32:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/brain-breakthrough-in-mice-could-mean-huge-help-for-schizophrenia-patients/</guid>
      <description>The marvels of science are coming fast and furious these days. A big contributor to advances in our knowledge are mice. These little rodents have been used to test technology and treatments before they are (hopefully) adapted for use in or on humans.
Pixabay Popular Mechanics (PM)has the news that scientists at Rockefeller University in New York have developed a device capable of scanning and displaying in a 3D model, in real time, the brain activities of mice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lego Genius Creates Breakfast Making Machine &amp; It is AWESOME</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/lego-genius-creates-breakfast-making-machine-it-is-awesome/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 19:19:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/lego-genius-creates-breakfast-making-machine-it-is-awesome/</guid>
      <description>If you are or ever have been a parent, you will know the wave of defeat that washes over you when you enter your child&amp;rsquo;s room and see it carpeted with hundreds if not thousands of multi-colored Lego pieces or you may have had the &amp;lsquo;pleasure&amp;rsquo; of stepping on the sharp-edged tokens of torture in the middle of the night.
Pixabay If so, do not get frustrated and toss the blocks out because the Legos may aid in helping your offspring tap into possible engineering excellence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chile&#39;s Getting a New Telescope -- And It&#39;s a Monster</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/chiles-getting-a-new-telescope-and-its-a-monster/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 19:01:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/chiles-getting-a-new-telescope-and-its-a-monster/</guid>
      <description>The mountains of Chile are home to some of the most advanced astronomical equipment in the world today, and it looks like they&amp;rsquo;re about to get a new addition. Work has begun on the erection of what promises to be the world&amp;rsquo;s largest optical reflecting telescope in the world. Perched atop the nearly 10,000 foot high Cerro Armazones in Chile, the Extremely Large Telescope (ELT) is the brainchild of the European Southern Observatory and is expected to be up and running in 2024.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Utah Dinosaur Footprints Survived the Ages, But Not Humans</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/utah-dinosaur-footprints-survived-the-ages-but-not-humans/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 13:37:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/utah-dinosaur-footprints-survived-the-ages-but-not-humans/</guid>
      <description>Dinosaur footprints permanently encased in the ground in Utah have survived the elements for millions of years. Now they&amp;rsquo;re facing a new threat and it isn&amp;rsquo;t from Mother Nature, it&amp;rsquo;s from the tourists who come to view them each year.
Wikimedia Commons - Phil Konstantin Impressions from the remote past are being vandalized, intentionally and unintentionally, by guests visiting Red Fleet State Park in Utah, reports Fox News At an area around a reservoir, the &amp;lsquo;fossilized&amp;rsquo; footprints of the dilophosaurus, a species of raptor, are being removed from the ground and tossed into the natural water pit below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Create First Synthetic Embryos in Lab - Here&#39;s What it Means for Humans</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientists-create-first-synthetic-embryos-in-lab-heres-what-it-means-for-humans/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 13:17:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientists-create-first-synthetic-embryos-in-lab-heres-what-it-means-for-humans/</guid>
      <description>It is possible that in the near future infertile women will have access to proto-embryos that will go on to develop into viable human offspring.
IFLScience.com IFL Science writes that scientists from Maastricht University and the Hubrecht Institute in the Netherlands have successfully used the stem cells of mice to initiate the process of pregnancy in a mouse womb. Using bundles of the stem cells, the researchers created an embryo in a dish and when placed in a womb, it triggered a biochemical reaction that began to prepare the womb for pregnancy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Criminal Gangs Use High Tech to Fight the FBI</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/criminal-gangs-use-high-tech-to-fight-the-fbi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 02:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/criminal-gangs-use-high-tech-to-fight-the-fbi/</guid>
      <description>Last winter at an undisclosed town in the United States, officials with the Federal Bureau of Investigation&amp;rsquo;s hostage rescue unit moved in to begin an extraction operation. Agents fanned out around the scene, some in obvious positions while others sat or lay concealed in other spots.
Digital Addicts Blog Not long after arriving on scene and staging personnel, the FBI team was harassed by a swarm of drones that made &amp;ldquo;high-speed, low passes at agents in the observation post&amp;rdquo; in an attempt to flush them out and prevent the Bureau from having eyes on the scene.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is This Planet the Closest Thing to an Earthlike Planet?  Scientists Think It Is</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/is-this-planet-the-closest-thing-to-an-earthlike-planet-scientists-think-it-is/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 23:42:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/is-this-planet-the-closest-thing-to-an-earthlike-planet-scientists-think-it-is/</guid>
      <description>Astronomers and other scientists focused on finding a habitable &amp;lsquo;earth-like&amp;rsquo; exoplanet in the cosmos have many requirements that have to be met before they seriously zero in on a candidate. One of these requirements is that the planet have a sizable iron core that would lend itself to the creation and maintenance of a magnetosphere.
NASA In February of 2017, European astronomers went public with the news that they had discovered a seven-planet orbiting the nearby star TRAPPIST-1, a celestial object located 39.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sir Richard Branson&#39;s Bringing the Space Age to the Desert in Dubai</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/sir-richard-bransons-bringing-the-space-age-to-the-desert-in-dubai/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 23:13:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/sir-richard-bransons-bringing-the-space-age-to-the-desert-in-dubai/</guid>
      <description>The future of overland cargo shipment and human travel is taking shape in the deserts of Dubai.
The Daily Mail writes that billionaire entrepreneur Richard Branson, founder and CEO of Virgin, is getting behind the development of what is called hyperloop technology.
Daily Mail Hyperloop uses a pod and tube system in which the pods are levitated and accelerated through the tubal system through electromagnetism, reaching speeds of up to 760mph.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Reveal Sun&#39;s Plans to Go Out with a Bang</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientists-reveal-suns-plans-to-go-out-with-a-bang/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 22:28:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientists-reveal-suns-plans-to-go-out-with-a-bang/</guid>
      <description>When it comes time for our Sun to essentially die, it will do so in a brilliant fashion. Following its planned end-of-life explosion 10 billion years from now, an enormous nebulous cloud of dust and gas will swirl throughout the void and, scientists now predict, will radiate a light that will slowly diminish over 100,000 years as the celestial debris coalesces into a white dwarf star.
Pixabay Previously, the scientific community thought that our sun was not large enough to form a glowing nebula, but after observing the luminescent remains of suns similar in size back in the 1980s, doubts emerged.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NASA Bringing Back Supersonic Air Travel - With No Sonic Boom</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/nasa-bringing-back-supersonic-air-travel-with-no-sonic-boom/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 22:02:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/nasa-bringing-back-supersonic-air-travel-with-no-sonic-boom/</guid>
      <description>Supersonic commercial flights have been hiatus since 2003, after the British-French Concorde went belly up to due to expensive operations and prohibitive passenger fares. While aeronautic enthusiasts mourned the end of such flights, those living in the path of the incoming and outgoing airplanes felt relief that the loud, bone rattling sonic booms of the Concorde would no longer be heard.
Wikimedia Commons If NASA has its way, though, supersonic flights will make a comeback soon, but will do so much more quietly, reports Fox News.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4.5 Quake Gives Californians Early Morning Wakeup Call - What&#39;s Next?</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/4-5-quake-gives-californians-early-morning-wakeup-call-whats-next/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 21:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/4-5-quake-gives-californians-early-morning-wakeup-call-whats-next/</guid>
      <description>From Yellowstone to Hawaii to the Gulf of Mexico, the Earth has been shaking and trembling in ways that have some people wondering what&amp;rsquo;s going on, and others warning that something bigger &amp;ndash; much bigger is on the horizon.
Los Angeles Times The conversation about what&amp;rsquo;s happening only intensified on Tuesday after residents of Southern California were jolted awake with a 4.5 earthquake at 4:49 am. The epicenter was near San Gorgonio Pass about 85 mile east of downtown Los Angeles, but it was felt from San Diego to Santa Clarita.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Major Hospitals Turn to &#34;Alternative&#34; Therapy to Heal Patients</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/major-hospitals-turn-to-alternative-therapy-to-heal-patients/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 20:34:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/major-hospitals-turn-to-alternative-therapy-to-heal-patients/</guid>
      <description>If the hospital doctor gazes deeply into your eyes and tells you that you&amp;rsquo;re getting very, very sleepy, it might not be from any sort of anesthetic.That&amp;rsquo;s because the Wall Street Journal is reporting that many major hospitals are now turning to hypnosis as a medical solution for some of their patients.
Flickr From the Wall Street Journal: Hypnotherapy—when patients enter a trance-like state using relaxation and visual images—is often associated with alternative medicine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep Sea Divers Encounter Bizarre Sea Creature</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/deep-sea-divers-encounter-bizarre-sea-creature/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 19:12:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/deep-sea-divers-encounter-bizarre-sea-creature/</guid>
      <description>Many have claimed that we know more about outer space than we do about the depths of our own oceans and that may be true. Fortunately technology and know-how is helping us to plunge the deeper and deeper into the ocean depths, and we&amp;rsquo;re finding some pretty remarkable things.
__
IFLScience This is exactly what happened when the Nautilus Live expedition was exploring the ocean floor and a sea creature known as as siphonore appeared in one of the cameras on its remote operating vehicle (ROV).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jupiter and Venus are Warping Earth&#39;s Orbit -- And It&#39;s Messing With Our Climate</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/jupiter-and-venus-are-warping-earths-orbit-and-its-messing-with-our-climate/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 16:41:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/jupiter-and-venus-are-warping-earths-orbit-and-its-messing-with-our-climate/</guid>
      <description>You ever have those people in your life that, whenever you&amp;rsquo;re around them, can just kind of knock you out of your orbit? Well, the Earth does, too! Except those people are planets and they go by the name of &amp;ldquo;Jupiter&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Venus.&amp;rdquo;
Pixabay Scientists are finally confirming what they&amp;rsquo;ve suspected for many years, that every 405,000 years the gravitational pull of Jupiter and Venus warp the Earth&amp;rsquo;s orbit from a circular orbit around the Sun to one that&amp;rsquo;s 5% elliptical.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Jersey Beach Gets Visit from Sea Monster</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/new-jersey-beach-gets-visit-from-sea-monster/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 15:19:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/new-jersey-beach-gets-visit-from-sea-monster/</guid>
      <description>The depths of the Atlantic Ocean have given up one of its rarities this past week, alarming beach-goers and exciting marine biologists and paleo-anthropologists.
Daily Star On May 4, Stephanie Hall of Ocean Gate, NJ was on a morning run on Island Beach State Park, located along the coast at about the mid-way point of the Jersey shoreline, when she spot a rather strange looking head from the appearing to look around.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Study Love Lives of Senior Citizens - Here are the Results</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/researchers-study-love-lives-of-senior-citizens-here-are-the-results/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 21:46:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/researchers-study-love-lives-of-senior-citizens-here-are-the-results/</guid>
      <description>Can the golden years in life still be a time of sexual desire and intimacy? This is the question asked by scientists out of Michigan. According to a report from the University of Michigan referenced by The Guardian, there is a sizeable chunk of seniors that are still sexually active and a much larger cadre of elders who say that sex is important in all stages of life.
Pixabay The Michigan research found that 40% of those surveyed between the ages of 65 and 80 were sexually active.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Complete Radar Scan of King Tut&#39;s Tomb - Here are the Surprising Results</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientists-complete-radar-scan-of-king-tuts-tomb-here-are-the-surprising-results/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 21:31:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientists-complete-radar-scan-of-king-tuts-tomb-here-are-the-surprising-results/</guid>
      <description>The buzz all started in 2015 when archaeologists studied high resolution images of the northern and western internal walls of King Tut&amp;rsquo;s tomb. Zooming in on the high resolution images, they found markings in the plaster the bore and uncanny resemblance to ones found by Howard Carter in 1922.
Pixabay Carter&amp;rsquo;s markings turned out to be the entrance to King Tut&amp;rsquo;s Tomb itself! So, when scientists made the discovery and then radar specialist Hirokatsu Watanabe confirmed their findings in 2016, Egyptologists minds ran wild with the possibilities of what could be found in the secret chamber.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Discover Surprising Hidden Benefit of Fasting</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientists-discover-surprising-hidden-benefit-of-fasting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 20:12:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientists-discover-surprising-hidden-benefit-of-fasting/</guid>
      <description>Fasting has long been a part of the world&amp;rsquo;s major religions and has even caught on within the past few years as a health trend here in the United States. Some people fast intermittently, restricting their food intake to just a few hours a day, while some bio-hackers are fasting for days at a time. Scientists are now taking a closer look at fasting and its health benefits, and they&amp;rsquo;re making some interesting discoveries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Quantum Anomaly Changes What We Know About Reality</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/a-quantum-anomaly-changes-what-we-know-about-reality/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 19:33:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/a-quantum-anomaly-changes-what-we-know-about-reality/</guid>
      <description>There are some in the scientific community who believe that we are on the cusp of a fundamental shift in the perceived reality, or paradigm, experienced by humanity, or at least those populations exposed to current scientific breakthroughs.
Pixabay Scientific American reports that as researchers delve deeper into quantum mechanics, unlocking the mysteries it holds, there is a growing cognitive shift in how ‘reality’ is perceived. The shift, if it occurs, will involve humanity’s departure from the non-contextuality of our sensory observations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Look to Medieval Period for Proof of Planet 9</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/researchers-look-to-medieval-period-for-proof-of-planet-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 19:17:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/researchers-look-to-medieval-period-for-proof-of-planet-9/</guid>
      <description>There are some astronomers who have theorized that in the depths of our solar system, far beyond the orbit of Neptune, there is a large cold planet that has evaded discovery by modern researchers. ‘Planet Nine’, as it has been dubbed, may have been knowingly or unknowingly revealed by our medieval ancestors.
NASA Fox News writes that two researchers from Queen&amp;rsquo;s University Belfast in Northern Ireland are searching through old scrolls and tapestries from the Medieval era, like the famous Bayeux Tapestry that showed the 1066 AD appearance of Haley’s Comet, looking for clues about Planet Nine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent Scientific Brain Breakthrough Sparks Huge Ethical Debate</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/recent-scientific-brain-breakthrough-sparks-huge-ethical-debate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 15:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/recent-scientific-brain-breakthrough-sparks-huge-ethical-debate/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to scientists at Yale University, specific vignettes from Matt Goening’s ‘Futurama’ may be far from science fiction. In April, the scientists were able to reanimate the brains of 100 pigs that had been killed beforehand. For thirty-six hours, the swine brains were kept ‘functioning’ and has given a glimmer of hope that such a process could be replicated in primates and then humans. Enter the clips of Futurama’s ‘heads in jars’ scenes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rare Earthquake Strikes on Sunday - Is This a Sign of Something Bigger?</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/rare-earthquake-strikes-on-sunday-is-this-a-sign-of-something-bigger/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 14:53:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/rare-earthquake-strikes-on-sunday-is-this-a-sign-of-something-bigger/</guid>
      <description>With Kilauea erupting and Yellowstone trembling, reports of another earthquake really aren&amp;rsquo;t that surprising. The location, however, is something of a head scratcher. On Sunday, the U.S. Geological Survey, reported that an earthquake took place 160 miles southeast of New Orleans and 120 miles southeast of Grand Isle.
The Weather Channel The 4.9 quake was also reported by the National Tsunami Warning Center, but it was not strong enough to create a real threat of a tsunami.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Vents Open on Erupting Hawaiian Volcano - This is NOT Good</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/new-vents-open-on-erupting-hawaiian-volcano-this-is-not-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2018 17:32:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/new-vents-open-on-erupting-hawaiian-volcano-this-is-not-good/</guid>
      <description>Living conditions have not gotten any better for folks living on the big island of Hawaii. Between the earthquakes and volcanic eruptions that have taken place in the past few days, many evacuated residents are wondering when and if they&amp;rsquo;ll ever be able to return home.
Max Pixel On Friday the Island was rocked by an earthquake measuring 6.9 on the Richter scale, the largest quake recorded their in more than 40 years, and the rumbling continued into Saturday as the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Best Houseplants for Purifying Your Home&#39;s Air and Keeping it Free From Toxins</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/5-best-houseplants-for-purifying-your-homes-air-and-keeping-it-free-from-toxins/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 21:42:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/5-best-houseplants-for-purifying-your-homes-air-and-keeping-it-free-from-toxins/</guid>
      <description>The vast majority of our lives is spent breathing indoor air. Whether at home or at the office, the quality of our breathing is only as good as the quality of air to take in. Fortunately, several species of house plant not only beautify our surroundings, but also purify the air you breathe. Here are some species you may want to add to your home or office: 1) Spider Plant</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Weekend&#39;s Meteor Shower is Brought to You By Halley&#39;s Comet - Here&#39;s Where to See It</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/this-weekends-meteor-shower-is-brought-to-you-by-halleys-comet-heres-where-to-see-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 17:57:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/this-weekends-meteor-shower-is-brought-to-you-by-halleys-comet-heres-where-to-see-it/</guid>
      <description>Halley&amp;rsquo;s Comet - 1986 - NASA
[/caption] Halley&amp;rsquo;s Comet itself won&amp;rsquo;t be coming around this part of our galaxy again for another 43 years or so, but thanks to the Earth crossing its path, we&amp;rsquo;ll be treated to quite the meteor spectacle in the pre-dawn hours of this weekend. Regular skywatchers know where to look to see the meteor shower that will be taking place this weekend and again in October but for the rest of us, here&amp;rsquo;s where and when to look.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Record World Record High Temperature for Month of April - Here&#39;s Where It Happened</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientists-record-world-record-high-temperature-for-month-of-april-heres-where-it-happened/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 15:09:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientists-record-world-record-high-temperature-for-month-of-april-heres-where-it-happened/</guid>
      <description>As the debate about climate change rages on, scientists are offering some new evidence to the argument in the form of extreme temperature recordings. This latest one comes from Pakistan where scientists documented a world record temperature for the month of April. The temperature was recorded at a weather station in Nawabshah, Pakistan, where it was 122.4 degrees Fahrenheit in the shade!
Weather-Forecast.com[/caption] From IFLScience: It&amp;rsquo;s only May, and this year is setting new standards in terrifying extreme temperatures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NASA&#39;s New Fission Reactor Could Revolutionize Space Travel</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/nasas-new-fission-reactor-could-revolutionize-space-travel/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 14:37:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/nasas-new-fission-reactor-could-revolutionize-space-travel/</guid>
      <description>NASA[/caption] For years the possibility of nuclear fission has given hope to mankind. Nuclear fission would help us break our dependence on fossil fuels and help us power longer flights into deep space. Well, NASA has been experimenting with a nuclear fission power system and, so far, the results have gone extremely well. From IFLScience: The system is called Kilopower, and it involves using the heat generated by uranium to produce power.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NY Airport Robot Accused of Sexual Harrassment</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/ny-airport-robot-accused-of-sexual-harrassment/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 13:37:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/ny-airport-robot-accused-of-sexual-harrassment/</guid>
      <description>NY Post[/caption] New York’s LaGuardia Airport, like most major airline hubs, have their entrances swarmed by taxis looking to scoop up passengers before their competitors. The cutthroat business has resulted in the cabs ignoring parking protocols and idling areas. To combat this, LaGuardia has used security officers on foot to shoo away the cabbies, but that ended three months ago when the airport deployed the Knightscope K5 robot. It was hoped that the robot would be able to cover more ground in a more effective manner than its human predecessor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Utah Family Digging in Backyard Uncovers Ancient Horse</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/utah-family-digging-in-backyard-uncovers-ancient-horse/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 21:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/utah-family-digging-in-backyard-uncovers-ancient-horse/</guid>
      <description>CBS 4 Denver[/caption] Residents of Utah are not strangers to finding fossilized animal remains in the soil of their home state. Over the years, Utahans have found mammoths, saber-toothed cats, and a short faced bear, and now the Hill family can add an Ice Age shetland pony to that list. From AtlasObscura.com: While removing a sandbank from their back yard, the Hill family came across a strange skeleton they could not recognize.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Weekend&#39;s Meteor Shower is Courtesy of Halley&#39;s Comet</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/this-weekends-meteor-shower-is-courtesy-of-halleys-comet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 20:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/this-weekends-meteor-shower-is-courtesy-of-halleys-comet/</guid>
      <description>Wikimedia Commons
If you look toward the southeastern skies this weekend in the hours before dawn, the chances are good that you can see a pretty good meteor shower eminating from the constellation of Aquarius. What you may not realize, however, is that this meteor shower, and another one hitting our skies in October, is a direct result of Halley&amp;rsquo;s Comet. From EarthSky.org: Halley’s Comet, proud parent of two meteor showers, swings into the inner solar system about every 76 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nerdy &amp; Creepy Cuff Links of 1900 Pay Homage to Louis Pasteur</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/nerdy-creepy-cuff-links-of-1900-pay-homage-to-louis-pasteur/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 19:48:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/nerdy-creepy-cuff-links-of-1900-pay-homage-to-louis-pasteur/</guid>
      <description>ScienceMuseum.org.uk[/caption] Google &amp;ldquo;gifts for Dad,&amp;rdquo; and you&amp;rsquo;ll see things turn up like, watches, t-shirts, golf balls, ties, cigars, beer mugs, and everything in between. Try as you may, however, you probably won&amp;rsquo;t see anything like these Faberge cufflinks from 1900. Back then, it was possible to give dear old Dad the gift of the Black Death. That is if the Science Museum in London can part with their ownership of Faberge cufflinks bearing the image of Yersinia pestis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nurse&#39;s Horrifying Video of Lungs Will Make Anyone a Non-Smoker</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/nurses-horrifying-video-of-lungs-will-make-anyone-a-non-smoker/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 19:23:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/nurses-horrifying-video-of-lungs-will-make-anyone-a-non-smoker/</guid>
      <description>Amanda Eller / Facebook[/caption] A nurse from North Carolina is using Facebook to get in the faces &amp;ndash; and heads &amp;ndash; of cigarette smokers. IFL Science reports that Amanda Eller used the social media site to provide a very real and unsettling look at how cigarette smoke impairs the respiratory system in humans. In the video, there is placed on a table in a medical facility two sets of lungs. One from a smoker of one pack a day for twenty years and the other lungs from a ‘healthy person’.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rare Tasmanian Tiger Could Soon Be Brought Back from Extinction</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/rare-tasmanian-tiger-could-soon-be-brought-back-from-extinction/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 19:20:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/rare-tasmanian-tiger-could-soon-be-brought-back-from-extinction/</guid>
      <description>Australia’s Outback has been less crowded the past eighty years since the believed extinction of the thylacine or Tasmanian Tiger. The strange looking beast was a large stripped dingo-looking marsupial who entered the pages of history in 1936, when the last of its kind died in a Washington, D.C. zoo. Recent headway made by scientists looking to resurrect the woolly mammoth, however, have given biologists hope that the Tiger can once more roam the rugged terrain of the Outback.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here are the Warning Signs Super Volcanos Give Before They Blow</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/here-are-the-warning-signs-super-volcanos-give-before-they-blow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 16:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/here-are-the-warning-signs-super-volcanos-give-before-they-blow/</guid>
      <description>Rumblings, geyser eruptions and growing magma chambers at Yellowstone National Park in Wyoming have been unnerving citizens in and around the area lately, causing many to wonder if the super volcano underneath the park is about to erupt.
MaxPixel.net[/caption] A new study just release by academics from Illinois should help allay those fears. A paper authored by geologist Patricia Gregg and PhD student, Haley Cabaniss, both of the University of Illinois, is claiming that any imminent large-scale eruption would be proceeded by hundreds if not thousands of years of increased tectonic activity, a growing magma chamber and geological ‘uplift’ measured in meters and not inches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WintOGreen Lifesaver Effect May Be Responsible for Strange Light Over Arkansas</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/wintogreen-lifesaver-effect-may-be-responsible-for-strange-light-over-arkansas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 15:58:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/wintogreen-lifesaver-effect-may-be-responsible-for-strange-light-over-arkansas/</guid>
      <description>Some people say the mysterious light in the woods near Gurdon, Arkansas is the ghostly lantern of railroad worker who was murdered along the tracks. Others say it&amp;rsquo;s a scientific phenomenon akin to the one created by chomping down hard on Wint-O-Green Lifesavers, but all agree there&amp;rsquo;s definitely a strange light in woods near Gurdon.
http://www.flickr.com/photos/moneyman1870/[/caption]
In honor of the mysterious ‘Gurdon light’ and the folksinger whose name it so closely resembles, we&amp;rsquo;ve filled this article with several references to Gordon Lightfoot songs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Details Behind NASA&#39;s Latest Mission to Mars</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-details-behind-nasas-latest-mission-to-mars/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 14:43:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-details-behind-nasas-latest-mission-to-mars/</guid>
      <description>NASA - Jet Propulsion Laboratory[/caption] For all of its desolate alien façade, Mars has enough similarities to Earth to continually intrigue scientists. On May 5, NASA’s Jet Propulsion Laboratory will be launching another probe to the Red Planet but this one will not have the superficial focus of prior Mars Rovers, reports Science News. Skin Deep
Astronomists and scientists look upon Mars as the closest planetary copy of Earth that is within the ‘easy’ grasp of exploratory satellites and probes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweden&#39;s New Roads are Huge Step Toward Eliminating Fossil Fuels</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/swedens-new-roads-are-huge-step-toward-eliminating-fossil-fuels/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 14:25:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/swedens-new-roads-are-huge-step-toward-eliminating-fossil-fuels/</guid>
      <description>Sweden has big plans for saving the planet and they&amp;rsquo;re already making some positive gains. As a country, they&amp;rsquo;ve set the ambitious goal of reducing greenhouse gas emissions by 70% and being totally independent of fossil fuel by the year 2030.
eRoadArlanda[/caption] One way they&amp;rsquo;re hoping to accomplish this goal is with vehicle-charging electrified roads. Basically, they&amp;rsquo;re embedding electric conductors in the roads which constantly recharges electric cars that pass over the road.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious Eye in Appears in Sky Over the Netherlands</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/mysterious-eye-in-appears-in-sky-over-the-netherlands/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 21:44:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/mysterious-eye-in-appears-in-sky-over-the-netherlands/</guid>
      <description>The sky above the Netherlands on April 22 was the typical cloudy setting that natives are used to around this time of year. One thing that was not typical was an unusual cloud formation that had people offering various interpretations of what was being seen. One Eye Open The UK’s Express reports that on the aforementioned date a “monstrous eye in the sky” made from clouds appeared in the heavens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Australian Gvt Spending $500 Million in Attempt to Save Great Barrier Reef</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/australian-gvt-spending-500-million-in-attempt-to-save-great-barrier-reef/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 21:13:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/australian-gvt-spending-500-million-in-attempt-to-save-great-barrier-reef/</guid>
      <description>Great Barrier Reef - Wikimedia Commons We don&amp;rsquo;t know if it&amp;rsquo;s because the government of Australia has suddenly become very eco-conscious or because their $6.4 billion/year ($4.8 billion US) revenue generator is in trouble, but the Aussie government is finally making a substantial investment in protecting and rejuvenating this great natural treasure. Here&amp;rsquo;s the story from NPR: Australia&amp;rsquo;s government is investing 500 million Australian dollars (more than $377 million U.S.) to protect the Great Barrier Reef, which has been struggling to cope with storm damage, coral-eating starfish and bleaching events triggered by warmer oceans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things Continue to Heat Up Under Yellowstone National Park</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/things-continue-to-heat-up-under-yellowstone-national-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 20:03:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/things-continue-to-heat-up-under-yellowstone-national-park/</guid>
      <description>The signs that something is brewing beneath the earth at Wyoming’s Yellowstone National Park are increasing. Seismic events have been increasingly common, scientists have discovered that a magma bloom under the soil is larger than expected and much closer to the surface than previously thought and the venting of sulfur dioxide have been more and more common and lethal for indigenous fauna in the area. The Independent now reports that another sign has popped up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flat Earthers Have 1st Convention - Explain Why People Don&#39;t Fall Off the Edge</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/flat-earthers-have-1st-convention-explain-why-people-dont-fall-off-the-edge/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 19:37:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/flat-earthers-have-1st-convention-explain-why-people-dont-fall-off-the-edge/</guid>
      <description>Johnson Space Center - NASA In case you haven&amp;rsquo;t been paying attention, the flat Earth movement is a serious movement that&amp;rsquo;s gaining momentum &amp;ndash; especially among our younger members of society. Recent polling reveals that 16% of 18-24 year olds are &amp;ldquo;not sure&amp;rdquo; that the Earth is a sphere, and 10% of millenials now also have their doubts. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t help that celebrities, like the rapper B.o.B, are also now using their status to push the theory:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Astronomers Discover Hidden Galaxy Orbiting Around Milky Way</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/astronomers-discover-hidden-galaxy-orbiting-around-milky-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 17:02:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/astronomers-discover-hidden-galaxy-orbiting-around-milky-way/</guid>
      <description>NASA/JPL-Caltech/S. Stolovy (SSC/Caltech) Astronomers at Carnegie Mellon University have just discovered a tiny dwarf galaxy orbiting our solar system, which had somehow managed to avoid detection until now. Pretty sneaky, if you ask us! Here&amp;rsquo;s more from Alphr.com: _Visible from Earth’s southern hemisphere, roughly 90,000 lightyears away from the sun, the researchers explain Hydrus 1 is a faint, mildly elliptical galaxy that stretches only about 326 lightyears across. By comparison, our own Milky Way galaxy is around 100,000 lightyears across.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stephen Hawking&#39;s Final Theory on the Universe Published Today - Here&#39;s What It Says</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/stephen-hawkings-final-theory-on-the-universe-published-today-heres-what-it-says/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 16:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/stephen-hawkings-final-theory-on-the-universe-published-today-heres-what-it-says/</guid>
      <description>Flickr Famed theoretical physicist Stephen Hawking passed away in March of this year, but his final theory about the Universe has been published today. The study, published in conjunction with former student and frequent collaborator Thomas Hertog, addresses the conflict that arise between quantum mechanics and Einstein&amp;rsquo;s general relativity theory. From EarthSky.org: Hawking and Hertog’s latest study deals specifically with a subset of Big Bang theory, called eternal inflation. Most modern Big Bang theories incorporate the idea of an inflation, which calls for an exponential expansion of space in the universe’s first fraction of a second.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archaeologist Finds Evidence to Prove Existence of Biblical King David</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/archaeologist-finds-evidence-to-prove-existence-of-biblical-king-david/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 15:01:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/archaeologist-finds-evidence-to-prove-existence-of-biblical-king-david/</guid>
      <description>The story of David and Goliath is one of the most widely known stories in the world. It&amp;rsquo;s hard to read about one sports team upsetting another without hearing it used as a parable. It even shows up in the Koran. Yet, historians have yet to agree on whether or not David was a real person.
King David Playing Harp by Gerard van Honthorst - Wikimedia Commons That&amp;rsquo;s why this recent discovery of an ancient city outside of Jerusalem is raising some eybrows in the archaeological world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chocolate Fans Are Going to Love This</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/chocolate-fans-are-going-to-love-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 20:52:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/chocolate-fans-are-going-to-love-this/</guid>
      <description>PX Here[/caption] Chocolate and red wine, two things humans love to over-indulge in because they read somewhere that it was good for you. Well, this article doesn&amp;rsquo;t address the red wine, but there have been some recent studies on chocolate that will put a smile on chocolate lovers&amp;rsquo; faces. From ScienceDaily.com: New research shows there might be health benefits to eating certain types of dark chocolate. Findings from two studies being presented today at the Experimental Biology 2018 annual meeting in San Diego show that consuming dark chocolate that has a high concentration of cacao (minimally 70% cacao, 30% organic cane sugar) has positive effects on stress levels, inflammation, mood, memory and immunity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breakthrough Brain Technology Could Restore Sight to the Blind</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/breakthrough-brain-technology-could-restore-sight-to-the-blind/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 19:56:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/breakthrough-brain-technology-could-restore-sight-to-the-blind/</guid>
      <description>It seems that every single day scientists make a breakthrough that seems impossible. For people who have to deal with the loss of a sense, such as sight, hearing, or touch, this recent breakthrough may prove to be especially exciting.
Brain in Human[/caption] The Independent reports that neurologists have made a tremendous advance in undoing the loss of senses in some people. Using what has become referred to as a ‘holographic brain modulator’, scientists have crafted for themselves the ability to target sensory receptors in the body with encoded hologram stimuli that reportedly mimics that of real external forces like light and the contact of objects on someone’s skin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent US Solar Eclipse Set Off Atmospheric Wave Measured Around the Globe</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/recent-us-solar-eclipse-set-off-atmospheric-wave-measured-around-the-globe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 19:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/recent-us-solar-eclipse-set-off-atmospheric-wave-measured-around-the-globe/</guid>
      <description>Flickr[/caption] Did you see the bug total solar eclipse last August? Did you feel it? If not, don’t fret, because while the eclipse did indeed case a palpable sensation, it did so at around 180 miles above the Earth’s surface. On August 21, 2017 many Americans and Canadians lifted their protected eyes to the heavens to take in a rare total solar eclipse. For an average of two minutes, midday turned a bit darker in spots and downright nighttime in others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Authorities Raid Poacher&#39;s House in Madagascar - Agents Shocked at What They Found</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/authorities-raid-poachers-house-in-madagascar-agents-shocked-at-what-they-found/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 18:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/authorities-raid-poachers-house-in-madagascar-agents-shocked-at-what-they-found/</guid>
      <description>Wikimedia Commons[/caption] An emergency visit by a team from Madagascar’s environmental agency as well as police to a home in Toliara recently uncovered what looks to be a smuggling operation of epic proportions. As agents from the government descended on the abode, following complaints from neighbors of a rancid smell coming from the two story building, they interrupted the work of three people in the process of burying deceased radiated tortoises.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harvard Scientists Hope This Extinct Animal Can Make a &#39;Mammoth&#39; Comeback</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/harvard-scientists-hope-this-extinct-animal-can-make-a-mammoth-comeback/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 18:13:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/harvard-scientists-hope-this-extinct-animal-can-make-a-mammoth-comeback/</guid>
      <description>Wikimedia Commons[/caption] The Flintstones&amp;rsquo; dishwasher is one step closer to being resurrected. Move over Maytag! Make way for the Woolly Mammoth! C/Net reports now that scientists have successfully duplicated 44 mammoth genes, they are now hoping to grow a mammoth-hybrid in an artificial womb. The large hairy elephant walked the earth as early as 2.5 million years ago before going extinct around 3rd millennium B.C. A team of researchers at Harvard University, headed up by well-known geneticist Professor George Church, participated in the Fourth International Vatican Conference in Vatican City on April 27.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Common Virus Linked to 7 Autoimmune Diseases</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/common-virus-linked-to-7-autoimmune-diseases/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 16:42:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/common-virus-linked-to-7-autoimmune-diseases/</guid>
      <description>Cells with Epstein Barr Virus | Wikimedia Commons[/caption] In a stunning bit of news, the Cincinnati Children’s Hospital has announced that a team of its researchers have concluded that the injection at least some forms of viral DNA into the human lymphatic system may be causing the onset of seven debilitating diseases. IFLScience writes that a study of patients who received shots of the Epstein-Barr Virus (EBV) as part of a vaccination process against mononucleosis (mono) had increased chances of developing autoimmune diseases such as lupus, multiple sclerosis, rheumatoid arthritis, juvenile idiopathic arthritis, inflammatory bowel disease, celiac disease, and type 1 diabetes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crime Researcher Releases Shocking Fact About Number of Serial Killers in US</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/crime-researcher-releases-shocking-fact-about-number-of-serial-killers-in-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 16:01:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/crime-researcher-releases-shocking-fact-about-number-of-serial-killers-in-us/</guid>
      <description>Vox[/caption] “The taste of death that lives within He loves it when he Tastes their final breath Stalking gives him pleasure Killing is the final act He takes no pity With his lust for death.” &amp;mdash;-’Psycho Man’, Ozzy Osbourne The recent arrest of the notorious Golden State Killer, a man now identified as 72-year-old Joseph James DeAngelo Jr, caused the resurfacing of our society’s recurrent predations by serial killers. DeAngelo operated for over a decade, from the 1970s to the 1980s, terrorizing parts of California with his ten murders and 46 known rapes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Underwater Robot Confirms Scientists Greatest Fears in Gulf of Oman</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/underwater-robot-confirms-scientists-greatest-fears-in-gulf-of-oman/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 15:34:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/underwater-robot-confirms-scientists-greatest-fears-in-gulf-of-oman/</guid>
      <description>Flickr | Gulf of Oman | by Francisco Anzola[/caption] It seems like every day we&amp;rsquo;re learning something new about the oceans. Sometimes we discover new sea life or new ways that animals communicate with each other under water, other times, however, we come across disturbing features like this one&amp;hellip; Recently, robots exploring the depths of the Gulf of Oman have discovered a &amp;ldquo;dead zone&amp;rdquo; the size of Scotland! From IFLScience: “Our research shows that the situation is actually worse than feared – and that the area of dead zone is vast and growing,” said Dr Bastien Queste, who led the research published this week in Geophysical Research Letter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yes, There Really Are Exploding Ants</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/yes-there-really-are-exploding-ants/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 22:23:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/yes-there-really-are-exploding-ants/</guid>
      <description>As acts of terror and acts of war, humans have been willing to destroy themselves if it meant killing the enemy. From kamikaze pilots to suicide bombers, this is nothing new. What&amp;rsquo;s surprising, though, is that there&amp;rsquo;s a counter part to this in the animal kingdom. Popular Mechanics has written an article that tells of a certain species of ant that acts, in essence, like a suicide bomber.
Poplular Mechanics[/caption] Self-Sacrifice It has been known for decades now that the worker segment of the Colobopsis species of ant exploded as part of their defensive tools against predators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Police Found in This Doctor&#39;s Mansion Has San Antonio Residents Freaking Out!</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/what-police-found-in-this-doctors-mansion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 21:28:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/what-police-found-in-this-doctors-mansion/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;We couldn&amp;rsquo;t believe what we found inside the home,&amp;rdquo; San Antonio police officer Chet Daniels said. &amp;ldquo;In all my years on the force, I&amp;rsquo;ve never seen anything like this. There were cats and dogs everywhere, just covered in fecal matter. It was sad.&amp;rdquo; 
When police officer C. Daniels served a warrant on a luxurious home around 8 a.m. on Sunday, he expected it to be a routine call. After receiving noise and smell complaints from neighbors, officer Daniels and his partner Jason Stewart paid a visit to the well-to-do 100 block of Sioux Circle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swiss Scientists Observe Einstein&#39;s &#34;Spooky Tale&#34; in Action</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/swiss-scientists-observe-einsteins-spooky-tale-in-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 21:27:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/swiss-scientists-observe-einsteins-spooky-tale-in-action/</guid>
      <description>There is no more bizarre world than that of quantum physics. In this realm, truth is indeed stranger than any science fiction that could be conceived of by man.
Wikipedia
One aspect of this strange world is an eight decade mystery that may be close to being solved, writes Live Science. A ‘Spooky’ Tale In 1935, physicists and theoreticians Albert Einsein, Boris Podolsky and Nathan Rosen were trying to make heads and tails of a rather strange occurrence in the quantum realm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk Just Fired His Robots and Hired Humans to Take Their Places</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/elon-musk-just-fired-his-robots-and-hired-humans-to-take-their-places/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 20:50:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/elon-musk-just-fired-his-robots-and-hired-humans-to-take-their-places/</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk, the founder and current CEO of Tesla, Inc., has been sleeping on a couch at his company’s Fremont, California plant lately following a slowdown in production that has caught the attention of the public in the last few weeks.
Flickr - pestoverde[/caption] Inconvenient Conveyors…And Automation The Freemont plant is centered around the production of the Tesla Model 3 electric car. When the model was announced, Musk told the public that it would run consumers $35,000, a very reasonable price, to purchase the car and that the California facility would pump out 5,000 vehicles a week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>N. Korea&#39;s ‘Tired Mountain’ May Be The Real Reason Kim Jong Un is Ready for Peace</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/n-koreas-tired-mountain-may-be-the-real-reason-kim-jong-un-is-ready-for-peace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 20:24:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/n-koreas-tired-mountain-may-be-the-real-reason-kim-jong-un-is-ready-for-peace/</guid>
      <description>National news is filled with stories about how North Korean despot Kim Jong Un has announced that his nation will no longer conduct nuclear tests and will be shutting down its primary site at the 7,200 foot-high Mount Mantap. World political leaders are applauding the news and are portraying Kim as making a bold and decisive step towards peace. Is the gesture by Kim, however, based on a genuine interest in lofty goals of peace or is it based on a more grounded development?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experts at University of Texas Launch Controversial Program Aimed at Men</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/experts-at-university-of-texas-launch-controversial-program-aimed-at-men/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 17:24:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/experts-at-university-of-texas-launch-controversial-program-aimed-at-men/</guid>
      <description>Turn on any TV show or watch any commercial and what you will most likely see are scenes with characters consisting of strong, smart women and dopey and weak men. Those of you with children in high school or college have most likely heard of Academia’s crusade against ‘toxic masculinity’.

Now, one Texas university is attempting to slap a medical motivation behind dangerous masculinity, reports PJ Media.

Tyranny of the Technocrats At the University of Texas at Austin, the Counseling and Mental Health Center has initiated a campaign to tell men that their traits of masculinity are barriers to a balanced mental health.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Yellowstone About to Blow? Recent Geyser Eruptions Have Some People Worried</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/is-yellowstone-about-to-blow-recent-geyser-eruptions-have-some-people-worried/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 15:58:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/is-yellowstone-about-to-blow-recent-geyser-eruptions-have-some-people-worried/</guid>
      <description>Things have been heating up in Yellowstone Park lately, geologically speaking, and scientists have been scratching their heads trying to figure out why. The flurry of activity revolves around the Steamboat Geyser which has erupted 3 times in recent weeks.

The infamous geyser spouted on March 15, April 19, and again on Friday April 27. Steamboat is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest geyser and sits at the crown of the Yellowstone caldera volcanic crater.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia’s ‘Floating Chernobyl’ Alarms Officials</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/russias-floating-chernobyl-alarms-officials/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 15:41:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/russias-floating-chernobyl-alarms-officials/</guid>
      <description>The nuclear age has taken to the high seas. This statement has nothing to do with nuclear-powered submarines, aircraft carriers or ice-breaking naval vessels. The ground-breaking, or rather ground-leaving, event involves nuclear reactors perched atop floating barges and hauled out to sea.

‘Nuclear Titanic’ On April 28, a Russian planned and constructed nuclear facility was successfully tugged from its berthing area in the historic naval port of St. Petersburg to Murmansk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Research Claims to Solve JFK Assassination Theories, But Does It?</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/new-research-claims-to-solve-jfk-assassination-theories-but-does-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 17:56:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/new-research-claims-to-solve-jfk-assassination-theories-but-does-it/</guid>
      <description>The assassination of President John F. Kennedy took place over 50 years ago in Dallas, Texas, yet conspiracy theories still abound as to what happened on that fateful November day. Now, thanks to advancements in technology and the ability to digitally analyze audio and video footage of the shooting and its aftermath, one research firm thinks they&amp;rsquo;ve solved a major part of the puzzle.

From IFLScience.com According to official reports, Lee Harvey Oswald was the prime (and only) suspect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Could You Follow This Flapper Diet From 100 Years Ago?</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/could-you-follow-this-flapper-diet-from-100-years-ago/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 20:31:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/could-you-follow-this-flapper-diet-from-100-years-ago/</guid>
      <description>In the second decade of the 20th Century, American society was steeped in the opulence and hedonism of the ‘Roaring 20s’. The Great War was over and economic progress had returned big time to the United States. The zeitgeist was the closest Americans came to the French joie de vivre.

According to some sociologists, the generation during that time (the Crisis stage) was the artist group. The 1920s gave birth to bohemians and flappers, so it would indeed appear that the authors were right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flying Drone Taxi Lifts Off in Oregon - Are You Ready?</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/flying-drone-taxi-lifts-off-in-oregon-are-you-ready/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 19:52:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/flying-drone-taxi-lifts-off-in-oregon-are-you-ready/</guid>
      <description>All throughout the 20th century, one of the signature features of the future that Americans looked forward to was the possibility of flying cars. Getting in your car and, just like George Jetson, blasting off to work and then home again. Well, it looks like the future is not that far off.

The world may be on the cusp of the skies being filled with flying taxis. The European company, Airbus, who produces civilian and military aircraft, has released video of tests of its ‘Vahana’ vertical takeoff and landing (VTOL) drone taxi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Texas Scientist Solves Two Ansel Adams Mysteries</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/texas-scientist-solves-two-ansel-adams-mysteries/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 17:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/texas-scientist-solves-two-ansel-adams-mysteries/</guid>
      <description>Donald Olson is an amateur sleuth, but the mysteries he solves don&amp;rsquo;t put killers behind bars or reveal the identities of murderers in some sort of overly dramatic third act. No, Olson tackles the mysteries that artists and great figures in history have left for the rest of us to figure out.

The Art Detective From Atlas Obscura: An astrophysicist and forensic astronomer, Olson uses quantitative methods to answer questions raised by artwork, literature, and historical accounts—not the heady ones, but the basic, surprisingly slippery who, what, when, and where.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yes, There Used to Be Giant Sloths and Humans Used to Hunt Them</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/yes-there-used-to-be-giant-sloths-and-humans-used-to-hunt-them/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 20:37:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/yes-there-used-to-be-giant-sloths-and-humans-used-to-hunt-them/</guid>
      <description>Today, people tend to think of sloths as cute harmless creatures. Their images are all over the internet and videos of them on YouTube garner thousands &amp;ndash; and even millions of views. Their prehistoric ancestors, however, were a little different.

Over 10,000 years ago in what is now the New Mexico White Sands National Monument at least one pre-historic hunter followed the trail of a large beast. At some point, the hunter caught up to the animal causing the beast to rear up on its hind legs in an attempt to scare away the hunter or, if that failed, defend itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archaeologists in Peru Make Gruesome Discovery</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/archaeologists-in-peru/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 16:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/archaeologists-in-peru/</guid>
      <description>In the waning days of its civilization, a gathering of Chimú priests oversaw a religious ritual they hoped would stem the endless days of rain and the rising sea levels that threatened their 15th Century society located along the Pacific Ocean in modern day Peru.

Prior rituals involving the sacrifice of adults in order to appease the gods had failed. Desperate times called for desperate measures. An Unexpected Recourse For five years an interdisciplinary team, funded by National Geographic, headed up by Gabriel Prieto of the Universidad Nacional de Trujillo and John Verano of Tulane University have been slowly peeling back the layers of a mass grave located in the Chimú town of Huanchaquito-Las Llamas, but now known as the Peruvian district of Huanchaco.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Re-Examined Museum Piece Discovered to Be Older Than the Pyramids</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/re-examined-museum-piece-discovered-to-be-older-than-the-pyramids/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 15:29:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/re-examined-museum-piece-discovered-to-be-older-than-the-pyramids/</guid>
      <description>The Pleistocene Epoch is the term scientists use to describe the last ice age that ended about 11,700 years ago. It was at about this time, almost 12,000 years ago that a group of people in Siberia (the land where the ice age never really ended), carved a tree into a human like wooden idol almost 5 meters long.

Fast forward to 1894, when gold prospectors discovered the idol while digging up a peat bog near the Russian city Yekaterinburg.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japanese Farmers Turn to Wolf-Like Creature for Protection</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/japanese-farmers-turn-to-wolf-like-creature-for-protection/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 20:51:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/japanese-farmers-turn-to-wolf-like-creature-for-protection/</guid>
      <description>It looks and sounds like something out of a sci-fi horror flick. With eyes that glow a menacing red, white fangs and inhuman howls, a new creature is stalking the rice paddies and agricultural fields of Japan.

It is called the Super Monster Wolf and stands 20 inches tall and is around 25 ½ inches long. Oh and it costs about $4,800 to buy. The creature is a solar powered robot wolf designed to scare away scavengers and other animals from farms and rice paddies throughout Japan, writes The Sun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robot Solves Popular Puzzle in Less than a Second [Video]</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/robot-solves-popular-puzzle-in-less-than-a-second-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 20:08:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/robot-solves-popular-puzzle-in-less-than-a-second-video/</guid>
      <description>Remember the Rubik’s Cube? Those old enough to can probably appreciate this author’s level of frustration with the 3D puzzle. My frustration got to the point that I even peeled off (poorly) the stickers on the segments so I could pretend I successfully finished it.

Not my proudest moment. I was certainly nowhere close to current Guinness World Records holder Patrick Ponce from the USA, who completed a 3x3x3 cube in just 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York &amp; The Great Thunder Snow Blizzard of 2018</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/new-york-the-great-thunder-snow-blizzard-of-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 19:54:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/new-york-the-great-thunder-snow-blizzard-of-2018/</guid>
      <description>The Northeast has definitely experienced some intense weather this spring and a few weeks ago, a massive storm grew miles above the Big Apple. The energy it created gave birth to thunder storms during a major snow event.

On March 7, first New York City and then northern New Jersey, experienced thunder snow during a strong coastal front. In the process billions of ice crystals high up in the atmosphere moving at a frenetic pace due to the winds of the storm, began charging each other with electrical energy This rapid movement charges an area of the atmosphere, which in turn draws more ice crystals to it like a magnet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s Why California Residents Might Want to Start Buying Bottled Water</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/heres-why-california-residents-might-want-to-start-buying-bottled-water/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 18:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/heres-why-california-residents-might-want-to-start-buying-bottled-water/</guid>
      <description>Day-by-day, California is getting closer to running out of drinking water. In the wealthiest nation on Earth, it is inconceivable that this should be happening.
Now the Dems of Cali have to drink sewage because they are totally incompetent. California to add recycled sewer water to the state reservoirs https://t.co/SNWTVx3jFA #FoxNews
&amp;mdash; Martin a Patriot (@pfiec) March 8, 2018  Adversity being the mother of invention, the SFGate reports that San Diego is hoping its’ experiment in recycled water will trickle throughout the Golden State.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Known Story of the Deaf Men Who Helped NASA Get Into Space</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/little-known-story-of-the-deaf-men-who-helped-nasa-get-into-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 17:25:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/little-known-story-of-the-deaf-men-who-helped-nasa-get-into-space/</guid>
      <description>The story of the American space program and the organized effort it took to launch astronauts into space and, eventually, onto the moon is a remarkable tale of people from all walks of life coming together to achieve a great mission.

The contribution of several remarkable women was portrayed in the recent hit movie Hidden Figures, and now Discover Magazine has the account of a group of men who, up until now, have been unheard of in the tale of the exploration of space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marine Biologists CT Scan an Entire Whale - Here&#39;s What They Found</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/marine-biologists-ct-scan-an-entire-whale-heres-what-they-found/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 16:51:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/marine-biologists-ct-scan-an-entire-whale-heres-what-they-found/</guid>
      <description>In a bid to help biologists better understand the aquatic environs of whales and how humans impact them, researchers from San Diego State University (SDSU) have completed a crucial examination of one ocean species.

Discover Magazine writes that the results “will help researchers better protect these massive mammals of the sea.” Can You Hear Me Now? Thanks to a large computed tomography (CT) machine used to scan solid-fuel rocket engines, SDSU scientists were able to analyze the interior of a deceased 11-foot young minke whale found beached years before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What the Heck Just Happened at Yellowstone?</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/yellowstone-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 15:33:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/yellowstone-video/</guid>
      <description>Things got a bit bizarre on the evening of April 21 at one of the thermal vents belonging to the increasingly active Yellowstone caldera. A video of the incidents has been posted to YouTube but result in more questions than answers.
Has Yellowstone volcano STARTED erupting? Shock claims as ‘explosion’ spotted on live feed https://t.co/VXIxDwl9dq pic.twitter.com/LRQQzr0TDf
&amp;mdash; encyclopedic (@encyclopedicuk) April 25, 2018  It Starts With a Body… In the video posted by YouTuber Kat Martin, the vent can be seen in the dark of night, spewing steam and heat into the cold Wyoming air.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shadow Security System for Seniors - More Effective Than Guard Dogs?</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/shadow-security-system-for-seniors-more-effective-than-guard-dogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 14:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/shadow-security-system-for-seniors-more-effective-than-guard-dogs/</guid>
      <description>In this day and age of escalating crime, it is understandable that people living alone, especially women, feel a bit unsecure. Those suffering from this condition can and usually get a dog or alarm system, but what about those who live in pet-free apartments or townhouses?

A solution may be in the offering from Leopalace21 Corp, a Japanese firm that designed a program to ward off possible trespassers or thieves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NASA Probe&#39;s Up Close Pictures of Jupiter</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/nasa-probes-up-close-pictures-of-jupiter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 21:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/nasa-probes-up-close-pictures-of-jupiter/</guid>
      <description>The images are breathtaking. It is as if a painter with tremendous creativity and a sense for wonderous patterns had composed them.
You&amp;#39;ve just crossed over into the Twilight Zone. This image captures the swirling cloud formations in #Jupiter’s terminator – the region where day meets night. https://t.co/BrHKWPVjtS pic.twitter.com/En9mwkcEz7
&amp;mdash; NASA&amp;#39;s Juno Mission (@NASAJuno) March 1, 2018  NASA’s Juno craft has recently taken some updated pictures of Jupiter’s interior and the results are extraordinary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Power of Breathing to Calm Your Brain</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-power-of-breathing-to-calm-your-brain/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 18:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-power-of-breathing-to-calm-your-brain/</guid>
      <description>For years, humans have relied on breathing as a way to achieve peace of mind. As you know, one of the most basic and effective forms of meditation is to become aware of your breath and follow it, in and out of your body.

Well, it looks like science is confirming all of religion&amp;rsquo;s teachings on the positive effects of breathing. A recent article in Psychology Today talks about a 2016 conducted by neuroscientists from Stanford, UCLA, and St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bezos&#39; Latest Brainstorm: A Walking, Talking Alexa in Every Home</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/bezos-latest-brainstorm-a-walking-talking-alexa-in-every-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 18:46:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/bezos-latest-brainstorm-a-walking-talking-alexa-in-every-home/</guid>
      <description>Like it or not, artificial intelligence is advancing at a phenomenal rate. While some people fear the Pandora&amp;rsquo;s Box that AI will open up and others are, at the very least, leery of the rise of the machine, some people are optimistic and welcoming of the new technology. Jeff Bezos is hoping you fall into the third category.

Here&amp;rsquo;s the story from Bloomberg: The retail and cloud computing giant has embarked on an ambitious, top-secret plan to build a domestic robot, according to people familiar with the plans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Reach Conclusions After 80 Year Long Happiness Study</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientists-reach-conclusions-after-80-year-long-happiness-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 18:41:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientists-reach-conclusions-after-80-year-long-happiness-study/</guid>
      <description>A multi-generational group of researchers have published the results of an 80-year-long study tracking the lives nearly 2,000 Americans. The study looked to answer an eternal question that has had philosophers, theologians and scientists consumed with curiosity: what is the secret to happiness?

Happy Man[/caption] The Company You Keep IFLScience writes that the study was handled by “a team of scientists at Harvard University” that discovered, thanks to evolving medical research and technology, the key to happiness was the development and maintenance of strong relationships with other people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geologist Run Earthquake Simulation in San Francisco, Here are the Results</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/geologist-run-earthquake-simulation-in-san-francisco-here-are-the-results/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 18:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/geologist-run-earthquake-simulation-in-san-francisco-here-are-the-results/</guid>
      <description>California is used to earthquakes. There are small to medium tremors that occur monthly throughout the year. The last major quake to strike California was the shallow 6.9 Loma Prieta earthquake in 1989, often referred to as the ‘World Series Quake’ since it struck during a MLB playoff game. The quake killed 67 people, injured 3,000 and cost $5 billion in damages.
  Before that, in 1906, a vicious 7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Court Hands Down Verdict in &#39;Monkey See, Monkey Selfie&#39; Case</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/court-hands-down-verdict-in-monkey-see-monkey-selfie-case/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 18:03:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/court-hands-down-verdict-in-monkey-see-monkey-selfie-case/</guid>
      <description>It’s not the equivalent of the Scope Monkey Trial of 1925, but another legal case with a primate at the center of it has found its way into American culture. Unlike the Scopes trial, which addressed the weighty subject of biological evolution, this case is a comical farce of a lawsuit over photo selfies.

‘Monkey See Monkey Sue’ The U.S. 9th Circuit Court of Appeals has recently ruled on a 2011 lawsuit filed by the People for the Ethical Treatment of Animals (PETA) over photographs inadvertently taken of an Indonesian crested macaque, named Naruto, by British nature photographer David Slater, reports the Huffington Post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archaeologists Find Rare Roman Statue... in Egypt</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/archaeologists-find-rare-roman-statue-in-egypt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 22:26:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/archaeologists-find-rare-roman-statue-in-egypt/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re an archaeologist, Egypt has got to be the place to go! Not only are they finding Eqyptian artifacts over there, but now they&amp;rsquo;re finding Roman ones, too! From Newsweek:

Archaeologists in Egypt have unearthed the bust of Roman Emperor Marcus Aurelius, who was best known for his philosophical interests. They made the discovery in the Temple of Kom Ombo, where a years-long project is being done to preserve the site from groundwater damage, The Associated Press reports.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tyson Prediction: First Trillionaire Will Make Money in Outer Space</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/tyson-prediction-first-trillionaire-will-make-money-in-outer-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 21:20:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/tyson-prediction-first-trillionaire-will-make-money-in-outer-space/</guid>
      <description>When you think of the wealthy these days, you think of billionaires like Bill Gates, Elon Musk, Warren Buffet, Mark Zuckerberg, Oprah, and Jeff Bezos. While all of these are busy stirring up their fortunes on terra firma, famed astrophysicist Neil deGrasse Tyson believe that space will produce the first trillionaire.

From the Daily Star: “The first trillionaire there will ever be is the person who exploits the natural resources on asteroids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Real Life &#39;Lassie&#39; Leads Rescuers to Little Girl Lost in Wilderness</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/real-life-lassie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 19:03:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/real-life-lassie/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to the incredibly heroic actions of a physically impaired dog an Australian family has their three-year-old daughter back safe and sound, reports Fox News. The backstory is a heart-warming story of survival and loyalty.

Every Parents Worst Nightmare On a cool and rainy April 20 day in Queensland, Australia the Bennett family was enjoying the beginning of the weekend when Leisa Bennett noticed that her three-year-old granddaughter, Aurora, had could not be found in the house and in the immediate vicinity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yukon Saloon Serves Up Stomach Churning Cocktail to Guests</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/yukon-saloon-serves-up-stomach-churning-cocktail-to-guests/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 17:50:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/yukon-saloon-serves-up-stomach-churning-cocktail-to-guests/</guid>
      <description>If you are ever in the Canadian Yukon&amp;rsquo;s Dawson City, stop by the Sourdough Saloon for some food and drinks and be sure to experience a peculiar cocktail called the &amp;lsquo;Sourtoe&amp;rsquo;. Nick Griffiths would appreciate the visit.

The Drink Has (Frost)bite Griffiths, a frequent contender in extreme racings, participated this last winter in the Yukon Arctic Ultra. The race is a punishing 300-mile jaunt via foot, dogsled and mountain bikes through inhospitable freezing landscapes, with temperatures getting down to 58 degrees Fahrenheit below zero, making it one of the coldest races in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Man Gets Attacked by Rattlesnake, Bear, &amp; Tiger Shark - And Lives to Tell About It</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/man-gets-attacked-by-rattlesnake-bear-tiger-shark-and-lives-to-tell-about-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 17:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/man-gets-attacked-by-rattlesnake-bear-tiger-shark-and-lives-to-tell-about-it/</guid>
      <description>Beauty is in the eye of the beholder and the same may be said of luck. A twenty-year-old Colorado native named Dylan McWilliams may either be the most unlucky or luckiest man, reports Sky News.

On April 19, while enjoying a two week vacation to Hawaii, McWilliams was on his surfboard in the early morning waters of Shipwreck&amp;rsquo;s Beach, 50 yards off of Poipu. The avid surfer and survival instructor was enjoying a beautiful morning when he suddenly felt something clamp down on one of his submerged legs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Authorities Still Unable to ID Strange Craft in Skies Over Chile</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/authorities-still-unable-to-id-strange-craft-in-skies-over-chile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 16:21:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/authorities-still-unable-to-id-strange-craft-in-skies-over-chile/</guid>
      <description>After two years of trying to determine what it was that was drifting above the clouds off the coast of Chile on November 11 of 2014, that nation&amp;rsquo;s version of our Federal Aviation Administration (FAA), the CEFAA, has recently released nearly ten minutes of footage of an apparent UFO that has left Chilean officials at a loss to explain, reports Huffington Post.

On the date mentioned above, two Chilean naval aviators flying an Airbus Cougar AS-532 helicopter on a routine daytime patrol, spotted what they later described as a white, semi-oval shaped &amp;ldquo;flat, elongated structure that had two thermal spotlights like discharges that did not coincide with the axel of motion&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NASA Just Took a Giant Leap Forward in It&#39;s Mission to Find Habitable Planets</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/nasa-just-took-a-giant-leap-forward-in-its-mission-to-find-habitable-planets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 19:41:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/nasa-just-took-a-giant-leap-forward-in-its-mission-to-find-habitable-planets/</guid>
      <description>Last week a Space X Falcon 9 Rocket took off from Cape Canaveral Air Station in Florida and launched a very special satellite named TESS into Earth&amp;rsquo;s orbit. TESS stands for Transiting Exoplanet Surevey Satellite and its mission is to discover new planets. NASA is very excited about the possibilities.

From Space.com: &amp;ldquo;TESS is going to dramatically increase the number of planets that we have to study,&amp;rdquo; TESS principal investigator George Ricker, of the Massachusetts Institute of Technology, said during a pre-launch briefing Sunday (April 15).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guests at &#39;The Shining&#39; Hotel Accidentally Take Picture of Ghost</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/guests-at-the-shining-hotel-accidentally-take-picture-of-ghost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 17:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/guests-at-the-shining-hotel-accidentally-take-picture-of-ghost/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been almost 40 years since Stanley Kubrick&amp;rsquo;s horror masterpiece The Shining hit the silver screens of America. The movie, starring Jack Nicholson, is based on a 1977 Stephen King novel of the same name and was tremendous hit for Nicholson, Kubrick, and King when it hit theaters in the summer of 1980.

Stanley Kubrick[/caption] Many people know that much, but what you may not know is that King wrote his novel based on a paranormal experience he had while staying at The Staley Hotel in Estes Park, CO in 1974.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Journalist Accidentally Given Files to Secret Government Project</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/journalist-accidentally-given-files-to-secret-government-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 21:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/journalist-accidentally-given-files-to-secret-government-project/</guid>
      <description>A people should never fear their government, for that is tyranny. The opposite, the government fearing the people, is the guarantor of freedom. Unfortunately, we suffer under the ‘aegis’ of a meddling centralized government masquerading as a benevolent patriarch. Agencies like the CIA, the Department of Homeland Security, the FBI and the National Security Agency to name a few, operate in the shadows of unconstitutionality and violations of human rights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biblical Numerologist Predicts End of the World for Monday</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/biblical-numerologist-predicts-end-of-the-world-for-monday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 20:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/biblical-numerologist-predicts-end-of-the-world-for-monday/</guid>
      <description>It seems like we have these predictions at least a couple of times a year. Some predictions usually occur in the fall, around the Jewish New Year. Enjoy your weekend, folks because according to some Christian eschatologists and numerologists, Monday April 23 will be the end of the world, reports the UK’s Express. Those prophesizing the imminent end are divided into two camps; those that believe our termination will come at the arrival of a mysterious alien planet referred to as ‘Planet X’ or Nibiru and the other camp that says our end will come as Jesus Christ arrives for the Second Coming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk Might Have Some Explaining to Do</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/elon-musk-might-have-some-explaining-to-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 20:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/elon-musk-might-have-some-explaining-to-do/</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk is a visionary. His Tesla brand has been the hottest thing in the automotive industry, and we&amp;rsquo;re just a few months removed from him launching a convertible into space with two Falcon rocket boosters that returned to Earth and landed themselves.

As a forward thinker and futurist, he&amp;rsquo;s planning a mission to Mars and warning Americans about the dangers of the advent of artificial intelligence. After viewing this next report, however, it seems someone should be warning Mr Musk about the problems in his own company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Submarine Discovery Solves Decades Old WW2 Mystery</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/submarine-discovery-solves-decades-old-ww2-mystery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 20:09:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/submarine-discovery-solves-decades-old-ww2-mystery/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s no secret that as World War II was winding down and Germany&amp;rsquo;s defeat became imminent that many Nazis fled to South America where they established new lives for themselves in countries such as Argentina and Brazil. Most notably among these were Adolf Eichmann and Josef Mengele.

Well, earlier this week off the coast of Denmark, researchers discovered the wreckage of a German submarine that was long rumored to have played a pivotal role in carrying the Nazis to South America.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Law in India Approves Death Penalty for Child Rapists</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/new-law-in-india-approves-death-penalty-for-child-rapists/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 17:56:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/new-law-in-india-approves-death-penalty-for-child-rapists/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to combatting the rise in crimes of sexual violence against children, the nation of India is done fooling around. Prime Minister Narendra Modi officially approved an ordinance which allows the death penalty to be handed down to anyone caught raping a child under the age of 12.

Even though the ordinance will require parliamentary approval within the next six months for it to become a law, child rapists can be prosecuted under this ordinance in the mean time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Finally Explain Curious Circles in Arctic Ice</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientists-finally-explain-curious-circles-in-arctic-ice/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 16:23:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientists-finally-explain-curious-circles-in-arctic-ice/</guid>
      <description>Each year for the past 10 years NASA has conducted airborne missions over both of Earth&amp;rsquo;s polar regions to map land and sea ice. On April 14, as part of this year&amp;rsquo;s mission, scientist John Sonntag noticed something he&amp;rsquo;d never seen before. There were random circles poking through the ice exposing the ocean water below.

So, as they flew about 50 miles northwest of Canada&amp;rsquo;s Mackenzie River Delta, Sonntag snapped a picture of the strange circles from the window of the plane.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Promotional Robot Freaks Out Pub Patrons with One Creepy Question</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/promotional-robot-freaks-out-pub-patrons-with-one-creepy-question/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 20:17:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/promotional-robot-freaks-out-pub-patrons-with-one-creepy-question/</guid>
      <description>Patrons of a London neighborhood pub got more than a pint of ale and cucumber sandwiches during their visit. Daily Mail reports that Engineered Arts, a company based in Penryn, Cornwall, created and embedded an artificial intelligence-based robot inside The Prince Alfred pub as part of a marketing campaign for HBO’s dystopic ‘Westworld’.

An Eerie Doppelgänger The robot, nicknamed Fred, was modeled after English actor Tedroy Newell and was seated in a booth with a pint in hand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LA Woman Comes Home From Work to Find Intruder in Bathroom Doing THIS</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/la-woman-comes-home-from-work-to-find-intruder-in-bathroom-doing-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 19:36:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/la-woman-comes-home-from-work-to-find-intruder-in-bathroom-doing-this/</guid>
      <description>Picture this scenario: You had a long day at work and cannot wait to get home, change into something more comfortable, put your feet up and finally relax. For one Monroe, Louisiana resident such a wish did not end as expected.

In the late afternoon of April 17, an unidentified woman entered her home, weary from hours at her job, to find someone had already gone into her house and was still there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Implant Human Brain Cells into Mice - You Won&#39;t Believe What Happened Next</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientists-implant-human-brain-cells-into-mice/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 18:55:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/scientists-implant-human-brain-cells-into-mice/</guid>
      <description>‘Of Mice and Men’ has a new interpretation now thanks to a group of scientists in California and if this interpretation is successful, debilitating mental disorders may be a thing of the past in years to come.

A group of researchers at Salk Institute in La Jolla, San Diego, California have succeeded in implanting human brain stem cells into the brains of mice and the results have been startling, reports the UK’s Express.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why This NFL Superstar&#39;s Secret Life Attracted The FBI&#39;s Attention</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/why-this-nfl-superstars-secret-life-attracted-fbi-spm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2018 03:34:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/why-this-nfl-superstars-secret-life-attracted-fbi-spm/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever worked so hard in your life that you wanted to let loose and have a bit of dangerous fun? Most of us have and it was no different for this football superstar. He thrived on competition, the thrill and excitement, that it brings to the table when he knocks someone out to run across the field and get that touchdown. The thrill has driven him to be the superstar that he is today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Man Emerges As Vietnam War Soldier Missing For 40 Years</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/man-emerges-as-vietnam-war-soldier-missing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 17:46:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/man-emerges-as-vietnam-war-soldier-missing/</guid>
      <description>The Vietnam war came to an end in 1975, leaving countless men lost or presumed dead. One soldier, Army Sgt. 1st Class John Hartley Robinson, was assumed to be one of the men who became a prisoner of war of the Vietcong or to have lost his life in battle. Then, nearly 40 years later, a man turned up claiming to be Army Sgt. 1st Class Robinson. He told stories of living a life in secret in the Vietnamese jungle after the war ended until he was found in 2008.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When 3 Conservatives Stop Into This Liberal Restaurant For Lunch, The Waitress Is In For A Big Surprise</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/when-3-conservatives-stop-into-this-liberal-restaurant-for-lunch-the-waitress-is-in-for-a-big-surprise/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 17:43:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/when-3-conservatives-stop-into-this-liberal-restaurant-for-lunch-the-waitress-is-in-for-a-big-surprise/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve all heard the old adage &amp;ldquo;never judge a book by its cover,&amp;rdquo; but the truth is we&amp;rsquo;re constantly making judgments about people and things around us. Most of the time it&amp;rsquo;s without even realizing it, just an automatic thing. You see someone wearing certain clothes or who looks a certain way and assume you know something about them. Rosalynd Harris thought she knew all about the three men who were seated in her section of the restaurant that afternoon just by the hats they were wearing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Amazingly Perfectly Timed Photos</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/perfectly-time-photo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 18:27:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/perfectly-time-photo/</guid>
      <description>twitter
You might be the best photographer there is out there but sometimes, you don’t have to be the best to take a perfect photo. You just need to be at the right place in the right moment. It will not matter if you take it with a phone or a very good camera; you just need to be passionate about what you do. Most of the time, you won’t even notice you took an awesome photo till you sit down to look at them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>15 Marvel Actresses Who Sizzle On And Off The Screen</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/15-marvel-actresses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 06:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/15-marvel-actresses/</guid>
      <description>All too often, the men of the Marvel universe take center stage. It makes sense on the surface of things, given that most superheroes are men. In the past few decades, however, our superheroine sisters have all been busy making names for themselves and changing the landscape of comic-inspired cinema. The Marvel-verse couldn&amp;rsquo;t survive without the women behind it, and those heroines wouldn&amp;rsquo;t exist without the indomitable actors who brought them to life on the big screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 GIFs That Show Live News Reporting Isn&#39;t Always A Great Idea</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/live-news-reporting-isnt-always-a-great-idea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 06:54:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/live-news-reporting-isnt-always-a-great-idea/</guid>
      <description>Piximus TV reporters live glamorous lives and we&amp;rsquo;ve all envied them, just a little, when we&amp;rsquo;ve seen them reporting from a star-studded event and enjoying the limelight. What many of us haven&amp;rsquo;t considered is that live-reporting his its dark side too. Live means that you can&amp;rsquo;t redo a take or reshoot a scene. If things go wrong, the whole world is going to know it. That&amp;rsquo;s what happens in these 20 hilarious live TV moments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Amazing Historical Photos That Show Exactly How Our Culture Has Evolved</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-amazing-historical-photos-that-show-exactly-how-our-culture-has-evolved/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 22:20:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-amazing-historical-photos-that-show-exactly-how-our-culture-has-evolved/</guid>
      <description>They say that the past can teach us many lessons, but the truth is that many of us never paid that much attention in history classes at school. That&amp;rsquo;s because history in school is always so boring. Who wants to be bored all the time? Not us. So, we don&amp;rsquo;t remember much from back then. That&amp;rsquo;s why we&amp;rsquo;ve delved into the archives to bring you 20 images from the past with real stories to tell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>15 Hottest Female Soccer Players On The Planet</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/15-hottest-female-soccer-players-on-the-planet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 10:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/15-hottest-female-soccer-players-on-the-planet/</guid>
      <description>Once seen as a male-dominated sport, female soccer players all over the globe are dominating both on and off the field. From their killer looks to their outrageous athletic ability, here are 15 of the most gorgeous and impressive women in soccer. Read on to see if your favorite made the list.
England&amp;rsquo;s Toni Duggan Twitter Toni Duggan celebrated her 18 birthday by scoring the opening goal in England&amp;rsquo;s 2009 UEFA Women&amp;rsquo;s Under-19 Championship final win against Sweden in Belarus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>15 Of The Sexiest Women In American Sports</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/15-of-the-sexiest-women-in-american-sports/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 09:28:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/15-of-the-sexiest-women-in-american-sports/</guid>
      <description>With the 2018 Winter Olympics coming to a close, I&amp;rsquo;m sure many of us are left wondering how so many of our highest-achieving athletes can also be graced with such good looks. We haven&amp;rsquo;t yet come up with the formula for Olympian success, but we did come up with a list of the 15 hottest female American athletes for you to swoon over.
Allison Stokke Cleverst Track and field athlete Allison Stokke got her start during school, breaking a number of American records for high school pole vaulting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ready For Takeoff! These Airport Fails Are Almost Too Funny To Handle</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/ready-for-takeoff-these-airport-fails-are-almost-too-funny-to-handle/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 19:27:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/ready-for-takeoff-these-airport-fails-are-almost-too-funny-to-handle/</guid>
      <description>youtube Travelling is on many of our bucket lists. Whether you want to travel the globe or go cross-country, jumping on a plane is a convenient and relatively fast way to get anywhere you want to go. Navigating an airport may seem like a hike in itself. There are endless terminals and countless security measures — but even more astounding are the different people you get to see. The hectic, busy atmosphere of most airports sometimes has travelers acting rather silly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insane Pictures Of The Most Flexible Girls In The World</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/insane-pictures-of-the-most-flexible-girls-in-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 04:24:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/insane-pictures-of-the-most-flexible-girls-in-the-world/</guid>
      <description>Although the human body is incredibly resilient in terms of what it can endure, most people aren&amp;rsquo;t very flexible. Mastering the art of contortion takes a lot of training and good, rubbery genes. Many factors are taken into account when establishing personal flexibility: joint structure, ligaments, tendons, muscles, skin, tissue injury, fat (or adipose) tissue, body temperature, activity level, age and sex all influence an individual&amp;rsquo;s range of motion about a joint.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazing, Perfectly-Timed Cheerleader Fails That Will Make You Cringe, Then Laugh</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/amazing-perfectly-timed-cheerleader-fails-that-will-make-you-cringe-then-laugh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 20:28:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/amazing-perfectly-timed-cheerleader-fails-that-will-make-you-cringe-then-laugh/</guid>
      <description>Cheerleading began as a way to motivate sports teams during gameplay with positive team spirit. As time has gone on, it&amp;rsquo;s really evolved into a sport of its own. Cheer competitions are now held all around the world and feature groups of incredibly talented athletes. For a sport so focused on gymnastics and routines, there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of work that goes into making the perfect cheer. Luckily for us, that means there&amp;rsquo;s plenty of footage and photographs of what happens when something goes wrong!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just Some Pics Of Girls Wearing Yoga Pants To Help Brighten Your Day</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/just-some-pics-of-girls-wearing-yoga-pants-to-help-brighten-your-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 19:44:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/just-some-pics-of-girls-wearing-yoga-pants-to-help-brighten-your-day/</guid>
      <description>pantso When you think of art, you probably don&amp;rsquo;t immediately think about the female body, even though it&amp;rsquo;s what 90% of art throughout history is based on. Sometimes the natural beauty of the everyday real world is right in front of you, possibly in downward-facing dog position. Though we&amp;rsquo;re not the type to mess with perfection, adding a pair of yoga pants to a beautiful body is an undeniable improvement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Legendary Presidents Ranked Dumbest To Smartest</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-legendary-presidents-ranked-dumbest-to-smartest/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 21:25:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-legendary-presidents-ranked-dumbest-to-smartest/</guid>
      <description>C|Net It&amp;rsquo;s no secret that in order to be elected president, you have to have some unique qualities. Sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s bravery. Sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s charm. Many would argue that sometimes, it&amp;rsquo;s just the ability to attract a wealthy and generous donor base. No matter what the specific appeal may be, it is true that no average person can coast to the Oval Office without having to work for it. When it comes to running the most powerful nation in the world, the standards are high and the stakes are higher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>These Celebrities Fought Hard Against Drugs And Addiction, But Eventually Lost Everything</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/these-celebrities-fought-hard-against-drugs-and-addiction-but-eventually-lost-everything/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 18:47:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/these-celebrities-fought-hard-against-drugs-and-addiction-but-eventually-lost-everything/</guid>
      <description>NYDailyNews Our obsession with celebrities is a phenomenon as old as the moving picture. For some reason, a switch flips in our brains when we see someone on a screen that makes us want to know everything possible about that person and what they&amp;rsquo;re doing every single day. But the pressure of constantly being in the public eye can have an adverse effect on celebrities, most of whom are just regular people trying to live normal lives when they&amp;rsquo;re off-set.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oops! These Are The Most Awkward &#39;Walk Of Shame&#39; Photos We&#39;ve Ever Seen</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/oops-these-are-the-most-awkward-walk-of-shame-photos-weve-ever-seen/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 06:56:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/oops-these-are-the-most-awkward-walk-of-shame-photos-weve-ever-seen/</guid>
      <description>sickchirpse Everyone likes to party now and then to let off some steam and get crazy with friends. What you have to remember when you&amp;rsquo;re partying, however, is how you&amp;rsquo;re planning to get home the next day! Not everyone knows exactly where they&amp;rsquo;ll end up the night of a party, and the next day, they&amp;rsquo;re forced to do the Walk of Shame. From the heels they&amp;rsquo;re still wearing to the messy hair, you can tell these ladies got down with their bad selves last night, and who knows what kind of trouble they got into.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>These Politicians Are Popular, But Their Kids Are Absolute Nightmares</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/these-politicians-are-popular-but-their-kids-are-absolute-nightmares/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 01:55:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/these-politicians-are-popular-but-their-kids-are-absolute-nightmares/</guid>
      <description>dailymail We tend to hold those in political power to a higher standard than we do ourselves. We see them as the golden moral pillars of society; perfect humans who never so much as double park. Why? Great question. Politicians and the people that surround them are, in fact, normal humans. Hence, they are susceptible to the same struggles and moral failings as anyone, and that means that they can be pretty crappy parents sometimes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>These Perfectly-Timed Sports Photos Will Make Even Non-Sports Fans Literal LOL</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/these-perfectly-timed-sports-photos-will-make-even-non-sports-fans-literal-lol/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 01:44:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/these-perfectly-timed-sports-photos-will-make-even-non-sports-fans-literal-lol/</guid>
      <description>pinkfinishpicture You might think that sports are all about good timing in the first place, and that&amp;rsquo;s certainly true. You need that perfect opportunity to set up a field goal or find space to drop the ball in the basket. But that&amp;rsquo;s a different kind of timing than comedic timing, and we want to laugh today. These fantastic photos are moments that won&amp;rsquo;t ever happen again. They required a lucky photographer to be in the right place at the right time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>These Female Olympians Have Our Hearts Racing, And You&#39;re About To See Why</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/female-olympians/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 07:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/female-olympians/</guid>
      <description>With the 2018 Olympics upon us, you might find yourself flipping through photos of hot female athletes &amp;ndash; so, we&amp;rsquo;ve saved you some trouble. While all athletes are in shape (it&amp;rsquo;s kind of a requirement of the job) some of them are just downright sexy. For many of them, time off from training means there&amp;rsquo;s plenty of time to model, and plenty of these ladies do just that. You may recognize a number of these sexy athletes from their various ads and photoshoots in which they aren&amp;rsquo;t at all shy about showing off their incredible bodies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ridiculous People of Walmart</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-ridiculous-people-of-walmart/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 22:53:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-ridiculous-people-of-walmart/</guid>
      <description>LipstickAlley Who doesn&amp;rsquo;t love to shop at Walmart? This leading retail chain has everything that you need ranging from clothing, food, jewelry, electronics, and household items. With such a vast collection, the retail store attracts different types of people. In fact, the store may be America&amp;rsquo;s real retail convergence zone. However, everyone has a unique experience purchasing at the store. Some of the clients who shop at Walmart walk in with unique costumes and habits that no one else can match.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Most Insane Animal Attacks</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-most-insane-animal-attacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 20:25:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-most-insane-animal-attacks/</guid>
      <description>ThePinsta Animal attacks are a common cause of either human injuries or fatalities. In the U.S. alone, up to five million people are attacked by dogs and cats each year, with the frequency of animal attacks varying depending on geographical location. In the U.S., an individual is more likely to be killed by domesticated animals than they are to die from being hit by lighting. When agitated, hungry, or scared, animals go back to their true nature - the instinct to survive no matter the cause.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Celebrities You Had No Idea Are Atheist</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-celebrities-you-had-no-idea-are-atheist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 22:47:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-celebrities-you-had-no-idea-are-atheist/</guid>
      <description>qpolitical Hollywood stars mesmerize everyday people with their larger than life portrayals of historical and dramatic figures. Some celebrities convince us, when playing people like Ghandi, Moses or Jesus Christ, that they have a devoutly spiritual soul. That’s is certainly a testament to their great acting skills and abilities to create on-screen passion. But, at the end of the day, we generally do not know these stars of the silver screen personally.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Celebrities With Good For Nothing Kids</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-celebrities-with-good-for-nothing-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 20:48:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-celebrities-with-good-for-nothing-kids/</guid>
      <description>teriobrien Like the saying goes, the apple doesn’t fall far from the tree. This definitely holds true for children of famous celebrities. These tots often inherit their parents’ superstar good looks and talents. However, the work ethic and personal skills that helped launch their parents to the top of their fields is often completely lacking in the more privileged progeny. Hidden by the shade of their parent’s fame, their problems usually don’t catch the public eye until they’ve gone completely off the deep end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Amazingly Perfectly Timed Photos</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/timed-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 20:04:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/timed-photos/</guid>
      <description>twitter
You might be the best photographer there is out there but sometimes, you don’t have to be the best to take a perfect photo. You just need to be at the right place in the right moment. It will not matter if you take it with a phone or a very good camera; you just need to be passionate about what you do. Most of the time, you won’t even notice you took an awesome photo till you sit down to look at them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 20 Cutest Interspecies Friendships of All Time!</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-20-cutest-interspecies-friendships-of-all-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 20:22:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-20-cutest-interspecies-friendships-of-all-time/</guid>
      <description>While some friendships are as a result of the coming together of similar personalities, others are made up of the strangest of characters. This is the case when two animals from different species meet and form an unbreakable bond of friendship. The interspecies friendships are not only strong but also cute, a factor that makes them a source of inspiration even for humans. There have been several instances where animals of different species developed unbelievable bonds, with some interspecies friendships being termed as adoptions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Hilarious Photos of Bad Dogs</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-hilarious-photos-of-bad-dogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 19:34:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-hilarious-photos-of-bad-dogs/</guid>
      <description>Humans and dogs share a special bond – a symbiotic one for that matter. Our furry friends not only provide us companionship, but they&amp;rsquo;re also probably the most loyal pets we can own. However, that doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean that every day is cuddles, rocking, and joy.
Seenox It reaches a time when they get rebellious and engage in all manner trouble in the house. Sometimes we scold them. Other times we cannot help it but burst out laughing at their funny and stupid behavior.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Horribly Awkward Wedding Fails</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-horribly-awkward-wedding-fails/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 21:43:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-horribly-awkward-wedding-fails/</guid>
      <description>BridalHairArt Weddings are meant to be beautiful. When we think of two people committing to love each other for the rest of our lives, our minds conjure pictures of white doves and perfumed flowers. Motivated brides spend months and small fortunes to plan and execute the perfect experience. Sometimes, however, good planning just isn’t enough. No matter how carefully an event is prepared, the unexpected can still happen. But that doesn’t have to ruin the big day!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Celebs You Didn&#39;t Realize Were Transgender</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-celebs-you-didnt-realize-were-transgender/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 21:27:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-celebs-you-didnt-realize-were-transgender/</guid>
      <description>Transgender people are making themselves known more and more. Transgender people have always been courageous; however, many are now also becoming famous for what they are doing and how they are doing it. Younger people are no longer accepting arbitrarily-imposed definitions of gender identity or sexual orientation. In general, they are much more fluid about these things. They realize that these personal feelings are truly up to each individual. Diversity is amazing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Amazingly Perfectly Timed Photos</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-amazingly-perfectly-timed-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 06:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-amazingly-perfectly-timed-photos/</guid>
      <description>wnewslife
You might be the best photographer there is out there but sometimes, you don’t have to be the best to take a perfect photo. You just need to be at the right place in the right moment. It will not matter if you take it with a phone or a very good camera; you just need to be passionate about what you do. Most of the time, you won’t even notice you took an awesome photo till you sit down to look at them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful Wives of Celebrities: Then and Now</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/beautiful-wives-of-celebrities/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 19:41:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/beautiful-wives-of-celebrities/</guid>
      <description>“Behind every great man, there’s a great woman.” Celebrities are no exception. Throughout history, the public has followed the love lives of celebs, from dating to marriage to children. However, here are the wives, and ex-wives, you may not remember.
Robert Redford – Lola Van Wagenen Robert Redford and Lola Van Wagenen met, in 1957, and were secretly married, in Las Vegas, in 1958. However, they had a public ceremony a few months later, in Provo, Utah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Photos Donald Trump Doesn&#39;t Want You To See</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-photos-donald-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 00:22:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-photos-donald-trump/</guid>
      <description>Here are 20 photos Donald Trump would pay Shadow Brokers to take off the internet for good, especially the 8th one.
1. Dishonoring the national flag CNN Trump went vocal with his famous 144 characters to blast out NFL star Colin Kaepernick&amp;rsquo;s deliberate choice to sit out of the National Anthem. However, as this photo reveals, Trump also has little or no allegiance to pledge for the anthem. Did things change after he became the president?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secrets About The Trump Family You Didn&#39;t Know</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/secrets-about-the-trump-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 23:25:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/secrets-about-the-trump-family/</guid>
      <description>Donald Trump and his family have been in the limelight since he ascended to the presidency, and mostly for the wrong reasons. This list brings to light some of the secrets of this family from a seemingly incestuous father-daughter relationship through the facts of a neglected daughter, to a son who spent an entire year partying.
1. A descendant of immigrants WBDaily From his campaign manifestos, you would think Trump’s family has been in America for the past four generations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 20 Richest Politicians in the World</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-20-richest-politicians-in-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 22:36:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-20-richest-politicians-in-the-world/</guid>
      <description>Politicians rise and become famous but most of appear to be rich even before they are elected to serve in public offices. Political career thrives with stable financial backing. While they earn a big salary when they get into the public office, some are richer than others. Most of them are from wealthy families and others have made their investments. Here is a list of the 20 richest politicians in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Cancer Symptoms You Should Not Ignore!</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-cancer-symptoms-you-should-not-ignore/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 21:59:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-cancer-symptoms-you-should-not-ignore/</guid>
      <description>Cancer is a disease that comes with very few visible symptoms. It is always good to have it detected early before it spreads to others parts of the body. It is curable if diagnosed in its initial stages. There are cancer symptoms that you should not ignore, and that means you see need your doctor for immediate cancer screening. It will help you start treatment on time or even prevent the disease.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entire Family Gathers Around Dalmatian To Witness Something Spectacular... Keep You Eyes On The Dog</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/dalmatian-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 07:05:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/dalmatian-story/</guid>
      <description>One of the most treasured bonds you can experience is a relationship with your family dog. These furry friends become treasured members of your family. They live in your home, they travel with you and bring you joy (or frustration) each day. Many families take hundreds of photos and videos to post in their homes or share with the world. Video of one joyful Dalmatian is going viral after she stuck a special pose for her dad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Unapologetic Life Of Howard Stern</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-unapologetic-life-of-howard-stern/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2017 22:42:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-unapologetic-life-of-howard-stern/</guid>
      <description>Cloudfont Some claim that Howard Stern was chased out of terrestrial radio by the fists and screams of moralists. Others say that he left by his own steam, settling in at a quieter and better-paying gig on satellite radio, where the moralists could find no, even slightly absurd, argument to ban him. From whichever perspective you see him through his eighties metal-hair, which for some creepy reason he looks good with the metal-kid curly locks in 2017, you have to agree he has never apologized for anything he&amp;rsquo;s said or done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Insane Celebrity Mansions You Wish You Lived In</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-insane-celebrity-mansions-you-wish-you-lived-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 20:53:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-insane-celebrity-mansions-you-wish-you-lived-in/</guid>
      <description>SunSentinel We all dream of living in sprawling, luxurious, marble finished mansions. This will remain a dream for many of us but for most superstars; it is a reality. Most celebrities make a lot of money from their careers, and they also love to flaunt their fortunes. Considering the amount of money they make every year, it should not come as a surprise that they live in luxurious mega mansions in some of the most beautiful and exclusive neighborhoods on earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hilarious Photos Of Animals Taken At The Exact Perfect Moment</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/hilarious-photos-of-animals-taken-at-the-exact-perfect-moment/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2017 22:54:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/hilarious-photos-of-animals-taken-at-the-exact-perfect-moment/</guid>
      <description>DailyStar Wild animals are majestic, fascinating, frightening and at times, downright hilarious. Animal photography is a labor of love that requires a lot of patience and it may take a great deal of time to capture that perfect moment. However, whether out of pure luck or preparedness, some talented wildlife photographers have successfully captured some perfectly timed animal photos. Most of these incredible shots of animals looking goofy are so unbelievable such that you would have missed the moment just by blinking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Most Stunning Wives and Girlfriends of NBA Stars</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-most-stunning-wives-and-girlfriends-of-nba-stars/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2017 18:55:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-most-stunning-wives-and-girlfriends-of-nba-stars/</guid>
      <description>Over the past several years the NBA has turned into quite possibly the biggest sport in america, with more stars in the league than any other. With all of this new star-power, the pretty, and not so pretty, women are sure to not be far behind. We are here to keep you up to date with all of the off-court drama, and bring you the hottest (and strangest) wives and girlfriends of the NBA superstars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 20 Most Dangerous Prisons In The World</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-20-most-dangerous-prisons-in-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 21:33:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-20-most-dangerous-prisons-in-the-world/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re guilty of binge watching _Orange is the New Black_ and imagining what life would be like serving time in a corrections facility, you&amp;rsquo;re not alone. However, if you care to preserve that misguided fantasy, turn back now. In reality, prison doesn’t generally conjure feelings of safety or warm, fuzzy thoughts. But there are institutions that are so extraordinarily unsafe and inhumane, it defies imagination. For those who are curious about real life in some of the most notoriously dangerous prisons in the world, click on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Photos Politicians Don&#39;t Want You to See</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-photos-politicians-dont-want-you-to-see/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 21:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-photos-politicians-dont-want-you-to-see/</guid>
      <description>Politicians are required by the general population to behave their best. Most of them are known to spend fortunes working on their public image. However, as expected there are always those awkward instances captured on camera which they wish never happened, and you never see. Here is a collection of 20 pictures politicians cannot let you know. They include awkward handshakes, checking out each other’s anatomy and awkward hugs and kisses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>16 Times Donald Trump Broke the Law</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/16-times-donald-trump-broke-the-law/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/16-times-donald-trump-broke-the-law/</guid>
      <description>Wonkette     1. Misusing corporate resources 2. Deceptive business practices 3. Charitable Solicitation laws 4. IRS self-dealing law 5. 18 US CODE Section 599 6. Election’s self-funding law 7. Wisconsin Election law 8. State Education law 9. Copyright law 10. Immigration and labor laws 11. Anti-discrimination laws 12. Sexually harassing women 13. Sales tax laws 14.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 20 Most Deadly Animals in the World</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-20-most-deadly-animals-in-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-20-most-deadly-animals-in-the-world/</guid>
      <description>Over the years, there are those animals that have continued to steal the top position among the deadliest animals in the world. Although you cannot rule them out, there’s more to it than just brawn, large teeth, and venom defensive mechanisms when it comes to categorizing the most life-threatening creatures on the earth and in water. You think sharks, lions, and elephants are deadliest animals? You&amp;rsquo;re dead wrong. Some of the little creatures that you find cute and probably been playing around with are surprisingly extremely dangerous.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Behind The Scenes Facts About Forrest Gump You Didn&#39;t Know</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/behind-the-scenes-facts-about-forrest-gump-you-didnt-know/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 20:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/behind-the-scenes-facts-about-forrest-gump-you-didnt-know/</guid>
      <description>Forrest Gump turned Hollywood upside-down in 1994. Tom Hanks delivered, possibly, his finest performance to date, and many believe it to be one of the greatest films ever made. The movie had the perfect blend of humor, action and emotional drama, that really resonated with its audience. At the &amp;lsquo;Oscars&amp;rsquo; it won Best Picture and Tom Hanks won Best Actor. With all of its popularity, Forrest Gump has some unknown behind the scenes aspects, that even the most hardcore fan probably doesn&amp;rsquo;t even know about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Top 20 Dumbest Things Donald Trump Has Ever Done</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-top-20-dumbest-things-donald-trump-has-ever-done/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2017 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-top-20-dumbest-things-donald-trump-has-ever-done/</guid>
      <description>Other than being the president, it is indisputable that Donald Trump is entertaining. Most people are divided between hating and loving him; some refer to him as a buffoon. In front of a camera, Trump makes an effort not to show his ego. This has been seen on various occasions from honoring fallen soldiers to his family meetings. The efforts sometimes don&amp;rsquo;t just work! In some instances, he utters disgusting and offensive words against women.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Most Expensive &amp; Shocking Celebrity Plastic Surgeries</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/most-expensive-shocking-celebrity-plastic-surgeries/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 22:20:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/most-expensive-shocking-celebrity-plastic-surgeries/</guid>
      <description>Donatella Versace – $25,000 She is synonymous with her last name in the fashion industry. As she has aged she has tried to keep herself young. $25k, might seem like alot, but compared to the other names on this list, it is actually quite cheap. We&amp;rsquo;re thinking she wishes she had shelled out more money, because she looks sort of inhuman at this point!

Pinterest
Lil’ Kim – $19,625 With the passing of time comes a change for the better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>21 Rare Vietnam War Photos You Never Knew Existed</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/21-rare-vietnam-war-photos-you-never-knew-existed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/21-rare-vietnam-war-photos-you-never-knew-existed/</guid>
      <description>The Vietnam War remains to be one of the most controversial and deadliest in the world’s history especially the United States. The war lasted for 20 years and claimed approximately 3.5 million lives. It is estimated that about 60,000 of those who died were Americans who were fighting the Soviet Union. The cold war was based on the fact that the Soviet Union had to be stopped due to its political influence as well as the spread of its communism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 20 Smartest Presidents of All Time (And Where Trump Ranks Among Them)</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/top-20-smartest-presidents-of-all-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/top-20-smartest-presidents-of-all-time/</guid>
      <description>In 2006 Dean Simonton, psychology professor at University of California at Davis, finished researching the &amp;ldquo;intellectual brilliance&amp;rdquo; of 42 U.S. presidents. Some presidents pre-dated modern IQ testing. So Simonton estimated their scores with personality traits referenced in their biographies that indicate an above-average level of intelligence ­‑‑ &amp;ldquo;wise,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;inventive,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;artistic,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;curious,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;sophisticated,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;complicated,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;insightful.” From that study, we compiled a list of the top 20 smartest presidents. And where the current President (Donald Trump) ranks among them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extremely Rare Historical Photos You Won&#39;t Find In History Books</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/extremely-rare-historical-photos-you-wont-find-in-history-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 19:28:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/extremely-rare-historical-photos-you-wont-find-in-history-books/</guid>
      <description>If you think you know your history, get ready to be humbled. The rare photographs below show a different perspective of historical events, and you probably wouldn’t find them in any school textbook.
Imgur
Che Guevera &amp;amp; Fidel Castro BlazePress
Two very controversial political figures from Cuba, hang out together whilst fishing in the 60&amp;rsquo;s. Police Woman Chasing Skinny Dippers Vintag
Some brave fellas there, going skinny dipping in the middle of the day in a crowded park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tiffany Is Not The “Forgotten Trump” And Here&#39;s Why</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/tiffany-is-not-the-forgotten-trump-and-heres-why-ia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 05:45:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/tiffany-is-not-the-forgotten-trump-and-heres-why-ia/</guid>
      <description>Tiffany Trump, Donald&amp;rsquo;s youngest of two daughters, is the only child born out of his second marriage to Marla Maples. Tiffany has been called the “forgotten Trump” by various publications, as though she&amp;rsquo;s been all but forgotten since her father&amp;rsquo;s election to the presidency. But maybe Tiffany is only out of the limelight because she has a lot going on! Here&amp;rsquo;s a look at Tiffany&amp;rsquo;s life and what the future may hold for her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kardashians: The Unknown Early Years</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/kardashians-early-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 20:21:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/kardashians-early-years/</guid>
      <description>Even if you are not a fan, it is hard to look away from the rumors and gossip that follow the wealthy family. And safe to say there are many of them. From Kim’s bold magazine cover to Khloe’s real biological father, even if you don’t watch the show you most likely are aware of all the drama, since it is plastered all over our television sets, smartphones, tablets and computers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Lame To Fame: Amazing Celebrity Transformations That&#39;ll Make You Double-Take!</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/from-lame-to-fame-amazing-celebrity-transformations-thatll-make-you-double-take-ia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 05:58:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/from-lame-to-fame-amazing-celebrity-transformations-thatll-make-you-double-take-ia/</guid>
      <description>Stars grow up just like regular people. Plus, with the added pressure from fans and critics, it makes sense that celebrities would want to change a few things every now and again. From weight loss to total make overs, these 30 stars have had the biggest transformations of our time.
BET
Jonah Hill - 2016 InTouch
Jonah Hill has become rather well known for his rapid weight fluctuations. In 2016 he appeared to be bigger than he had ever been.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 20 Celebs You Didn&#39;t Know Were Gay</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/top-20-celebs-you-didnt-know-were-gay-ia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 05:57:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/top-20-celebs-you-didnt-know-were-gay-ia/</guid>
      <description>Many movie stars and artists are in gay relationships. Even though they try to keep their private life away from the public domain, they are eventually exposed. However, there are those who embrace who they are by admitting to the world that they are gay. Below is a list of 20 celebrities who you didn&amp;rsquo;t know were gay.
1. Tom Daley 
DailyStar Tom used a homemade video to break his silence regarding his relationship status.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful Hollywood Celebs: Then and Now</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/where-are-these-beautiful-celebrities-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 23:26:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/where-are-these-beautiful-celebrities-today/</guid>
      <description>We all remember these vixens from the 80&amp;rsquo;s and 90&amp;rsquo;s. They were beautiful celebrities starring in our favorite movies and TV shows. Over the years they have fallen out of the spotlight. But we are here to track them down for you and show how they have aged over the years. Some for better, some for tragically worse.

Kelly McGillis We fell in love with her in the 80&amp;rsquo;s as Maverick&amp;rsquo;s brainy beau, Charlie Blackwood, in &amp;lsquo;Top Gun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Most Shocking Wives and Girlfriends of NBA Stars</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-23-hottest-wags-in-the-nba/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 20:05:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-23-hottest-wags-in-the-nba/</guid>
      <description>Over the past several years the NBA has turned into quite possibly the biggest sport in america, with more stars in the league than any other. With all of this new star-power, the pretty, and not so pretty, women are sure to not be far behind. We are here to keep you up to date with all of the off-court drama, and bring you the hottest (and strangest) wives and girlfriends of the NBA superstars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Horribly Awkward Prom Photos</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-horribly-awkward-prom-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 21:04:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-horribly-awkward-prom-photos/</guid>
      <description>Highschool is a very awkward time to be alive. We are growing into out bodies, and learning how to be a social human. Have you ever gone back and looked at your cringeworthy prom photo from many years ago? Well, these are the worst of the worst! Enjoy!

Complex
Class Act Michelle Obama Caught in Wicked Chair 
Pinterest
Whoever thought that wicker would be great for a formal prom photo that would stick around for decades did not have two cents to rub together in the common sense category.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 20 Best Things Donald Trump Has Done In Office</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/top-20-best-things-donald-trump-has-done-in-office/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/top-20-best-things-donald-trump-has-done-in-office/</guid>
      <description>There are a lot of reports painting Trump as an entertaining president full of himself. Such news however valid they may be should also focus on the president&amp;rsquo;s achievements. It is indisputable that the Trump administration achieved some of its promises within the first 100 days in office.

Source Others are still in progress. Here are some of the presidents best achievements since taking the position.
1. Neil Gorsuch Supreme Court Justice Against all the odds, Trump managed not only to nominate but also confirm Neil Gorsuch as the Supreme Court Justice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 20 Celebs You Didn&#39;t Know Were Gay</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/top-20-celebs-you-didnt-know-were-gay/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 18:31:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/top-20-celebs-you-didnt-know-were-gay/</guid>
      <description>Many movie stars and artists are in gay relationships. Even though they try to keep their private life away from the public domain, they are eventually exposed. However, there are those who embrace who they are by admitting to the world that they are gay. Below is a list of 20 celebrities who you didn&amp;rsquo;t know were gay.
1. Tom Daley 
DailyStar Tom used a homemade video to break his silence regarding his relationship status.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Lame To Fame: Amazing Celebrity Transformations That&#39;ll Make You Double-Take!</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/from-lame-to-fame-amazing-celebrity-transformations-thatll-make-you-double-take/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 18:47:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/from-lame-to-fame-amazing-celebrity-transformations-thatll-make-you-double-take/</guid>
      <description>Stars grow up just like regular people. Plus, with the added pressure from fans and critics, it makes sense that celebrities would want to change a few things every now and again. From weight loss to total make overs, these 30 stars have had the biggest transformations of our time.

BET
Jonah Hill - 2016 
InTouch
Jonah Hill has become rather well known for his rapid weight fluctuations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game of Thrones Characters - How They Are Described in Book and How They Appear on TV</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/game-of-thrones-characters-how-they-are-described-in-book-and-how-they-appear-on-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 19:36:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/game-of-thrones-characters-how-they-are-described-in-book-and-how-they-appear-on-tv/</guid>
      <description>Lovers of HBO’s TV series Game of Thrones who have read George R.R Martin’s book _A Song of Ice and Fire_ upon which the series is based, acknowledge the fact that key differences exist between the characters in the book and TV series. Naturally, the nature of the medium allows some changes to take place as we transit from the books to a television show. Even as the show continues to develop through season 7, the differences between the book version and the show become more pronounced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Actors You didn&#39;t Realize Passed Away in 2017</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-actors-you-didnt-realize-passed-away-in-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 19:07:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/20-actors-you-didnt-realize-passed-away-in-2017/</guid>
      <description>Reddit Life is short, so they say. Any moment someone can die and when death strikes all we can do is mourn the departed soul and wish that it rest s in eternal peace. Unfortunately, death isn&amp;rsquo;t selective about who should go and who should remain on earth. Over the past few years, we have lost some of the greatest men and women who brought us unforgettable memories. 2017 hasn&amp;rsquo;t been any different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Celebrity Children All Grown Up</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/10-celebrity-children-all-grown-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 23:23:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/10-celebrity-children-all-grown-up/</guid>
      <description>Celebrities’ lives are splashed across a myriad of media outlets every day, all day. The reality is reporting on celebrities is really big business.
The children of these gifted, renowned individuals, however, are often purposefully hidden from the public for obvious reasons. What is quite fascinating is that celebrity offspring are frequently even more impressive than their parents. A large percentage of these celebrity children try to follow their parents’ professional career paths.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What The Cast Of Game Of Thrones Were Like Before They Got Famous</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/what-the-cast-of-game-of-thrones-were-like-before-they-got-famous/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 00:05:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/what-the-cast-of-game-of-thrones-were-like-before-they-got-famous/</guid>
      <description>Game of Thrones is undoubtedly one of the most popular shows to have ever graced the small screen. With its vast world and intriguing characters, this monster HBO original from writer George R.R. Martin premiered to great acclaim and a healthy fan craze. Part of the success is the cast, who are made up of some well-known names and newcomers alike.
TheSuperficial
Here is a look at what some of the brilliant cast was up to before they entered the world of Westeros.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>These 30 Celebrities Dodged Their Taxes And Ran From The IRS</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/these-30-celebrities-dodged-taxes-ran-from-the-irs-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2017 20:43:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/these-30-celebrities-dodged-taxes-ran-from-the-irs-2/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Money is a problem until you&amp;rsquo;ve got some.&amp;rdquo; This adage is true for some, but not for these riches-to-rags celebrities. Whether it be gambling, bad investing, or poor spending, these people have all had to evade the taxman at least once in their lives. From boxers to actors to presidents of the United States, here are 30 celebrities who fled the IRS.
Flickr
Pamela Anderson Flickr
Known as a bona fide sex symbol in the 1990s, Pamela Anderson has had a rough going of things as of late.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Celebrities Who Went Broke and Have To Work Normal Jobs</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/these-30-celebrities-dodged-their-taxes-and-ran-from-the-irs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2017 20:12:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/these-30-celebrities-dodged-their-taxes-and-ran-from-the-irs/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Money is a problem until you&amp;rsquo;ve got some.&amp;rdquo; This adage is true for some, but not for these riches-to-rags celebrities. Whether it be gambling, bad investing, or poor spending, these people have all had to evade the taxman at least once in their lives. From boxers to actors to presidents of the United States, here are 30 celebrities who lost it all.
Pinterest
Vanilla Ice Sells Real Estate MasterChollo</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Shocking Net Worth Of These Celebs Will Completely Boggle Your Mind</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/shocking-net-worths/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 17:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/shocking-net-worths/</guid>
      <description>Reddit Life is short, so they say. Any moment someone can die and when death strikes all we can do is mourn the departed soul and wish that it rest s in eternal peace. Unfortunately, death isn&amp;rsquo;t selective about who should go and who should remain on earth. Over the past few years, we have lost some of the greatest men and women who brought us unforgettable memories. 2017 hasn&amp;rsquo;t been any different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Much Does Dr. Oz Make? Net Worths Of Famous TV Doctors</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/tv-doctors-net-worth/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 20:59:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/tv-doctors-net-worth/</guid>
      <description>It takes a lot of hard work and training to become a doctor. But to become a doctor with your own television show? Now that&amp;rsquo;s tough. Thankfully, our favorite medical media personalities seem to earn back what they put into their programs (and then some)! Ever wondered what Dr. Phil earns in a year, or the net worth of hunky former Bachelor contestant Travis Stork? We&amp;rsquo;ve got the dirt!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Missing Son Comes Home 3 Years Later (Except It Isn&#39;t Him)</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/missing-son-comes-home-3-years-later/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 20:53:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/missing-son-comes-home-3-years-later/</guid>
      <description>YouTube The year was 1994 when Nicholas Barclay, a 13-year-old boy, completely vanished from his San Antonio home. For over three years, Nicholas remained a ghost and his parents and even the authorities had no leads on where he disappeared to. One day, the family received an unsettling phone call. It was a boy in Spain who claimed to be Nicholas. Who was this boy, actually? Keep reading to find out the shocking truth!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harrowing Confession Might Finally Crack Natalee Holloway Case</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/harrowing-confession-might-finally-crack-natalee-holloway-case/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 15:28:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/harrowing-confession-might-finally-crack-natalee-holloway-case/</guid>
      <description>Hollywoodlife In 2005, Alabama teen Natalee Holloway disappeared during her graduation trip in the Carribean island of Aruba. 12 years since Natalee went missing, the crime still remains unsolved. However, recent developments that have surfaced may offer new clues regarding her disappearance. Will this case full of mystery and intrigue finally be solved soon?
An Alabama Girl Hollywoodlife In 1986, Natalee was born in Clinton, Mississippi to David and Beth Holloway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Abandoned, Slowly Decaying Cruise Ship Given New Life With These Amazing Photos</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/abandoned-cruise-ship/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 18:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/abandoned-cruise-ship/</guid>
      <description>On January 13, 2012, a cruise ship hit an underwater rock formation off the coast of Tuscany. The Costa Concordia capsized, killing a total of 31 passengers and one crew member. In 2016, a photographer by the name of Jonathan Danko Kielkowski illegally swam out to the ship in order to take some photos. Here is a look at some of the amazing, eerie footage that he was able to capture once he climbed onboard&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It Took 45 Years For &#39;The Keepers&#39; Investigators To Rule This Out</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-keepers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 18:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-keepers/</guid>
      <description>Netflix Some cases become so mystifying that they become lost in the shuffle. Others tend to be dusted off with even a morsel of new evidence presented. The case you&amp;rsquo;re about to read about became so bizarre that it&amp;rsquo;s the subject of a new documentary. The subject of this case had big dreams as a high schooler&amp;hellip;
The Brightest In The Room Netflix Born in Lawrenceville, Pennsylvania, Sister Catherine &amp;ldquo;Cathy&amp;rdquo; Cesnik was one of the smartest kids in St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Texas Teens Disappeared 30 Years Ago. Today, Cops Got A New Lead</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/two-texas-teens-disappeared/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 17:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/two-texas-teens-disappeared/</guid>
      <description>Facebook For law enforcement, nothing is worse than when a murder case goes old. The public is begging for answers, the family for closure, and the system for justice. But sometimes there&amp;rsquo;s just not enough evidence. Like with the 1988 murder of two Texas teenagers in what investigators considered a possible religious (read Satanic) ritual. But their story isn&amp;rsquo;t over by a long shot. Now 30 years later, Texas police have made an arrest that just so happened to uncover new evidence in one of the state&amp;rsquo;s most grisly cold cases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Missing Son Comes Home 3 Years Later (Except It Isn&#39;t Him)</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/missing-son-comes-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 17:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/missing-son-comes-home/</guid>
      <description>YouTube The year was 1994 when Nicholas Barclay, a 13-year-old boy, completely vanished from his San Antonio home. For over three years, Nicholas remained a ghost and his parents and even the authorities had no leads on where he disappeared to. One day, the family received an unsettling phone call. It was a boy in Spain who claimed to be Nicholas. Who was this boy, actually? Keep reading to find out the shocking truth!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Employee&#39;s Cruise Disappearance 5 Years Ago Still Unsolved</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/missing-disney-cruise-line-crew-member/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 23:56:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/missing-disney-cruise-line-crew-member/</guid>
      <description>Embarking on a Disney cruise is intended to be a once in a lifetime experience, including character visits and excitement at every turn. Every aspect of the journey—from the food to the entertainment—is magical, but the disappearance of a ship&amp;rsquo;s employee in 2011 brought the joyful voyage to a sudden halt. The tragic disappearance of employee Rebecca Coriam on the cruise ship the Wonder in 2011 is still unexplained to this day, but there have been a couple of encouraging new breaks in the case that took our breath away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Does Ivanka Trump Do For The White House? Her &#39;Unprecedented&#39; Role</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/ivanka-trump-do-for-the-white-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 03:42:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/ivanka-trump-do-for-the-white-house/</guid>
      <description>The news made its way out in press releases at the end of March 2017: Ivanka Trump had finally figured out what exactly she&amp;rsquo;d be doing in the White House. Officials noted that she&amp;rsquo;d already been in an &amp;ldquo;unprecedented role,&amp;rdquo; different than previous presidential children (of course). Here&amp;rsquo;s a thorough roundup of her background and the secrets of her new role working for the most powerful man in the world (and dad).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tiffany Is Not The “Forgotten Trump” And Here&#39;s Why</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/why-dont-the-trumps-ever-talk-about-missing-daughter-tiffany/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 03:27:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/why-dont-the-trumps-ever-talk-about-missing-daughter-tiffany/</guid>
      <description>Tiffany Trump, Donald&amp;rsquo;s youngest of two daughters, is the only child born out of his second marriage to Marla Maples. Tiffany has been called the “forgotten Trump” by various publications, as though she&amp;rsquo;s been all but forgotten since her father&amp;rsquo;s election to the presidency. But maybe Tiffany is only out of the limelight because she has a lot going on! Here&amp;rsquo;s a look at Tiffany&amp;rsquo;s life and what the future may hold for her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artsy, Clever Vandalism That&#39;ll Make You Look At Your Dull World Differently</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/times-vandalism-improved-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 03:12:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/times-vandalism-improved-things/</guid>
      <description>and expensive way to ruin the environment around us and just means that resources are diverted away from more important matters just to tidy the place up. However, at its finest, vandalism can also be high art and truly capture some insight into the human condition. These pics don&amp;rsquo;t show that kind of vandalism, but it is the kind that makes you laugh when you see it. These vandals weren&amp;rsquo;t out to change the world, they were just out to make your day brighter!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ridiculous Celebrity Impulse Buys That Will Blow Your Socks Off</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/ridiculous-celebrity-impulse-buys/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 02:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/ridiculous-celebrity-impulse-buys/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve all impulsively bought that pack of gum while waiting in line at the supermarket. But imagine if you had millions of dollars burning in your pocket. What would you spend it on? If celebrities are any example, it&amp;rsquo;d probably be something pretty ridiculous. From pet cobras to blinged-out bathtubs, here are some of the most extravagant celebrity impulse buys on record.
And One $1,700 Plane Ticket For My Hat, Please Wikipedia</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Famous Celebs Who Are Frugal And Clip Coupons Just Like You</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/famous-celebs-frugal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/famous-celebs-frugal/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s no shame in pinching a few pennies, even if you are able to live rather lavishly. Lifestyles of the rich and the famous may make it seem like money isn&amp;rsquo;t an option, but some celebrities still prefer to spend frugally. These celebs actually use coupons to save some hard-earned cash, and you will be shocked by some of the stars that prefer to get a good deal!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>