<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Politics on Brainsation</title>
    <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/tags/politics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Politics on Brainsation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 17:43:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/tags/politics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>When 3 Conservatives Stop Into This Liberal Restaurant For Lunch, The Waitress Is In For A Big Surprise</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/when-3-conservatives-stop-into-this-liberal-restaurant-for-lunch-the-waitress-is-in-for-a-big-surprise/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 17:43:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/when-3-conservatives-stop-into-this-liberal-restaurant-for-lunch-the-waitress-is-in-for-a-big-surprise/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve all heard the old adage &amp;ldquo;never judge a book by its cover,&amp;rdquo; but the truth is we&amp;rsquo;re constantly making judgments about people and things around us. Most of the time it&amp;rsquo;s without even realizing it, just an automatic thing. You see someone wearing certain clothes or who looks a certain way and assume you know something about them. Rosalynd Harris thought she knew all about the three men who were seated in her section of the restaurant that afternoon just by the hats they were wearing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Legendary Presidents Ranked Dumbest To Smartest</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/20-legendary-presidents-ranked-dumbest-to-smartest/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 21:25:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/20-legendary-presidents-ranked-dumbest-to-smartest/</guid>
      <description>C|Net It&amp;rsquo;s no secret that in order to be elected president, you have to have some unique qualities. Sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s bravery. Sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s charm. Many would argue that sometimes, it&amp;rsquo;s just the ability to attract a wealthy and generous donor base. No matter what the specific appeal may be, it is true that no average person can coast to the Oval Office without having to work for it. When it comes to running the most powerful nation in the world, the standards are high and the stakes are higher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Legendary Presidents Ranked Dumbest To Smartest</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/20-legendary-presidents-ranked-dumbest-to-smartest/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 21:25:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/20-legendary-presidents-ranked-dumbest-to-smartest/</guid>
      <description>C|Net It&amp;rsquo;s no secret that in order to be elected president, you have to have some unique qualities. Sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s bravery. Sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s charm. Many would argue that sometimes, it&amp;rsquo;s just the ability to attract a wealthy and generous donor base. No matter what the specific appeal may be, it is true that no average person can coast to the Oval Office without having to work for it. When it comes to running the most powerful nation in the world, the standards are high and the stakes are higher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>These Politicians Are Popular, But Their Kids Are Absolute Nightmares</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/these-politicians-are-popular-but-their-kids-are-absolute-nightmares/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 01:55:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/these-politicians-are-popular-but-their-kids-are-absolute-nightmares/</guid>
      <description>dailymail We tend to hold those in political power to a higher standard than we do ourselves. We see them as the golden moral pillars of society; perfect humans who never so much as double park. Why? Great question. Politicians and the people that surround them are, in fact, normal humans. Hence, they are susceptible to the same struggles and moral failings as anyone, and that means that they can be pretty crappy parents sometimes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Photos Donald Trump Doesn&#39;t Want You To See</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/20-photos-donald-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 00:22:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/20-photos-donald-trump/</guid>
      <description>Here are 20 photos Donald Trump would pay Shadow Brokers to take off the internet for good, especially the 8th one.
1. Dishonoring the national flag CNN Trump went vocal with his famous 144 characters to blast out NFL star Colin Kaepernick&amp;rsquo;s deliberate choice to sit out of the National Anthem. However, as this photo reveals, Trump also has little or no allegiance to pledge for the anthem. Did things change after he became the president?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secrets About The Trump Family You Didn&#39;t Know</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/secrets-about-the-trump-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 23:25:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/secrets-about-the-trump-family/</guid>
      <description>Donald Trump and his family have been in the limelight since he ascended to the presidency, and mostly for the wrong reasons. This list brings to light some of the secrets of this family from a seemingly incestuous father-daughter relationship through the facts of a neglected daughter, to a son who spent an entire year partying.
1. A descendant of immigrants WBDaily From his campaign manifestos, you would think Trump’s family has been in America for the past four generations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 20 Richest Politicians in the World</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/the-20-richest-politicians-in-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 22:36:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/the-20-richest-politicians-in-the-world/</guid>
      <description>Politicians rise and become famous but most of appear to be rich even before they are elected to serve in public offices. Political career thrives with stable financial backing. While they earn a big salary when they get into the public office, some are richer than others. Most of them are from wealthy families and others have made their investments. Here is a list of the 20 richest politicians in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Photos Politicians Don&#39;t Want You to See</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/20-photos-politicians-dont-want-you-to-see/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 21:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/20-photos-politicians-dont-want-you-to-see/</guid>
      <description>Politicians are required by the general population to behave their best. Most of them are known to spend fortunes working on their public image. However, as expected there are always those awkward instances captured on camera which they wish never happened, and you never see. Here is a collection of 20 pictures politicians cannot let you know. They include awkward handshakes, checking out each other’s anatomy and awkward hugs and kisses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>16 Times Donald Trump Broke the Law</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/16-times-donald-trump-broke-the-law/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/16-times-donald-trump-broke-the-law/</guid>
      <description>Wonkette     1. Misusing corporate resources 2. Deceptive business practices 3. Charitable Solicitation laws 4. IRS self-dealing law 5. 18 US CODE Section 599 6. Election’s self-funding law 7. Wisconsin Election law 8. State Education law 9. Copyright law 10. Immigration and labor laws 11. Anti-discrimination laws 12. Sexually harassing women 13. Sales tax laws 14.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Top 20 Dumbest Things Donald Trump Has Ever Done</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/the-top-20-dumbest-things-donald-trump-has-ever-done/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2017 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/the-top-20-dumbest-things-donald-trump-has-ever-done/</guid>
      <description>Other than being the president, it is indisputable that Donald Trump is entertaining. Most people are divided between hating and loving him; some refer to him as a buffoon. In front of a camera, Trump makes an effort not to show his ego. This has been seen on various occasions from honoring fallen soldiers to his family meetings. The efforts sometimes don&amp;rsquo;t just work! In some instances, he utters disgusting and offensive words against women.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tiffany Is Not The “Forgotten Trump” And Here&#39;s Why</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/tiffany-is-not-the-forgotten-trump-and-heres-why-ia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 05:45:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/tiffany-is-not-the-forgotten-trump-and-heres-why-ia/</guid>
      <description>Tiffany Trump, Donald&amp;rsquo;s youngest of two daughters, is the only child born out of his second marriage to Marla Maples. Tiffany has been called the “forgotten Trump” by various publications, as though she&amp;rsquo;s been all but forgotten since her father&amp;rsquo;s election to the presidency. But maybe Tiffany is only out of the limelight because she has a lot going on! Here&amp;rsquo;s a look at Tiffany&amp;rsquo;s life and what the future may hold for her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 20 Best Things Donald Trump Has Done In Office</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/top-20-best-things-donald-trump-has-done-in-office/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/top-20-best-things-donald-trump-has-done-in-office/</guid>
      <description>There are a lot of reports painting Trump as an entertaining president full of himself. Such news however valid they may be should also focus on the president&amp;rsquo;s achievements. It is indisputable that the Trump administration achieved some of its promises within the first 100 days in office.

Source Others are still in progress. Here are some of the presidents best achievements since taking the position.
1. Neil Gorsuch Supreme Court Justice Against all the odds, Trump managed not only to nominate but also confirm Neil Gorsuch as the Supreme Court Justice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Does Ivanka Trump Do For The White House? Her &#39;Unprecedented&#39; Role</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/ivanka-trump-do-for-the-white-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 03:42:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/ivanka-trump-do-for-the-white-house/</guid>
      <description>The news made its way out in press releases at the end of March 2017: Ivanka Trump had finally figured out what exactly she&amp;rsquo;d be doing in the White House. Officials noted that she&amp;rsquo;d already been in an &amp;ldquo;unprecedented role,&amp;rdquo; different than previous presidential children (of course). Here&amp;rsquo;s a thorough roundup of her background and the secrets of her new role working for the most powerful man in the world (and dad).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tiffany Is Not The “Forgotten Trump” And Here&#39;s Why</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/why-dont-the-trumps-ever-talk-about-missing-daughter-tiffany/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 03:27:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/why-dont-the-trumps-ever-talk-about-missing-daughter-tiffany/</guid>
      <description>Tiffany Trump, Donald&amp;rsquo;s youngest of two daughters, is the only child born out of his second marriage to Marla Maples. Tiffany has been called the “forgotten Trump” by various publications, as though she&amp;rsquo;s been all but forgotten since her father&amp;rsquo;s election to the presidency. But maybe Tiffany is only out of the limelight because she has a lot going on! Here&amp;rsquo;s a look at Tiffany&amp;rsquo;s life and what the future may hold for her.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>