<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hot Female Athletes on Brainsation</title>
    <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/tags/hot-female-athletes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hot Female Athletes on Brainsation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 10:06:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/tags/hot-female-athletes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>15 Hottest Female Soccer Players On The Planet</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/15-hottest-female-soccer-players-on-the-planet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 10:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/15-hottest-female-soccer-players-on-the-planet/</guid>
      <description>Once seen as a male-dominated sport, female soccer players all over the globe are dominating both on and off the field. From their killer looks to their outrageous athletic ability, here are 15 of the most gorgeous and impressive women in soccer. Read on to see if your favorite made the list.
England&amp;rsquo;s Toni Duggan Twitter Toni Duggan celebrated her 18 birthday by scoring the opening goal in England&amp;rsquo;s 2009 UEFA Women&amp;rsquo;s Under-19 Championship final win against Sweden in Belarus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>These Female Olympians Have Our Hearts Racing, And You&#39;re About To See Why</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/female-olympians/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 07:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/female-olympians/</guid>
      <description>With the 2018 Olympics upon us, you might find yourself flipping through photos of hot female athletes &amp;ndash; so, we&amp;rsquo;ve saved you some trouble. While all athletes are in shape (it&amp;rsquo;s kind of a requirement of the job) some of them are just downright sexy. For many of them, time off from training means there&amp;rsquo;s plenty of time to model, and plenty of these ladies do just that. You may recognize a number of these sexy athletes from their various ads and photoshoots in which they aren&amp;rsquo;t at all shy about showing off their incredible bodies.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>