<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Olympic Athletes on Brainsation</title>
    <link>http://st.brainsation.com/tags/olympic-athletes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Olympic Athletes on Brainsation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 09:28:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://st.brainsation.com/tags/olympic-athletes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>15 Of The Sexiest Women In American Sports</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/15-of-the-sexiest-women-in-american-sports/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 09:28:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/15-of-the-sexiest-women-in-american-sports/</guid>
      <description>With the 2018 Winter Olympics coming to a close, I&amp;rsquo;m sure many of us are left wondering how so many of our highest-achieving athletes can also be graced with such good looks. We haven&amp;rsquo;t yet come up with the formula for Olympian success, but we did come up with a list of the 15 hottest female American athletes for you to swoon over.
Allison Stokke Cleverst Track and field athlete Allison Stokke got her start during school, breaking a number of American records for high school pole vaulting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>These Female Olympians Have Our Hearts Racing, And You&#39;re About To See Why</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/female-olympians/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 07:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/female-olympians/</guid>
      <description>With the 2018 Olympics upon us, you might find yourself flipping through photos of hot female athletes &amp;ndash; so, we&amp;rsquo;ve saved you some trouble. While all athletes are in shape (it&amp;rsquo;s kind of a requirement of the job) some of them are just downright sexy. For many of them, time off from training means there&amp;rsquo;s plenty of time to model, and plenty of these ladies do just that. You may recognize a number of these sexy athletes from their various ads and photoshoots in which they aren&amp;rsquo;t at all shy about showing off their incredible bodies.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>