<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Det on Brainsation</title>
    <link>http://st.brainsation.com/tags/det/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Det on Brainsation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 05:45:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://st.brainsation.com/tags/det/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tiffany Is Not The “Forgotten Trump” And Here&#39;s Why</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/tiffany-is-not-the-forgotten-trump-and-heres-why-ia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 05:45:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/tiffany-is-not-the-forgotten-trump-and-heres-why-ia/</guid>
      <description>Tiffany Trump, Donald&amp;rsquo;s youngest of two daughters, is the only child born out of his second marriage to Marla Maples. Tiffany has been called the “forgotten Trump” by various publications, as though she&amp;rsquo;s been all but forgotten since her father&amp;rsquo;s election to the presidency. But maybe Tiffany is only out of the limelight because she has a lot going on! Here&amp;rsquo;s a look at Tiffany&amp;rsquo;s life and what the future may hold for her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Celebrity Children All Grown Up</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/10-celebrity-children-all-grown-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 23:23:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/10-celebrity-children-all-grown-up/</guid>
      <description>Celebrities’ lives are splashed across a myriad of media outlets every day, all day. The reality is reporting on celebrities is really big business.
The children of these gifted, renowned individuals, however, are often purposefully hidden from the public for obvious reasons. What is quite fascinating is that celebrity offspring are frequently even more impressive than their parents. A large percentage of these celebrity children try to follow their parents’ professional career paths.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What The Cast Of Game Of Thrones Were Like Before They Got Famous</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/what-the-cast-of-game-of-thrones-were-like-before-they-got-famous/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 00:05:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/what-the-cast-of-game-of-thrones-were-like-before-they-got-famous/</guid>
      <description>Game of Thrones is undoubtedly one of the most popular shows to have ever graced the small screen. With its vast world and intriguing characters, this monster HBO original from writer George R.R. Martin premiered to great acclaim and a healthy fan craze. Part of the success is the cast, who are made up of some well-known names and newcomers alike.
TheSuperficial
Here is a look at what some of the brilliant cast was up to before they entered the world of Westeros.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Celebrities Who Went Broke and Have To Work Normal Jobs</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/these-30-celebrities-dodged-their-taxes-and-ran-from-the-irs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2017 20:12:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/these-30-celebrities-dodged-their-taxes-and-ran-from-the-irs/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Money is a problem until you&amp;rsquo;ve got some.&amp;rdquo; This adage is true for some, but not for these riches-to-rags celebrities. Whether it be gambling, bad investing, or poor spending, these people have all had to evade the taxman at least once in their lives. From boxers to actors to presidents of the United States, here are 30 celebrities who lost it all.
Pinterest
Vanilla Ice Sells Real Estate MasterChollo</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Shocking Net Worth Of These Celebs Will Completely Boggle Your Mind</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/shocking-net-worths/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 17:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/shocking-net-worths/</guid>
      <description>Reddit Life is short, so they say. Any moment someone can die and when death strikes all we can do is mourn the departed soul and wish that it rest s in eternal peace. Unfortunately, death isn&amp;rsquo;t selective about who should go and who should remain on earth. Over the past few years, we have lost some of the greatest men and women who brought us unforgettable memories. 2017 hasn&amp;rsquo;t been any different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Abandoned, Slowly Decaying Cruise Ship Given New Life With These Amazing Photos</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/abandoned-cruise-ship/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 18:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/abandoned-cruise-ship/</guid>
      <description>On January 13, 2012, a cruise ship hit an underwater rock formation off the coast of Tuscany. The Costa Concordia capsized, killing a total of 31 passengers and one crew member. In 2016, a photographer by the name of Jonathan Danko Kielkowski illegally swam out to the ship in order to take some photos. Here is a look at some of the amazing, eerie footage that he was able to capture once he climbed onboard&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It Took 45 Years For &#39;The Keepers&#39; Investigators To Rule This Out</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-keepers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 18:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/the-keepers/</guid>
      <description>Netflix Some cases become so mystifying that they become lost in the shuffle. Others tend to be dusted off with even a morsel of new evidence presented. The case you&amp;rsquo;re about to read about became so bizarre that it&amp;rsquo;s the subject of a new documentary. The subject of this case had big dreams as a high schooler&amp;hellip;
The Brightest In The Room Netflix Born in Lawrenceville, Pennsylvania, Sister Catherine &amp;ldquo;Cathy&amp;rdquo; Cesnik was one of the smartest kids in St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Texas Teens Disappeared 30 Years Ago. Today, Cops Got A New Lead</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/two-texas-teens-disappeared/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 17:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/two-texas-teens-disappeared/</guid>
      <description>Facebook For law enforcement, nothing is worse than when a murder case goes old. The public is begging for answers, the family for closure, and the system for justice. But sometimes there&amp;rsquo;s just not enough evidence. Like with the 1988 murder of two Texas teenagers in what investigators considered a possible religious (read Satanic) ritual. But their story isn&amp;rsquo;t over by a long shot. Now 30 years later, Texas police have made an arrest that just so happened to uncover new evidence in one of the state&amp;rsquo;s most grisly cold cases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Missing Son Comes Home 3 Years Later (Except It Isn&#39;t Him)</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/missing-son-comes-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 17:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/missing-son-comes-home/</guid>
      <description>YouTube The year was 1994 when Nicholas Barclay, a 13-year-old boy, completely vanished from his San Antonio home. For over three years, Nicholas remained a ghost and his parents and even the authorities had no leads on where he disappeared to. One day, the family received an unsettling phone call. It was a boy in Spain who claimed to be Nicholas. Who was this boy, actually? Keep reading to find out the shocking truth!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Employee&#39;s Cruise Disappearance 5 Years Ago Still Unsolved</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/missing-disney-cruise-line-crew-member/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 23:56:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/missing-disney-cruise-line-crew-member/</guid>
      <description>Embarking on a Disney cruise is intended to be a once in a lifetime experience, including character visits and excitement at every turn. Every aspect of the journey—from the food to the entertainment—is magical, but the disappearance of a ship&amp;rsquo;s employee in 2011 brought the joyful voyage to a sudden halt. The tragic disappearance of employee Rebecca Coriam on the cruise ship the Wonder in 2011 is still unexplained to this day, but there have been a couple of encouraging new breaks in the case that took our breath away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Does Ivanka Trump Do For The White House? Her &#39;Unprecedented&#39; Role</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/ivanka-trump-do-for-the-white-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 03:42:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/ivanka-trump-do-for-the-white-house/</guid>
      <description>The news made its way out in press releases at the end of March 2017: Ivanka Trump had finally figured out what exactly she&amp;rsquo;d be doing in the White House. Officials noted that she&amp;rsquo;d already been in an &amp;ldquo;unprecedented role,&amp;rdquo; different than previous presidential children (of course). Here&amp;rsquo;s a thorough roundup of her background and the secrets of her new role working for the most powerful man in the world (and dad).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tiffany Is Not The “Forgotten Trump” And Here&#39;s Why</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/why-dont-the-trumps-ever-talk-about-missing-daughter-tiffany/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 03:27:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/why-dont-the-trumps-ever-talk-about-missing-daughter-tiffany/</guid>
      <description>Tiffany Trump, Donald&amp;rsquo;s youngest of two daughters, is the only child born out of his second marriage to Marla Maples. Tiffany has been called the “forgotten Trump” by various publications, as though she&amp;rsquo;s been all but forgotten since her father&amp;rsquo;s election to the presidency. But maybe Tiffany is only out of the limelight because she has a lot going on! Here&amp;rsquo;s a look at Tiffany&amp;rsquo;s life and what the future may hold for her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artsy, Clever Vandalism That&#39;ll Make You Look At Your Dull World Differently</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/times-vandalism-improved-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 03:12:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/times-vandalism-improved-things/</guid>
      <description>and expensive way to ruin the environment around us and just means that resources are diverted away from more important matters just to tidy the place up. However, at its finest, vandalism can also be high art and truly capture some insight into the human condition. These pics don&amp;rsquo;t show that kind of vandalism, but it is the kind that makes you laugh when you see it. These vandals weren&amp;rsquo;t out to change the world, they were just out to make your day brighter!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ridiculous Celebrity Impulse Buys That Will Blow Your Socks Off</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/ridiculous-celebrity-impulse-buys/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 02:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/ridiculous-celebrity-impulse-buys/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve all impulsively bought that pack of gum while waiting in line at the supermarket. But imagine if you had millions of dollars burning in your pocket. What would you spend it on? If celebrities are any example, it&amp;rsquo;d probably be something pretty ridiculous. From pet cobras to blinged-out bathtubs, here are some of the most extravagant celebrity impulse buys on record.
And One $1,700 Plane Ticket For My Hat, Please Wikipedia</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Famous Celebs Who Are Frugal And Clip Coupons Just Like You</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/famous-celebs-frugal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/famous-celebs-frugal/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s no shame in pinching a few pennies, even if you are able to live rather lavishly. Lifestyles of the rich and the famous may make it seem like money isn&amp;rsquo;t an option, but some celebrities still prefer to spend frugally. These celebs actually use coupons to save some hard-earned cash, and you will be shocked by some of the stars that prefer to get a good deal!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>