<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Celebrities on Brainsation</title>
    <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/tags/celebrities/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Celebrities on Brainsation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 18:47:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/tags/celebrities/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>These Celebrities Fought Hard Against Drugs And Addiction, But Eventually Lost Everything</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/these-celebrities-fought-hard-against-drugs-and-addiction-but-eventually-lost-everything/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 18:47:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/these-celebrities-fought-hard-against-drugs-and-addiction-but-eventually-lost-everything/</guid>
      <description>NYDailyNews Our obsession with celebrities is a phenomenon as old as the moving picture. For some reason, a switch flips in our brains when we see someone on a screen that makes us want to know everything possible about that person and what they&amp;rsquo;re doing every single day. But the pressure of constantly being in the public eye can have an adverse effect on celebrities, most of whom are just regular people trying to live normal lives when they&amp;rsquo;re off-set.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>These Politicians Are Popular, But Their Kids Are Absolute Nightmares</title>
      <link>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/these-politicians-are-popular-but-their-kids-are-absolute-nightmares/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 01:55:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brainsation.com.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/post/these-politicians-are-popular-but-their-kids-are-absolute-nightmares/</guid>
      <description>dailymail We tend to hold those in political power to a higher standard than we do ourselves. We see them as the golden moral pillars of society; perfect humans who never so much as double park. Why? Great question. Politicians and the people that surround them are, in fact, normal humans. Hence, they are susceptible to the same struggles and moral failings as anyone, and that means that they can be pretty crappy parents sometimes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>