<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dtmob on Brainsation</title>
    <link>http://st.brainsation.com/tags/dtmob/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dtmob on Brainsation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2017 20:43:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://st.brainsation.com/tags/dtmob/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>These 30 Celebrities Dodged Their Taxes And Ran From The IRS</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/these-30-celebrities-dodged-taxes-ran-from-the-irs-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2017 20:43:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/these-30-celebrities-dodged-taxes-ran-from-the-irs-2/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Money is a problem until you&amp;rsquo;ve got some.&amp;rdquo; This adage is true for some, but not for these riches-to-rags celebrities. Whether it be gambling, bad investing, or poor spending, these people have all had to evade the taxman at least once in their lives. From boxers to actors to presidents of the United States, here are 30 celebrities who fled the IRS.
Flickr
Pamela Anderson Flickr
Known as a bona fide sex symbol in the 1990s, Pamela Anderson has had a rough going of things as of late.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Missing Son Comes Home 3 Years Later (Except It Isn&#39;t Him)</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/missing-son-comes-home-3-years-later/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 20:53:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/missing-son-comes-home-3-years-later/</guid>
      <description>YouTube The year was 1994 when Nicholas Barclay, a 13-year-old boy, completely vanished from his San Antonio home. For over three years, Nicholas remained a ghost and his parents and even the authorities had no leads on where he disappeared to. One day, the family received an unsettling phone call. It was a boy in Spain who claimed to be Nicholas. Who was this boy, actually? Keep reading to find out the shocking truth!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harrowing Confession Might Finally Crack Natalee Holloway Case</title>
      <link>http://st.brainsation.com/post/harrowing-confession-might-finally-crack-natalee-holloway-case/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 15:28:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://st.brainsation.com/post/harrowing-confession-might-finally-crack-natalee-holloway-case/</guid>
      <description>Hollywoodlife In 2005, Alabama teen Natalee Holloway disappeared during her graduation trip in the Carribean island of Aruba. 12 years since Natalee went missing, the crime still remains unsolved. However, recent developments that have surfaced may offer new clues regarding her disappearance. Will this case full of mystery and intrigue finally be solved soon?
An Alabama Girl Hollywoodlife In 1986, Natalee was born in Clinton, Mississippi to David and Beth Holloway.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>